<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss>
  <channel>
    <title>allwires</title>
    <link>[{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJaF1hQVQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFtRXw=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEF9YXA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtVVQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFtRWA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://www.accesswire.com/newsroom","container":".article-box","header":"a","description":".html-embed-21.w-embed","link":"a","date":".article-date","loadType":"puppeteer"}]</link>
    <description>feed for allwires</description>
    <item>
      <title>E3 Lithium Outlines 2024 Corporate Guidance and its Plans to Advance the Clearwater Project</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:16:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CALGARY, Alberta--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $EEMMF #canadianenergy--E3 Lithium is pleased to share its 2024 plans for advancing its Clearwater Project towards commercial operations.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221541557/en/E3-Lithium-Outlines-2024-Corporate-Guidance-and-its-Plans-to-Advance-the-Clearwater-Project/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steward Is Committed to Continuing to Work With Governor, Attorney General and State Regulators</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:58:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Today, Steward Health Care responded via letter to Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey, outlining the comprehensive financial documentation it has provided to various state agencies and regulatory bodies to date. The health care system also re-affirmed its commitment to working with the Commonwealth to ensure the continuity of safe, high-quality, and compassionate care for all patients. The full letter from Steward Health Care follows: Dear Governor Healey: We have revi</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221587747/en/Steward-Is-Committed-to-Continuing-to-Work-With-Governor-Attorney-General-and-State-Regulators/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Compression Partners Provides Update on 2023 K-1 Availability</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:38:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AUSTIN, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--USA Compression Partners, LP (NYSE: USAC) (“USA Compression”) today provided an update on the expected availability of the partnership’s 2023 Investor Tax Packages including Schedule K-1 for its common unitholders. Historically, USA Compression’s Investor Tax Packages have been available by the end of February for the preceding tax year; however, the timing of the availability of USA Compression’s 2023 Investor Tax Packages is dependent upon actions of the U.S. C</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221043744/en/USA-Compression-Partners-Provides-Update-on-2023-K-1-Availability/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratus Properties Inc. Responds to Unsolicited, Non-Binding Acquisition Proposal</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AUSTIN, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Stratus Properties Inc. (NASDAQ: STRS) (“Stratus” or the “Company”) today confirmed that on January 24, 2024 it received an unsolicited, non-binding proposal from NXSTEP Opportunity Partners (“NXSTEP”) to acquire Stratus for $27.18 per share in cash, subject to adjustments. NXSTEP’s proposal was subject to a number of conditions and assumptions, including important assumptions that were incorrect. Stratus’ Board of Directors (“Board”) considered the proposal and</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221907954/en/Stratus-Properties-Inc.-Responds-to-Unsolicited-Non-Binding-Acquisition-Proposal/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veritone Announces Restructuring Initiatives</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DENVER--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Veritone, Inc. (NASDAQ: VERI), a leader in enterprise AI software and solutions, today announced that it has implemented various restructuring initiatives with the purpose of optimizing Veritone’s organizational structure and accelerating its path to profitability. These initiatives, which began in January 2024, include a workforce reduction that will impact approximately 14% of Veritone’s worldwide workforce, with the majority of these workforce actions being completed</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221115992/en/Veritone-Announces-Restructuring-Initiatives/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BuzzFeed, Inc. Announces Sale of Complex to NTWRK in All-Cash Deal</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--BuzzFeed, Inc. Announces Sale of Complex to NTWRK in All-Cash Deal</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221201645/en/BuzzFeed-Inc.-Announces-Sale-of-Complex-to-NTWRK-in-All-Cash-Deal/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sonoran Announces a Positive Pre-Feasibility Study for the Cactus Mine Project with a US$509M Post-Tax NPV and 55 kstpa Copper Cathode over 21 Years</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:54:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CASA GRANDE, Ariz. &amp; TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $ASCU #Arizona--ASCU today announced it has completed its NI 43-101 Prefeasibility Study (“PFS”) for its Cactus Project in Arizona, USA.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221970177/en/Arizona-Sonoran-Announces-a-Positive-Pre-Feasibility-Study-for-the-Cactus-Mine-Project-with-a-US509M-Post-Tax-NPV-and-55-kstpa-Copper-Cathode-over-21-Years/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milliman analysis: Multiemployer pension funding at 89% in aggregate at year-end 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:45:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SEATTLE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Milliman has just released the latest results of its Multiemployer Pension Funding Study.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221263670/en/Milliman-analysis-Multiemployer-pension-funding-at-89-in-aggregate-at-year-end-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Software Included in Security Services Edge (SSE) Landscape Report by Independent Research Firm</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:26:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SEATTLE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--The Forrester "Security Service Edge (SSE) Solutions Landscape" helps organizations understand how Absolute helps them to address SSE use cases.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220838597/en/Absolute-Software-Included-in-Security-Services-Edge-SSE-Landscape-Report-by-Independent-Research-Firm/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightsource bp Completes $348 Million Financing Package for Two Utility-Scale Solar Projects in Texas</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN FRANCISCO--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #ERCOT--Lightsource bp completes $348 million financing for two utility-scale solar projects, additional energy security and diversification for Texas grid</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221400563/en/Lightsource-bp-Completes-348-Million-Financing-Package-for-Two-Utility-Scale-Solar-Projects-in-Texas/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWISSto12 named in “10 Hottest Satellite Companies” Annual List</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:17:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LAUSANNE, Switzerland--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #geostationary--SWISSto12, one of Europe’s fastest growing satellite and Radio Frequency product manufacturers, has been named by Via Satellite as one of the “10 Hottest Satellite Companies” in its annual list. Now in its sixth year, Via Satellite’s list highlights the “must watch” companies within the satellite sector who provide ground systems, manufacturing, imagery and sensing, satellite communications and launch services. Short-listed companies are selected by Via S</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221158949/en/SWISSto12-named-in-%E2%80%9C10-Hottest-Satellite-Companies%E2%80%9D-Annual-List/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGYL AI Completes Rebranding and Further Diversifies Product Offerings</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NASHVILLE, Tenn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--AGYL AI will now be the parent company for Writerly, EKOM, and AGYL Labs, allowing the company to streamline operations and accelerate growth.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221591359/en/AGYL-AI-Completes-Rebranding-and-Further-Diversifies-Product-Offerings/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aeSolutions Opens New Houston Office in Energy Corridor</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:35:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #ICS--aeSolutions, a leading consulting, engineering, and systems integration company specializing in industrial process safety and automation products and services, announces the opening of its newest office located in Houston’s Energy Corridor. The relocation is part of the company’s aggressive strategic growth plans and will serve as a hub for its operations in the Gulf Coast region. The new office will allow aeSolutions to enhance its service offerings in the energy sect</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221395818/en/aeSolutions-Opens-New-Houston-Office-in-Energy-Corridor/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propel Software Enhances Product Value Across Engineering, Sales, Marketing, and Service in 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:03:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SANTA CLARA, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #propelpvm--Propel Software, creator of the first product value management (PVM) platform, optimized speed, efficiency and value as it continued to disrupt the Product Lifecycle Management (PLM) category in 2023. Last year, Propel announced three major product releases providing ground-breaking solutions that reduce risk, decrease time to market, and get customers up and running quickly. Built on one of the world’s most secure business platforms, Salesforce, Propel PVM</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221672606/en/Propel-Software-Enhances-Product-Value-Across-Engineering-Sales-Marketing-and-Service-in-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Braze Continues Business Momentum with $500M CARR, New Global Leaders, and Marquee New Customers</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $BRZE--Braze (Nasdaq: BRZE), the leading customer engagement platform that empowers brands to Be Absolutely Engaging™, today announced strategic leadership appointments and new customer wins on the heels of a significant financial milestone. As previously announced, the company recently passed $500 million of Committed Annual Recurring Revenue (CARR), demonstrating the continued demand for Braze as brands recognize the critical role of customer engagement in driving growth,</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221186553/en/Braze-Continues-Business-Momentum-with-500M-CARR-New-Global-Leaders-and-Marquee-New-Customers/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortanix Surpasses Multiple Milestones, Reports Strong Growth for Fiscal Year 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SANTA CLARA, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Fortanix® Inc., a leader in data-first cybersecurity and pioneer of Confidential Computing, today announced another outstanding year for sales, strategic partnerships, product introductions and workforce expansion. During the fiscal year ended Jan. 31, 2024, Fortanix registered strong performance in critical areas, including the largest deal in company history, record new customer acquisitions—including the company’s first customers in the Japan and MENA re</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221041013/en/Fortanix-Surpasses-Multiple-Milestones-Reports-Strong-Growth-for-Fiscal-Year-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone Star Analysis Ltd. Opens New Headquarters in Lincoln</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LINCOLNSHIRE, England--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Lone Star Analysis Ltd., a trusted provider of leading-edge predictive and prescriptive analytics and Evolved AI®, has expanded its presence in the U.K., opening its new headquarters in Lincoln, England. This new space was necessitated by the Lone Star's rapid growth in the U.K. and enhances the company's capacity to serve customers in the United Kingdom, Europe, and the Middle East. The occasion was marked by a formal ribbon cutting ceremony. Air Chief M</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221055598/en/Lone-Star-Analysis-Ltd.-Opens-New-Headquarters-in-Lincoln/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sidus Space Reports Inducement Grant to New Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Sidus Space (NASDAQ: SIDU) (the “Company” or “Sidus”), a multi-faceted Space and Data-as-a-Service company, today announced the grant of an inducement award to the Company’s newly appointed Chief Financial Officer, Bill White. In connection with Mr. White’s appointment, the Sidus Space Board of Directors approved a stock option grant to Mr. White as an inducement material to Mr. White entering into employment with Sidus Space in accordance with Nasdaq List</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221122150/en/Sidus-Space-Reports-Inducement-Grant-to-New-Chief-Financial-Officer/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coya Therapeutics Issues Letter to Stockholders Highlighting Expansion of COYA 302 into Alzheimer’s Disease and Coya’s Pathway to a “Pipeline in a Product”</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Coya Therapeutics, Inc. (NASDAQ: COYA) (“Coya” or the “Company”), a clinical-stage biotechnology company developing multiple therapeutic programs intended to enhance regulatory T cell (Treg) function, releases the following letter to stockholders from its Chief Executive Officer and Chairman, Dr. Howard Berman. Dear Fellow Stockholders, Just over two months ago we announced our partnership with Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories for COYA 302 in Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221388488/en/Coya-Therapeutics-Issues-Letter-to-Stockholders-Highlighting-Expansion-of-COYA-302-into-Alzheimer%E2%80%99s-Disease-and-Coya%E2%80%99s-Pathway-to-a-%E2%80%9CPipeline-in-a-Product%E2%80%9D/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Trial Firm Elsberg Baker &amp;amp; Maruri PLLC Launches With Six Founding Partners From Selendy Gay Elsberg, Quinn Emanuel</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--A group of six renowned litigators led by David Elsberg, most recently a name partner at Selendy Gay Elsberg, and Rollo Baker IV and Silpa Maruri, former practice group leaders at Quinn Emanuel Urquhart &amp;amp; Sullivan, today launched a new trial law firm, Elsberg Baker &amp;amp; Maruri PLLC. The firm’s founding partners also include two former partners at Selendy Gay Elsberg, Michael Duke and Vivek Tata, as well as Jared Ruocco, a former partner at LTL Attorneys who previ</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220168006/en/New-Trial-Firm-Elsberg-Baker-Maruri-PLLC-Launches-With-Six-Founding-Partners-From-Selendy-Gay-Elsberg-Quinn-Emanuel/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concentric AI Achieves 200-percent Growth in 2023 as Leader in Data Security Posture Management</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN JOSE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #AI--Concentric AI, a leading vendor of intelligent AI-based solutions for autonomous data security posture management (DSPM), today announced a record year for 2023, which saw customer count triple and sales grow by 200 percent over 2022. The company continues to see significant rising sales traction across the board, particularly in industries with heightened data security and compliance concerns, including healthcare, financial services, energy, manufacturing, e</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221297522/en/Concentric-AI-Achieves-200-percent-Growth-in-2023-as-Leader-in-Data-Security-Posture-Management/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joby Completes Third Stage of FAA Certification Process</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SANTA CRUZ, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Joby Aviation, Inc. (NYSE:JOBY), a company developing electric air taxis for commercial passenger service, today announced it has become the first developer of electric vertical take-off and landing (eVTOL) aircraft to complete the third of five stages of the Federal Aviation Administration (“FAA”) type certification process. During the third stage of the process, Joby submitted certification plans that cover all of the aircraft’s structural, mechanical, and</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221698764/en/Joby-Completes-Third-Stage-of-FAA-Certification-Process/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floor &amp;amp; Decor Announces Grand Opening of Summerfield, Florida Store</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ATLANTA--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Floor &amp;amp; Decor (NYSE: FND), the leading high-growth retailer specializing in hard-surface flooring for homeowners and professionals, has announced the grand opening of its sixth warehouse location in Orlando/Ocala, with the addition of its newest location in Summerfield at 17115 SE 109th Terrace Road. The warehouse store and design center will open with a team of about 50 full-time and part-time associates led by Robert Tramel, the store Chief Executive Merchant. “W</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221732718/en/Floor-Decor-Announces-Grand-Opening-of-Summerfield-Florida-Store/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bioAffinity Technologies News Update</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN ANTONIO--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #ATS--bioAffinity Technologies shares the latest news updates about the company and its CyPath Lung noninvasive test for lung cancer.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221772695/en/bioAffinity-Technologies-News-Update/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoPark Announces 2P Reserve Replacement of 110%</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOGOTA, Colombia--(BUSINESS WIRE)--GeoPark Limited (“GeoPark” or the “Company”) (NYSE: GPRK), a leading independent Latin American oil and gas explorer, operator and consolidator, today announced its independent oil and gas reserves assessment, certified by DeGolyer and MacNaughton Corp. (D&amp;amp;M) under PRMS methodology, as of December 31, 2023. All reserves included in this release refer to GeoPark working interest before royalties paid in kind, except when specified. All figures are expressed</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240219121435/en/GeoPark-Announces-2P-Reserve-Replacement-of-110/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caesarstone Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MP MENASHE, Israel--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Caesarstone Ltd. (NASDAQ: CSTE), a leading developer and manufacturer of high-quality engineered surfaces, today reported financial results for its fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Yos Shiran, Caesarstone’s Chief Executive Officer commented, “In 2023, we implemented a new strategic plan and initiated significant restructuring actions which allowed us to achieve our primary financial objective for 2023, to generate positive cash flow from</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221191174/en/Caesarstone-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premier Packaging obtiene la condición de empresa propiedad de mujeres</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:55:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOUISVILLE, Kentucky--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Premier Packaging se enorgullece de anunciar que ha completado un importante requisito previo que permitirá a la empresa solicitar la certificación oficial Women Business Enterprise (WBE). A partir del 1 de marzo de 2024, Jill Gaynor asumirá las funciones de directora ejecutiva y accionista mayoritaria de la empresa de fabricación y distribución. En cuanto Jill Gaynor, actual directora de Marketing, asuma sus nuevas funciones, John Gaynor, actual propietar</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221539900/es/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premier Packaging Becomes Woman-Owned Business Enterprise</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 08:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOUISVILLE, Ky.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #Packaging--Premier Packaging is excited to announce it is seeking its official Women Business Enterprise (WBE) certification.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221179747/en/Premier-Packaging-Becomes-Woman-Owned-Business-Enterprise/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinovac Amends Shareholder Rights Plan</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:56:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BEIJING--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Sinovac Biotech Ltd. (“Sinovac” or the “Company”) (NASDAQ: SVA), a leading provider of biopharmaceutical products in China, today announced that its board of directors has amended its shareholder rights plan. The amendment extends the expiration date of the plan from February 22, 2024 to February 22, 2025. About SINOVAC Sinovac Biotech Ltd. (SINOVAC) is a China-based biopharmaceutical company that focuses on the R&amp;amp;D, manufacturing, and commercialization of biomedic</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220368905/en/Sinovac-Amends-Shareholder-Rights-Plan/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Payments Announces Pricing of Offering of $1.75 Billion of Convertible Senior Notes due 2031</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 04:39:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ATLANTA--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Global Payments Inc. (NYSE: GPN) today announced the pricing of its previously announced offering of $1.75 billion in aggregate principal amount of its 1.50% convertible senior notes due 2031 (the “Convertible Notes”). The Company granted the initial purchasers of the Convertible Notes an option to purchase, for settlement within a 13-day period beginning on, and including, the first date on which the Convertible Notes are issued, up to an additional $250 million aggre</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220511053/en/Global-Payments-Announces-Pricing-of-Offering-of-1.75-Billion-of-Convertible-Senior-Notes-due-2031/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YChnX-dlxR7bnql9VXy9e6PGT9SADxPkw1YVQTD4nSDrCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3k94Xo7_69M07VeF2vYttikOoOnRBQBKcY2buBEMh6FZQ==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haomo raises over RMB 100 million in Series B1 to speed up autonomous driving commercialization</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:58:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BEIJING--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Haomo.AI raised more than RMB 100 million in Series B1 round from Chengdu Wufa Private Equity Fund Management Co., Ltd. in the first such deal in the autonomous driving sector after China’s Lunar New Year holiday, to enhance R&amp;amp;D and support Wuhou district of Chengdu, Southwest China’s Sichuan Province, to develop robotics. "As a central district of Chengdu, Wuhou not only has a long history, but also leads in economic development. Wuhou has attracted investment and</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221571943/en/Haomo-raises-over-RMB-100-million-in-Series-B1-to-speed-up-autonomous-driving-commercialization/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crow Holdings Closes Tenth U.S. Diversified Value-Add Real Estate Fund at $3.1 Billion</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:42:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Crow Holdings, a leading national real estate investment and development firm, announced today the final close of Crow Holdings Realty Partners X, L.P. (“Fund X” or the “Fund”) at $3.1 billion of commitments with more than 70% of prior investors re-upping their investment in the flagship value-add fund series, and with significant participation from new investors that includes global banks, sovereign wealth funds, insurance companies, pension plans, family offices, and</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221214451/en/Crow-Holdings-Closes-Tenth-U.S.-Diversified-Value-Add-Real-Estate-Fund-at-3.1-Billion/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equitrans Midstream Announces Pricing of Private Offering of Senior Notes</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:27:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CANONSBURG, Pa.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Equitrans Midstream Corporation (NYSE: ETRN) (ETRN) today announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, EQM Midstream Partners, LP (EQM), has priced an offering of $600 million in aggregate principal amount of its 6.375% senior notes due 2029 (the Notes). The Notes will be issued at a price of par. EQM intends to use the net proceeds from the offering of the Notes to repay certain outstanding indebtedness, including borrowings under EQM’s Third Amended and Restat</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221290648/en/Equitrans-Midstream-Announces-Pricing-of-Private-Offering-of-Senior-Notes/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawai‘i Community Foundation Awards Grant to Restore and Steward Kula Lands Burned by Wildfire</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>KULA, Hawaii--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Hawai‘i Community Foundation awards a grant from the Maui Strong Fund to the Kula Community Watershed Alliance to support restoration of Kula lands.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221133034/en/Hawai%E2%80%98i-Community-Foundation-Awards-Grant-to-Restore-and-Steward-Kula-Lands-Burned-by-Wildfire/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Water Awarded New Research Grant Focusing on Early Warning System for Algal Blooms</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CAMDEN, N.J.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--American Water (NYSE: AWK), the largest regulated water and wastewater utility company in the U.S., today announced that it has been awarded a new grant from The Water Research Foundation (WRF), Determining the Role of Spectral Imaging as an Early Warning System for Presence/Significance of Algal Blooms [5266]. This research aims to develop cost-effective tools for early and reliable identification of harmful algal blooms. “American Water is delighted to partner w</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221572773/en/American-Water-Awarded-New-Research-Grant-Focusing-on-Early-Warning-System-for-Algal-Blooms/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orkes Raises $20M in Fresh Funding as Its Application Orchestration Platform Grows in Popularity With Developers and Enterprises</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:08:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CUPERTINO, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Orkes, whose platform offers the fastest way to scale distributed systems, has raised $20 million in new funding. The company has experienced significant growth since its initial launch and $9.3 million raise in 2022, including revealing a suite of industry-first AI tools and winning large multinational customers such as United Wholesale Mortgage, Foxtel, and up-and-coming startups like Collective. Thousands of organizations and Fortune 100 companies rely on</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221820989/en/Orkes-Raises-20M-in-Fresh-Funding-as-Its-Application-Orchestration-Platform-Grows-in-Popularity-With-Developers-and-Enterprises/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RET Ventures Leads $7.5 Million Series A in Conservation Labs to Interpret Sound for Water Conservation and Machinery Maintenance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PITTSBURGH--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Artificial intelligence company raises Series A; technology decodes acoustics into real-time insights to save industries billions of dollars.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221698668/en/RET-Ventures-Leads-7.5-Million-Series-A-in-Conservation-Labs-to-Interpret-Sound-for-Water-Conservation-and-Machinery-Maintenance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLARA Analytics Secures Funding From Nationwide</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SUNNYVALE, Calif. &amp; COLUMBUS, Ohio--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #AI--Nationwide investment in insurtech CLARA Analytics to fuel insurance claims optimization as the value of AI in claims management is recognized.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221342919/en/CLARA-Analytics-Secures-Funding-From-Nationwide/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insamo Launches with $12M Funding from Playground Global, venBio, and MRL Ventures Fund to Develop Best-in-Class Membrane-Permeable Macrocyclic Peptides</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:20:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BERKELEY, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Insamo Launches with $12M Funding from Playground Global, venBio, and MRL Ventures to Develop Best-in-Class Membrane-Permeable Macrocyclic Peptides</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221132401/en/Insamo-Launches-with-12M-Funding-from-Playground-Global-venBio-and-MRL-Ventures-Fund-to-Develop-Best-in-Class-Membrane-Permeable-Macrocyclic-Peptides/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strata Clean Energy Secures $559 Million Financing for 1GWh Battery Energy Storage Project in Arizona</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PHOENIX--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Strata Clean Energy Secures $559 Million Financing for 255MW/1,020MWh Scatter Wash battery storage complex to be operational by April 2025</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221070832/en/Strata-Clean-Energy-Secures-559-Million-Financing-for-1GWh-Battery-Energy-Storage-Project-in-Arizona/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ventiva Closes $10M Series C Investment Round</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:03:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>FREMONT, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Ventiva®, a leading company in active cooling solutions for electronic devices, today announced the successful completion of its $10 million Series C funding round. The investment was obtained from a balanced mix of new money from multiple investment funds along with strong participation from existing investors. The investment brings the total amount raised by Ventiva since inception to more than $40 million and will be used to further accelerate the company’s</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221621455/en/Ventiva-Closes-10M-Series-C-Investment-Round/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equitrans Midstream Announces Private Offering of Senior Notes</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CANONSBURG, Pa.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Equitrans Midstream Corporation (NYSE: ETRN) today announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, EQM Midstream Partners, LP (EQM), intends to offer, subject to market conditions, $600 million in aggregate principal amount of senior notes due 2029 (the Notes) in a private offering. EQM intends to use the net proceeds from the offering of the Notes to repay certain of its outstanding indebtedness, including borrowings under EQM’s Third Amended and Restated Credit A</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220235417/en/Equitrans-Midstream-Announces-Private-Offering-of-Senior-Notes/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affiliate of Paceline Equity Partners Makes Investment in Optimal Blue</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--An affiliate of Paceline Equity Partners, LLC (“Paceline”), a Dallas-based private equity manager, today announced that it has made a debt investment in a subsidiary of Constellation Software, Inc. (“Constellation”, TSX: CSU). Constellation acquires, manages and builds vertical market software businesses that provide mission-critical software solutions. As publicly announced on July 17, 2023, Intercontinental Exchange, Inc. (NYSE: ICE) and Black Knight, Inc. entered int</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220631399/en/Affiliate-of-Paceline-Equity-Partners-Makes-Investment-in-Optimal-Blue/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The OBIO® Investment Summit reaches new heights, drawing the attention of international capital to Canadian healthcare innovations</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--The OBIO® Investment Summit brings together global investors with emerging Canadian life sciences and health tech companies, technology innovators and ecosystem partners. This year, the Summit was held from February 14-16 at our new home, the Schwartz Reisman Innovation Centre in downtown Toronto. The Summit showcased over 90 of Canada's most promising early-stage companies, top universities and research institutions, giving them the opportunity to convene with interna</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221681232/en/The-OBIO%C2%AE-Investment-Summit-reaches-new-heights-drawing-the-attention-of-international-capital-to-Canadian-healthcare-innovations/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI lève 110 millions USD de financement de série C</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>JACKSONVILLE, Floride--(BUSINESS WIRE)--MMI (Medical Microinstruments, Inc.), une société de robotique qui se consacre à l’augmentation des options de traitement et à l’amélioration des résultats cliniques pour les patients souffrant de maladies complexes, a annoncé aujourd’hui avoir levé 110 millions USD en financement de série C. Dirigé par Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company, le tour de table est le plus grand investissement jamais réalisé en faveur de l’innovation en microchirurgie.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221192170/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI reúne 110 millones de dólares de financiamiento de serie C</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>JACKSONVILLE, Florida--(BUSINESS WIRE)--MMI (Medical Microinstruments, Inc.), una empresa de robótica dedicada a aumentar las opciones de tratamiento y mejorar los resultados clínicos de los pacientes con patologías complejas, ha anunciado hoy que ha recaudado 110 millones de dólares de serie C. La ronda, liderada por Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company, supone la mayor inversión de la historia en la innovación de la microcirugía. Los fondos financiarán la comercialización del sistema qu</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221398199/es/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI nimmt $110 Millionen bei Series C Financing auf</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--MMI (Medical Microinstruments, Inc.) ist ein Roboterhersteller, der neue Behandlungsmethoden für Patienten mit komplexen Beschwerden entwickelt. Heute hat das Unternehmen bekannt gegeben, dass es $110 Millionen bei einer Series C-Finanzierungsrunde aufgenommen hat. Diese wurde von Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company geleitet. Es handelt sich um die höchste jemals in die Innovation der Mikrochirurgie getätigte Investition. Die Finanzmittel werden die V</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221416718/de/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI 在 C 輪融資中籌集到1.1億美元</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>傑克遜維爾，佛羅里達州--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美國商業資訊)-- MMI（Medical Microinstruments, Inc.），一家致力於擴大治療選項並為複雜病情患者提升臨床成果的機器人技術公司，今日宣布成功完成1.1億美元的C輪融資。該輪融資由富達管理研究公司（Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company）領頭，創下了微創手術創新領域迄今最高的投資紀錄。 這筆資金將被用於推進 Symani® 手術系統在快速成長市場的商業化進程，同時也將資助持續的研究，這些研究旨在積累臨床證據及推動疾病適應範圍的擴大。此外，這些投資將促進先進技術能力的快速發展，並賦能 MMI 在全球範圍內擴展其運營能力。 MMI 以及其所有現有投資者——他們均參與了此次C輪融資——認為迅速成長的機會巨大。該公司預計，在技術進步和適應症範圍擴展的驅動下，適合進行機器人微創手術的市場規模將從每年的300萬例激增至2028年的2200萬例。 MMI 的首席執行官 Mark Toland 提到：「在醫療機器人投資成長趨緩的當下，這份來自投資者的支持增強了我們對</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221428705/zh-HK/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI haalt $ 110 miljoen op in Serie C-financiering</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--MMI (Medical Microinstruments, Inc.), een roboticabedrijf dat zich toelegt op het vergroten van de behandelingsopties en het verbeteren van de klinische resultaten voor patiënten met complexe aandoeningen, heeft vandaag aangekondigd dat het $ 110 miljoen aan Serie C-financiering heeft opgehaald. De ronde, geleid door Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company, markeert de grootste investering ooit in microchirurgie-innovatie. De fondsen zullen de commerciali</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221590727/nl/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI、シリーズC資金調達で1億1000万ドルを調達</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>フロリダ州ジャクソンビル--(BUSINESS WIRE)--（ビジネスワイヤ） -- 複雑な病状を抱える患者の治療選択肢を増やし、臨床転帰の改善に取り組むロボット企業のMMI (Medical Microinstruments, Inc.)は、シリーズC資金調達で1億1000万ドルを調達したことを発表しました。フィデリティ・マネジメント・アンド・リサーチ・カンパニーが主導するこの投資ラウンドは、マイクロサージェリーの技術革新に対する投資としては過去最大規模となります。 この資金は、高成長市場におけるSymani® Surgical Systemの商業化と、臨床証拠を生み出し、適応症状の拡大を可能にする研究への継続的な投資を支援するために活用されます。また、先進技術への投資を加速させ、MMIの事業能力をグローバルに拡張できるようにします。 MMIとその既存投資家、シリーズCの資金調達に貢献した投資家は全員、急速な成長の機会がかなりあると見ています。MMIは、対象となるロボットによるマイクロサージェリー手術の市場は、主に技術の進歩と適応症状の拡大により、2028年までに年間300万件か</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221733654/ja/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI Raises $110 Million in Series C Financing</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--MMI today announced that it has raised $110 million in Series C financing.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221774903/en/MMI-Raises-110-Million-in-Series-C-Financing/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI在 C 轮融资中筹资1.1亿美元</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>杰克逊维尔，佛罗里达州--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美国商业资讯)-- MMI（Medical Microinstruments, Inc.），一家专注于通过机器人技术增加治疗方案并改善复杂病症患者的临床结果的公司，今日宣布成功完成1.1亿美元的C轮融资。该轮融资由富达管理研究公司（Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company）领头，创下了微创手术创新领域迄今为止最大的单次投资记录。 这笔资金将用于推动Symani®手术系统在快速增长的市场中的商业化进程，并继续投资于临床证据的生成和适应证的扩展研究。此外，投资还将促进MMI先进技术能力的加速发展，并帮助公司在全球范围内扩展其运营能力。 MMI及其所有现有投资者均参与了此次C轮融资，共同看好公司的快速增长潜力。随着技术进步和适应症范围扩大，公司预计，符合条件的机器人微创手术数量将从每年300万例增至2028年的2200万例。 “在医疗机器人投资增长放缓的大环境下，这次融资加深了我们对开创性、更少侵入性开放式手术解决方案的信心，这是一个巨大市场，能从我们最精细的可动腕微型手术器械中获益，”</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221154481/zh-CN/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMI raccoglie 110 milioni di dollari in un ciclo di finanziamento di serie ‘C’</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>JACKSONVILLE, Florida--(BUSINESS WIRE)--MMI (Medical Microinstruments, Inc.), una società operante nel settore della robotica, impegnata ad ampliare la scelta di trattamenti e migliorare gli esiti clinici per pazienti con condizioni complesse, oggi ha annunciato di avere raccolto 110 milioni di dollari in un ciclo di finanziamento di serie ‘C’ guidato da Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company; si tratta del più grande investimento finora mai effettuato per promuovere l’innovazione nella mic</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221105207/it/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monroe Capital Supports Equity Group Investments’ Lanter Delivery Systems</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Monroe Capital LLC (“Monroe”) announced it acted as administrative agent and joint lead arranger on the funding of a senior credit facility to provide continued growth financing of Lanter Delivery Systems, an existing portfolio company of Equity Group Investments, the private investment firm founded by Sam Zell. Founded more than 40 years ago and based in St. Louis, Missouri, Lanter Delivery Systems is the country’s recognized leader in overnight delivery of critical p</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221140526/en/Monroe-Capital-Supports-Equity-Group-Investments%E2%80%99-Lanter-Delivery-Systems/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napier AI lands £45m backing from Crestline Investors to fuel continued growth in AI-powered financial crime compliance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 08:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LONDON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Napier AI lands £45m backing from Crestline Investors to fuel continued growth in AI-powered financial crime compliance</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221739353/en/Napier-AI-lands-%C2%A345m-backing-from-Crestline-Investors-to-fuel-continued-growth-in-AI-powered-financial-crime-compliance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Payments Announces Pricing of Offering of $1.75 Billion of Convertible Senior Notes due 2031</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 04:39:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ATLANTA--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Global Payments Inc. (NYSE: GPN) today announced the pricing of its previously announced offering of $1.75 billion in aggregate principal amount of its 1.50% convertible senior notes due 2031 (the “Convertible Notes”). The Company granted the initial purchasers of the Convertible Notes an option to purchase, for settlement within a 13-day period beginning on, and including, the first date on which the Convertible Notes are issued, up to an additional $250 million aggre</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220511053/en/Global-Payments-Announces-Pricing-of-Offering-of-1.75-Billion-of-Convertible-Senior-Notes-due-2031/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Lease Corporation Announces Pricing of Offering of C$400 Million of Senior Unsecured Medium-Term Notes</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 04:01:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Air Lease Corporation (NYSE: AL) (the “Company”) announced the pricing on February 20, 2024 of its offering of C$400 million aggregate principal amount of additional 5.40% senior unsecured medium-term notes due June 1, 2028 (the “Notes”). The sale of the Notes is expected to close on February 28, 2024, subject to satisfaction of customary closing conditions. The Notes will mature on June 1, 2028 and will bear interest at a rate of 5.40% per annum, payable semi-annu</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220370152/en/Air-Lease-Corporation-Announces-Pricing-of-Offering-of-C400-Million-of-Senior-Unsecured-Medium-Term-Notes/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-Based Ibex Investors Closes $106 Million Venture Fund to Invest in Early-Stage Israeli Startups</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 04:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DENVER &amp; TEL AVIV, Israel--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Ibex Investors LLC (“Ibex”), a US-based multi-stage and multi-strategy investment firm, announced today the close of its fourth Israel focused fund, Ibex Israel VC II LP (“the Fund”), with $106 million in capital commitments to invest in early-stage Israeli startups. The Fund follows Ibex’s $100 million Israel early-stage fund raised in 2020 and the roster of limited partners includes founders and current and former executives across a wide range of s</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220016374/en/US-Based-Ibex-Investors-Closes-106-Million-Venture-Fund-to-Invest-in-Early-Stage-Israeli-Startups/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Ymqj4g6qAlg7edDzhXcztJcgiwDl5F89IquLVWUqfRVgLxDkSKfgoruKb9yWl5as-PbWreMWuYBefATrZ0EPTUKvKXA1G4lfyVQLpVttJwGBSvR87oUDgbHejiywQBpbg==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sopra Steria Group : Un exercice 2023 qui confirme une nette augmentation de la performance opérationnelle de Sopra Steria</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 06:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News:  Le Conseil d’administration de Sopra Steria Group SA (Paris:SOP), réuni le 21 février 2024 sous la présidence de Pierre Pasquier, a arrêté les comptes pour l’exercice clos le 31 décembre 20232. Sopra Steria : résultats annuels consolidés 2023 2023   2022     Montant Taux de marge Var.   Montant   Taux de marge Principaux éléments du compte de résultat                 Chiffre d'affaires M€ 5 805,3     13,8%     5 101,2       Croissance organique % +6,6%</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221835425/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sopra Steria Group: Achieves Further Substantial Increase in Operating Performance in Financial Year 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 06:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: At its meeting on 21 February 2024 chaired by Pierre Pasquier, Sopra Steria Group (Paris:SOP) SA’s Board of Directors approved the financial statements for the financial year ended 31 December 20232. Sopra Steria: 2023 consolidated full-year results 2023   2022     Amount Margin Change   Amount   Margin Key income statement items                 Revenue €m 5,805.3     13.8%     5,101.2       Organic Growth % +6.6%                                        </description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221944210/en/Sopra-Steria-Group-Achieves-Further-Substantial-Increase-in-Operating-Performance-in-Financial-Year-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>联想集团：2023/24财年第三季度业绩</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:27:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>香港--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美国商业资讯)-- 联想集团有限公司 (港交所: 992) (ADR: LNVGY)，连同其附属公司 （“本集团”），今天公布第三季度业绩。集团整体营业额年比年增长3%至157亿美元，盈利能力连续第二个季度实现季比季改善。净利润为3.57亿美元（按照非香港财务报告准则[1]），净利润率季比季上升0.4%至2.3%。集团的多元化增长引擎持续发力，个人电脑以外业务在集团整体营业额中占比 42%，年比年上升1.3个百分点。 在过去的几个季度，得益于集团具韧性的核心业务和有效的持续转型，集团业绩逐季持续改善。方案服务业务集团营业额首次突破 20 亿美元的重要里程碑，运营利润额创历史新高，运营利润率超过 20%，其中运维服务和项目及解决方案服务业务的营业额连续11个季度实现年比年提升。基础设施方案业务集团营业额实现季度增长，其存储、软件和服务业务的营业额达到创纪录的 10 亿美元。智能设备业务集团营业额重回增长轨道，表现优于市场，而个人电脑出货量实现年比年增长，保持了领先的盈利能力。 财务亮点：   23/24财年 第三季度 百万美元 22/23财年</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221612901/zh-CN/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Group: Third Quarter Results 2023/24</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:26:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HONG KONG--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Lenovo Group Limited (HKSE: 992) (ADR: LNVGY), together with its subsidiaries (‘the Group’), today announced third quarter results reporting Group revenue increasing 3% year-on-year to US$15.7 billion, and Group profitability improving quarter-to-quarter for the second time in a row. Net income was US$357 million on a non-Hong Kong Financial Reporting Standards (non-HKFRS)[1] basis, with net income margin up 0.4% quarter-to-quarter to 2.3%. The Group’s diversified gr</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221855723/en/Lenovo-Group-Third-Quarter-Results-202324/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SJW Group Announces 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:06:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN JOSE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--SJW Group reports Q4 and 2023 financial results. Live webcast at 2 p.m. (ET) on February 22, 2024.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221538675/en/SJW-Group-Announces-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pan American Silver Reports Audited Financial Results for 2023 and Announces Intention to Make a Normal Course Issuer Bid</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:18:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>VANCOUVER, British Columbia--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Pan American Silver Corp. (NYSE: PAAS) (TSX: PAAS) ("Pan American" or the "Company") reports fourth quarter ("Q4 2023") financial results and audited financial results for the year ended December 31, 2023 ("FY 2023"). "Pan American enters 2024 in a solid financial position with cash and short-term investments totaling $440.9 million and the full $750.0 million available under our undrawn credit facility," said Michael Steinmann, President and Chief</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220333681/en/Pan-American-Silver-Reports-Audited-Financial-Results-for-2023-and-Announces-Intention-to-Make-a-Normal-Course-Issuer-Bid/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORRECTING and REPLACING Corporación Inmobiliaria Vesta Reports Fourth Quarter 2023 Earnings Results</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:44:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MEXICO CITY--(BUSINESS WIRE)--In the second sentence of the seventh bulleted item within Full Year and Q4 2023 Highlights, the figure for which the 81 thousand sf building located in Toluca was acquired should be changed to US $7.0 million (including closing costs) equivalent to an estimated 8.1% cap rate. (instead of US $25.3 million, equivalent to an estimated 8.5% cap rate). The updated release reads: CORPORACIÓN INMOBILIARIA VESTA REPORTS FOURTH QUARTER 2023 EARNINGS RESULTS Corporación Inm</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221476880/en/CORRECTING-and-REPLACING-Corporaci%C3%B3n-Inmobiliaria-Vesta-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyatt Announces Updated Timing of Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Earnings Release and Investor Conference Call</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:22:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Hyatt Hotels Corporation (“Hyatt” or the “Company”) (NYSE: H) announced today that it will release fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results on Friday, February 23, 2024, before the stock market opens, followed by a conference call at 9:00 a.m. CT. Participants are encouraged to listen to a simultaneous webcast of the conference call, accessible through the Company’s website at investors.hyatt.com. An archive of the webcast will be available on the Company’s</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221263610/en/Hyatt-Announces-Updated-Timing-of-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Earnings-Release-and-Investor-Conference-Call/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orbia Announces Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:11:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MEXICO CITY--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Orbia Advance Corporation, S.A.B. de C.V. (BMV: ORBIA*) (“the Company” or “Orbia”) today released unaudited results for the fourth quarter and full year of 2023. Orbia delivered EBITDA of $226 million for the fourth quarter of 2023 and $1.46 billion for the full year 2023, in line with recent guidance, demonstrating its resilience and ability to manage through a challenging market environment. Market conditions in the construction, infrastructure and capital invest</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221707370/en/Orbia-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORRECTING and REPLACING Mister Car Wash Announces Fourth Quarter and Fiscal Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TUCSON, Ariz.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--In the Fiscal 2024 Outlook table, the "Comparable-store sales growth %" row under the "2024 Initial Outlook" column should read: 0.5% to 2.5% (instead of -0.5% to 2.5%). The updated release reads: MISTER CAR WASH ANNOUNCES FOURTH QUARTER AND FISCAL YEAR 2023 FINANCIAL RESULTS Net revenues increased 7.4% during the quarter Comparable-store sales increased 0.7% during the quarter Unlimited Wash Club memberships increased 10.3% Opened a record 35 new greenfield loca</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221051221/en/CORRECTING-and-REPLACING-Mister-Car-Wash-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Fiscal-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valaris Reports Fourth Quarter 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:56:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HAMILTON, Bermuda--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Valaris Reports Fourth Quarter 2023 Results</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221354956/en/Valaris-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yext to Announce Fourth Quarter and Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results on March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:54:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Yext, Inc. (NYSE: YEXT), the leading digital presence platform for multi-location brands, today announced that its fourth quarter and full fiscal year 2024 results will be released on Wednesday, March 6, 2024, after the close of the market. The company will host a conference call at 5:00 p.m. (ET) / 2:00 p.m. (PT) to discuss its financial results with the investment community. A live webcast of the event will be available on the Yext Investor Relations website at http</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221671028/en/Yext-to-Announce-Fourth-Quarter-and-Fiscal-Year-2024-Financial-Results-on-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patterson Companies Fiscal 2024 Third Quarter Conference Call Scheduled for Wednesday, February 28, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:12:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ST. PAUL, Minn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Patterson Companies (Nasdaq: PDCO) today announced that it will hold its fiscal 2024 third-quarter call on Wednesday, February 28, 2024, at 7:30 a.m. CT (8:30 a.m. ET). The company’s earnings release will be issued that morning before the market opens. To access the live webcast, go to the investor relations section of the company’s website, www.PattersonCompanies.com. The fiscal 2024 third-quarter earnings conference call replay will be available beginning at</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221075519/en/Patterson-Companies-Fiscal-2024-Third-Quarter-Conference-Call-Scheduled-for-Wednesday-February-28-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ziff Davis Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results and Provides 2024 Guidance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:09:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Ziff Davis, Inc. (NASDAQ: ZD) (“Ziff Davis” or “the Company”) today reported unaudited financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. “We have a positive and encouraging outlook on 2024 that reflects a return to healthy growth rates at the company,” said Vivek Shah, Chief Executive Officer of Ziff Davis. “At the same time, we are well-positioned to act with conviction and decisiveness in the M&amp;amp;A market to further grow our business." FOU</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221537366/en/Ziff-Davis-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-and-Provides-2024-Guidance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superior Plus Announces Record Fourth Quarter, Achieves Full-Year Results In-Line with Guidance and Expects Adjusted EBITDA Growth of 5% in 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:51:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Superior Plus Corp. (“Superior” or “the company”) (TSX: SPB) today released its fourth quarter and year end results for the period ended December 31, 2023. Unless otherwise expressed, all financial figures are expressed in Canadian dollars. In announcing these results, Allan MacDonald, President and Chief Executive Officer said, “2023 was a transformational year for Superior. The closing of the Certarus acquisition on May 31, 2023 solidified the company’s position as t</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221741440/en/Superior-Plus-Announces-Record-Fourth-Quarter-Achieves-Full-Year-Results-In-Line-with-Guidance-and-Expects-Adjusted-EBITDA-Growth-of-5-in-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stelco Holdings Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:35:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HAMILTON, Ontario--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Stelco Holdings Inc. (“Stelco Holdings” or the “Company”), (TSX: STLC), a low cost, integrated and independent steelmaker with one of the newest and most technologically advanced integrated steelmaking facilities in North America, today announced financial results of the Company for the three months and year ended December 31, 2023. Stelco Holdings is the 100% owner of Stelco Inc. (“Stelco”), the operating company. Selected Financial Information (in millions</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221801248/en/Stelco-Holdings-Inc.-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nutrien Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:26:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SASKATOON, Saskatchewan--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Nutrien Ltd. (TSX and NYSE: NTR) announced today its fourth quarter 2023 results, with net earnings of $176 million ($0.35 diluted net earnings per share). Fourth quarter 2023 adjusted net earnings per share1 was $0.37 and adjusted EBITDA1 was $1.1 billion. “We saw a continuation of strong fertilizer market fundamentals in North America during the fourth quarter driven by improved affordability, an extended fall application season and low channel invent</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240216205375/en/Nutrien-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sturm, Ruger &amp;amp; Company, Inc. Reports 2023 Diluted Earnings of $2.71 Per Share and Declares Dividend of 23¢ Per Share</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SOUTHPORT, Conn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Sturm, Ruger &amp;amp; Company, Inc. (NYSE-RGR) announced today that for 2023 the Company reported net sales of $543.8 million and diluted earnings of $2.71 per share, compared with net sales of $595.8 million and diluted earnings of $4.96 per share in 2022. For the fourth quarter of 2023, net sales were $130.6 million and diluted earnings were 58¢ per share. For the corresponding period in 2022, net sales were $149.2 million and diluted earnings were $1.06 per sh</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221309557/en/Sturm-Ruger-Company-Inc.-Reports-2023-Diluted-Earnings-of-2.71-Per-Share-and-Declares-Dividend-of-23%C2%A2-Per-Share/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physicians Realty Trust Reports Fourth Quarter and Year Ended 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MILWAUKEE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Physicians Realty Trust (NYSE: DOC) (the “Company,” the “Trust,” “we,” “our” and “us”), a self-managed health care real estate investment trust, today announced results for the fourth quarter ended December 31, 2023. Fourth Quarter Financial Results Total revenue for the fourth quarter ended December 31, 2023, was $135.5 million, an increase of 2.2% from the fourth quarter ended December 31, 2022. As of December 31, 2023, the consolidated portfolio was approximately</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221749668/en/Physicians-Realty-Trust-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Year-Ended-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triple Flag Delivers Strong Q4 and Full Year 2023 Results; Long-Term GEOs Outlook Driven by Growth at Northparkes</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Triple Flag Precious Metals Corp. (with its subsidiaries, “Triple Flag” or the “Company”) (TSX: TFPM, NYSE: TFPM) announced its results for the fourth quarter and full year of 2023 and declared a dividend of US$0.0525 per common share to be paid on March 15, 2024. All amounts are expressed in US dollars unless otherwise indicated. “Our team and our operating partners delivered on an impressive set of milestones this past year. The portfolio achieved the seventh consecu</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221836842/en/Triple-Flag-Delivers-Strong-Q4-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-Long-Term-GEOs-Outlook-Driven-by-Growth-at-Northparkes/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avangrid Fourth Quarter &amp;amp; Full Year 2023 Financial Results Available on Company’s Website</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:45:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ORANGE, Conn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Avangrid, Inc. (NYSE:AGR) posted its fourth quarter &amp;amp; full year 2023 earnings release and presentation in the Investors section of the Company’s website. Interested parties can access using the following link: www.avangrid.com. In conjunction with the earnings release, Avangrid will conduct a webcast conference call with financial analysts on Thursday, February 22, 2024, beginning at 9:00 A.M. ET. Avangrid’s Executive team will present an overview of the fina</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221943849/en/Avangrid-Fourth-Quarter-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-Available-on-Company%E2%80%99s-Website/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannae Holdings, Inc. Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:42:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LAS VEGAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Cannae Holdings, Inc. (NYSE: CNNE) (“Cannae” or the “Company”) has released its fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results by posting them to its website. Please visit the Cannae website at www.cannaeholdings.com to view the fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results, which are included in its Letter to Shareholders. Conference Call As previously announced, Cannae will host a conference call, today, February 21, 2024 at 5:00pm (Eastern Time), to dis</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221633661/en/Cannae-Holdings-Inc.-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mativ Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:40:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ALPHARETTA, Ga.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mativ Holdings, Inc. ("Mativ" or the "Company") (NYSE: MATV) reported earnings results for the three months and year ended December 31, 2023. On July 6, 2022, Schweitzer-Mauduit International, Inc. ("SWM") and Neenah, Inc. ("Neenah") completed a merger of equals ("the Merger"). Financial results for periods prior to the Merger reflect only the continuing operations of legacy SWM results. On November 30, 2023, Mativ closed the sale of its Engineered Papers busin</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221497218/en/Mativ-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marriott Vacations Worldwide Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:34:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ORLANDO, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Marriott Vacations Worldwide Corporation (NYSE: VAC) (“MVW” or the “Company”) reported financial results for the fourth quarter and full year 2023 and provided guidance for full year 2024. “After a challenging year, we ended the year on a very positive note, growing contract sales by 4% in the fourth quarter on a year-over-year basis with VPG in-line with the prior year, after adjusting for the estimated impact of the Maui wildfires,” said John Geller, President</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240219343110/en/Marriott-Vacations-Worldwide-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franklin Street Properties Corp. to Announce Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:31:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>WAKEFIELD, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Franklin Street Properties Corp. (the “Company” or “FSP”) (NYSE American: FSP), a real estate investment trust (REIT), announced today that it expects to release its results for the fourth quarter and full year 2023 after the market closes on Monday, February 26, 2024. The Company will hold a conference call/webcast with the investment community to discuss the results at 11:00 AM ET on Tuesday morning, February 27, 2024. To access the call, please dial 888-440</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221125118/en/Franklin-Street-Properties-Corp.-to-Announce-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American States Water Company Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN DIMAS, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--American States Water Company (NYSE:AWR) today reported basic and fully diluted earnings per share of $0.55 for the quarter ended December 31, 2023, as compared to basic and fully diluted earnings per share of $0.50 for the quarter ended December 31, 2022, an increase of 10% (or $0.05 per share), which includes a favorable variance of $0.03 per share resulting from the impact of accounting estimates recorded in the fourth quarter of 2022 for revenues subject</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220250302/en/American-States-Water-Company-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q2 Holdings, Inc. Announces Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AUSTIN, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Q2 Holdings, Inc. (NYSE:QTWO), a leading provider of digital transformation solutions for financial services, today announced results for its fourth quarter and full year ending December 31, 2023. GAAP Results for the Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Revenue for the fourth quarter of $162.1 million, up 11 percent year-over-year and up 5 percent from the third quarter of 2023. Full-year 2023 revenue of $624.6 million, up 10 percent year-over-year. GAAP gross marg</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221512714/en/Q2-Holdings-Inc.-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordson Corporation Reports First Quarter Fiscal 2024 Results and Narrows Annual Guidance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>WESTLAKE, Ohio--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Nordson Corporation (Nasdaq: NDSN) today reported results for the fiscal first quarter ended January 31, 2024. Sales were $633 million, a 4% increase compared to the prior year’s first quarter sales of $610 million. The increase in first quarter 2024 sales included a favorable acquisition impact of 5%, partially offset by an organic sales decrease of 2%. The organic sales decrease was driven by ongoing pressure in electronics product lines, partially offset by g</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221342336/en/Nordson-Corporation-Reports-First-Quarter-Fiscal-2024-Results-and-Narrows-Annual-Guidance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coeur Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Coeur Mining, Inc. (“Coeur” or the “Company”) (NYSE: CDE) today reported fourth quarter 2023 financial results, including revenue of $262 million and cash flow from operating activities of $65 million. The Company reported GAAP net loss from continuing operations of $26 million, or $0.07 per share. On an adjusted basis1, Coeur reported EBITDA of $64 million, cash flow from operating activities before changes in working capital of $45 million and net loss from continuin</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221800064/en/Coeur-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Wilson Reports Q4 and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:26:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BEVERLY HILLS, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $KW--Kennedy-Wilson Holdings, Inc. (NYSE: KW), a leading global real estate investment company with $25 billion in AUM across its real estate equity and debt investment portfolio, today reported the following results for the fourth quarter and full year of 2023: “The fourth quarter capped off a strong year for our investment management platform which grew by 42% and contributed to 8% growth in Baseline EBITDA for 2023. Our 2023 financial results were impacted</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221608056/en/Kennedy-Wilson-Reports-Q4-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finance of America Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Earnings Release and Conference Call on March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:25:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PLANO, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Finance of America Companies Inc. (“Finance of America” or the “Company”) (NYSE: FOA), a modern retirement solutions platform, today announced that it will release results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023 after market closing on Wednesday, March 6, 2024. Webcast and Earnings Conference Call Management will host a webcast and conference call on the same day at 5:00 pm Eastern Time to discuss the Company’s results for the fourth quarter a</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221560927/en/Finance-of-America-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Earnings-Release-and-Conference-Call-on-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Unlimited Corp. Reports Fourth Quarter Results and Management Changes</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:23:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Dream Unlimited Corp. (TSX: DRM) (“Dream”, “the Company” or “we”) today announced its financial results for the three and twelve months ended December 31, 2023 (“fourth quarter”). “For many years we have been expecting the end of the never ending decline of interest rates. In 2023 we experienced the brunt of the reversal of interest rates to a 20 year high. The Company weathered the severe adjustment well, however, our interest in income properties experienced fair val</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221687375/en/Dream-Unlimited-Corp.-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-Results-and-Management-Changes/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valmont Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:16:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>OMAHA, Neb.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Valmont Industries, Inc. (NYSE: VMI), a global leader that provides vital infrastructure and advances agricultural productivity while driving innovation through technology, today reported financial results for the fourth quarter and fiscal year ended December 30, 2023. President and Chief Executive Officer Avner M. Applbaum commented, “The Valmont team delivered fourth-quarter results in line with our expectations. Despite lower sales volumes, we expanded gross pro</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221852269/en/Valmont-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingevity reports fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NORTH CHARLESTON, S.C.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Ingevity Corporation today reported its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year 2023.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221097281/en/Ingevity-reports-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2023-financial-results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airgain Sets Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Earnings Call for Wednesday, March 6, 2024 at 5:00 p.m. ET</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN DIEGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Airgain, Inc. (NASDAQ: AIRG), a leading provider of wireless connectivity solutions that creates and delivers embedded components, external antennas, and integrated systems across the globe, will hold a conference call on Wednesday, March 6, 2024 at 5:00 p.m. Eastern Time (2:00 p.m. Pacific Time) to discuss its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Airgain management will host the presentation, followed by a question-and-answ</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221161043/en/Airgain-Sets-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Earnings-Call-for-Wednesday-March-6-2024-at-500-p.m.-ET/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayville Engineering Company Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results Conference Call and Webcast Date</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MILWAUKEE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mayville Engineering Company (NYSE: MEC) (the “Company” or “MEC”), a leading value-added provider of design, prototyping and manufacturing solutions serving diverse end-markets, today announced that it will issue fourth quarter and full year 2023 results after the market closes on Tuesday, March 5, 2024. A conference call will be held the following day, Wednesday, March 6, 2024, at 10:00 a.m. ET to review the Company’s financial results, discuss recent events and con</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221201050/en/Mayville-Engineering-Company-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-Conference-Call-and-Webcast-Date/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Country Healthcare Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOCA RATON, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Cross Country Healthcare, Inc. (the “Company”) (Nasdaq: CCRN) today announced financial results for its fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. SELECTED FINANCIAL INFORMATION: Dollars are in thousands, except per share amounts Q4 2023   Variance Q4 2023 vs Q4 2022   Variance Q4 2023 vs Q3 2023   Full Year 2023   Variance 2023 vs 2022 Revenue $ 414,035     (34 ) %   (6 ) % $ 2,019,728     (28 ) % Gross profit margin*   21.9 %   (20 ) bps   (10 ) b</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220115360/en/Cross-Country-Healthcare-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genworth Financial Announces Fourth Quarter 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>RICHMOND, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $GNW #genworth--Genworth Financial announces fourth quarter 2023 results.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220615637/en/Genworth-Financial-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Pacific Land Corporation Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Texas Pacific Land Corporation (NYSE: TPL) (the “Company” or “TPL”) today announced its financial and operating results for the fourth quarter and full year of 2023. Fourth Quarter 2023 Highlights Net income of $113.1 million, or $14.73 per share (diluted) Revenues of $166.7 million Adjusted EBITDA(1) of $150.9 million Free cash flow (1) of $116.3 million Royalty production of 26.3 thousand barrels of oil equivalent per day, the highest quarterly royalty production leve</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221094108/en/Texas-Pacific-Land-Corporation-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge Investment Group Holdings Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SALT LAKE CITY--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bridge Investment Group Holdings Inc. (NYSE: BRDG) (“Bridge” or the “Company”) today reported its financial results for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. Net Income (Loss) was $0.7 million and $(87.4) million for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2023, respectively. On a basic and diluted basis, net loss attributable to Bridge per share of Class A common stock was $(0.20) and $(0.46) for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2023, respectivel</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221216817/en/Bridge-Investment-Group-Holdings-Inc.-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investcorp Credit Management BDC, Inc. Announces Revised Financial Results for the Quarter Ended December 31, 2023, and Quarterly and Supplemental Distribution</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Investcorp Credit Management BDC, Inc. (NASDAQ: ICMB) (“ICMB” or the “Company”) announced its revised financial results today for its fiscal second quarter ended December 31, 2023, to reflect approximately $388,000 (or approximately $0.02 per share) of adjustments relating to the incorrect accrual of certain expenses reported in the Company’s consolidated financial statements contained in a press release issued by the Company February 12, 2024. HIGHLIGHTS On February</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221321957/en/Investcorp-Credit-Management-BDC-Inc.-Announces-Revised-Financial-Results-for-the-Quarter-Ended-December-31-2023-and-Quarterly-and-Supplemental-Distribution/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perdoceo Education Corporation Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SCHAUMBURG, Ill.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--PERDOCEO EDUCATION CORPORATION REPORTS FOURTH QUARTER AND FULL YEAR 2023 RESULTS</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221341398/en/Perdoceo-Education-Corporation-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICON Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DUBLIN--(BUSINESS WIRE)--ICON Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221492475/en/ICON-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cheesecake Factory Reports Results for Fourth Quarter of Fiscal 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CALABASAS HILLS, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--The Cheesecake Factory Incorporated (NASDAQ: CAKE) today reported financial results for the fourth quarter of fiscal 2023, which ended on January 2, 2024. Total revenues were $877.0 million in the fourth quarter of fiscal 2023 compared to $892.8 million in the fourth quarter of fiscal 2022. The fourth quarter of fiscal 2023 included 13 weeks compared to 14 weeks in the fourth quarter of fiscal 2022. Excluding the impact of the additional week in fiscal</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221813908/en/The-Cheesecake-Factory-Reports-Results-for-Fourth-Quarter-of-Fiscal-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LANSING, Mich.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Jackson Financial Inc. (NYSE: JXN) (Jackson®) today announced financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Fourth Quarter Highlights Net income (loss) attributable to Jackson Financial Inc. common shareholders of $(1.6) billion, or $(19.64) per diluted share in the fourth quarter of 2023, compared to $(1.2) billion, or $(13.74) per diluted share in the fourth quarter of 2022 Adjusted operating earnings1 of $204 million, or $2.5</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221973462/en/Jackson-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriplePoint Venture Growth BDC Corp. to Announce 2023 Fourth Quarter and Fiscal Year Financial Results on Wednesday, March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MENLO PARK, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--TriplePoint Venture Growth BDC Corp. (NYSE: TPVG) (the “Company”), the leading financing provider to venture growth stage companies backed by a select group of venture capital firms in technology and other high growth industries, today announced it will release its financial results for its fourth quarter and fiscal year ended December 31, 2023 after market-close on Wednesday, March 6, 2024. James P. Labe, chief executive officer and chairman of the board, S</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221983170/en/TriplePoint-Venture-Growth-BDC-Corp.-to-Announce-2023-Fourth-Quarter-and-Fiscal-Year-Financial-Results-on-Wednesday-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The St. Joe Company Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results and Declares a Quarterly Dividend of $0.12</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:10:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PANAMA CITY BEACH, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #JOE--THE ST. JOE COMPANY REPORTS FOURTH QUARTER AND FULL YEAR 2023 RESULTS AND DECLARES A QUARTERLY DIVIDEND OF $0.12.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221446919/en/The-St.-Joe-Company-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-and-Declares-a-Quarterly-Dividend-of-0.12/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian Releases Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:10:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>IRVINE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Rivian Automotive, Inc. (NASDAQ: RIVN) today announced fourth quarter and year end 2023 financial results. The results reflect continued progress against key value drivers including ramping production, improving cost efficiency, and driving demand through successfully introducing new technologies and enhancing the customer experience. Production and manufacturing progress continued to improve throughout 2023. On a full-year basis, the company produced 57,232 veh</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221757259/en/Rivian-Releases-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inseego reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results and announces CEO transition</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:10:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN DIEGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $insg #earnings--Inseego Corp. (Nasdaq: INSG) (the “Company”), a technology leader in 5G and 4G mobile and fixed wireless solutions for mobile network operators, Fortune 500 enterprises, SMBs, and consumers, today reported its results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. The Company reported fourth quarter revenue of $42.8 million, GAAP operating loss of $11.1 million, GAAP net loss of $14.3 million, GAAP net loss of $1.28 per share, and Adjusted EBITDA of positiv</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221565174/en/Inseego-reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-and-announces-CEO-transition/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadstone Net Lease Announces 2023 Results and its Healthcare Portfolio Simplification Strategy</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:10:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>VICTOR, N.Y.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Broadstone Net Lease Announces 2023 Results and its Healthcare Portfolio Simplification Strategy</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221682114/en/Broadstone-Net-Lease-Announces-2023-Results-and-its-Healthcare-Portfolio-Simplification-Strategy/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spok Reports Fourth Quarter And Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:10:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ALEXANDRIA, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Spok Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ: SPOK), a global leader in healthcare communications, today announced results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. In addition, the Company’s Board of Directors declared a regular quarterly dividend of $0.3125 per share, payable on March 29, 2024, to stockholders of record on March 15, 2024. Recent Highlights: Generated net income of $3.4 million, or $0.17 per diluted share, in the fourth quarter, compared to</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221290700/en/Spok-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-And-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebblebrook Hotel Trust Reports 2023 Results and Provides 2024 Outlook</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:06:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BETHESDA, Md.--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $PEB #REIT--Pebblebrook Hotel Trust Reports 2023 Results and Provides 2024 Outlook</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221980576/en/Pebblebrook-Hotel-Trust-Reports-2023-Results-and-Provides-2024-Outlook/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akili Announces Release Date for Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results, Provides Investor Communications and Board and Corporate Governance Updates</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Akili, Inc. (Nasdaq: AKLI), a leading digital medicine company, today provided several corporate updates, including that it plans to report fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results and a business update via press release on Thursday, February 29, 2024 after the market closes. The company will not be hosting an earnings conference call for this release. Akili is also providing the following updates: Upcoming Conference Participation Akili CEO Matt Franklin wil</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221483326/en/Akili-Announces-Release-Date-for-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-Provides-Investor-Communications-and-Board-and-Corporate-Governance-Updates/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact Sciences Announces Fourth Quarter 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MADISON, Wis.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Exact Sciences Corp. (Nasdaq: EXAS), a leading provider of cancer screening and diagnostic tests, today announced that the company generated revenue of $647 million for the fourth quarter of 2023 and $2.50 billion for the full year of 2023, both ended Dec. 31, 2023. “The Exact Sciences team advanced our mission to help eradicate cancer by testing a record number of patients with Cologuard® and Oncotype DX® in the fourth quarter, leading to strong financial result</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221510454/en/Exact-Sciences-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camping World Holdings, Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter 2023 Results, Returns to Positive New Vehicle Unit Volume Growth, Continues Acquisition Pace, Committed to Delivering Unit Volume, Market Share, and Strong Earnings Growth in 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LINCOLNSHIRE, Ill.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Camping World Holdings, Inc. (NYSE: CWH) (the “Company” or “CWH”), America’s Recreation Dealer, today reported results for the year and fourth quarter ended December 31, 2023. Marcus Lemonis, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Camping World Holdings, Inc. stated, “Beginning in December, our new vehicle same store unit growth turned positive, with January and February to date trending up from mid-single to low-double digits. We achieved our goal of signi</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221815066/en/Camping-World-Holdings-Inc.-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Results-Returns-to-Positive-New-Vehicle-Unit-Volume-Growth-Continues-Acquisition-Pace-Committed-to-Delivering-Unit-Volume-Market-Share-and-Strong-Earnings-Growth-in-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weave Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LEHI, Utah--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Weave (NYSE: WEAV), a leading all-in-one customer experience and payments software platform for small and medium-sized healthcare businesses, today announced its financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. “Weave delivered another strong quarter, capping off a terrific year in which we saw continuous quarterly improvements in revenue growth rate, gross and operating margin, adjusted EBITDA, free cash flow, and customer acquisition,” sa</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221897054/en/Weave-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocky Brands, Inc. to Report Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results on February 28, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NELSONVILLE, Ohio--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Rocky Brands, Inc. (NASDAQ: RCKY) today announced that the company will release its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023, after the market close on Wednesday, February 28, 2024. Management will host a conference call that afternoon (February 28, 2024) at 4:30 p.m. ET to discuss the financial results. Investors and analysts interested in participating in the call are invited to dial (888) 886-7786 (domestic) or (416) 7</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221921830/en/Rocky-Brands-Inc.-to-Report-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-on-February-28-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glaukos Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ALISO VIEJO, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Glaukos Corporation (NYSE: GKOS), an ophthalmic pharmaceutical and medical technology company focused on novel therapies for the treatment of glaucoma, corneal disorders and retinal diseases, today announced financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Key highlights include: Record net sales of $82.4 million in Q4 2023 increased 16% year-over-year on a reported basis and 15% year-over-year on a constant currency basis. Gl</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221978087/en/Glaukos-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olo Announces Fourth-Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Olo Inc. (NYSE:OLO), a leading restaurant technology provider, today announced financial results for the fourth-quarter and full-year ended December 31, 2023. “We finished 2023 on a strong note by surpassing the high-end of both fourth-quarter revenue and non-GAAP operating income guidance, alongside notable enterprise deployments and continued product and platform innovation,” said Noah Glass, Olo’s Founder and CEO. “In 2024, we’re focused on delivering balanced grow</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221978931/en/Olo-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinstripes Reports Fiscal Third Quarter 2024 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NORTHBROOK, Ill.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Pinstripes Holdings, Inc. (“Pinstripes” or “the Company”) (NYSE: PNST), a best-in-class experiential dining and entertainment brand combining bistro, bowling, bocce and private event space, today reported its financial results for the fiscal third quarter ended January 7, 2024. Third Quarter Fiscal 2024 Highlights Total revenue increased 14.1% to $32.2 million, compared to the prior year fiscal third quarter Food and beverage revenues increased 14.2% to $24.9</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221404252/en/Pinstripes-Reports-Fiscal-Third-Quarter-2024-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CareDx to Report Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BRISBANE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--CareDx, Inc. (Nasdaq: CDNA) – The Transplant Company™ focused on the discovery, development, and commercialization of clinically differentiated, high-value healthcare solutions for transplant patients and caregivers – today announced it will report financial results for the fourth quarter and full year 2023 after market close on Wednesday, February 28, 2024. Company management will host a corresponding conference call beginning at 1:30 p.m. Pacific Time / 4:30</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221454518/en/CareDx-to-Report-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joby Aviation Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SANTA CRUZ, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Joby Aviation, Inc. (NYSE:JOBY), a company developing all-electric aircraft for commercial passenger service, today issued its Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Shareholder Letter detailing the company’s operational and financial results for the period ending December 31, 2023. The company will host a live audio webcast of its conference call to discuss the results at 2:00 p.m. PT (5:00 p.m. ET) today. Fourth Quarter 2023 Highlights: Certification and Testin</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221485064/en/Joby-Aviation-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DigitalOcean Announces Fourth Quarter and Fiscal Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--DigitalOcean Holdings, Inc. (NYSE: DOCN), the developer cloud optimized for startups and growing digital businesses, today announced results for its fourth quarter and fiscal year ended December 31, 2023. “I’m excited to have joined DigitalOcean and to advance our position as a preferred platform for developers at startups and growing digital businesses, enabling them to rapidly build, deploy and scale applications that can change the world,” said Paddy Srinivasan, CE</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220330521/en/DigitalOcean-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Fiscal-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunnova Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Sunnova Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220812778/en/Sunnova-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arcus Biosciences Reports Fourth-Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Financial Results and Provides a Pipeline Update</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HAYWARD, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Arcus Biosciences, Inc. (NYSE:RCUS), a clinical-stage, global biopharmaceutical company focused on developing differentiated molecules and combination therapies for people with cancer, today reported financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023, and provided a pipeline update on its clinical-stage investigational molecules – targeting TIGIT, the adenosine axis (CD73 and A2a/A2b receptors), HIF-2a, AXL and PD-1 – across multiple</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221004993/en/Arcus-Biosciences-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-and-Provides-a-Pipeline-Update/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five9 Reports Full Year 2023 Revenue Growth of 17% to a Record $910 Million</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN RAMON, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Five9, Inc. (NASDAQ:FIVN), the Intelligent CX Platform provider, today reported results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Fourth Quarter 2023 Financial Results Revenue for the fourth quarter of 2023 increased 15% to a record $239.1 million, compared to $208.3 million for the fourth quarter of 2022. GAAP gross margin was 52.9% for the fourth quarter of 2023, compared to 53.8% for the fourth quarter of 2022. Adjusted gross margin was</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221037873/en/Five9-Reports-Full-Year-2023-Revenue-Growth-of-17-to-a-Record-910-Million/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Bros Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>GRANTS PASS, Ore.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Dutch Bros Inc. (NYSE: BROS; “Dutch Bros” or the “Company”), one of the fastest-growing brands in the quick service beverage industry in the United States by location count, today reported financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. Christine Barone, Chief Executive Officer and President of Dutch Bros, stated, “We had an exceptional 2023 and entered 2024 with great momentum. We continued to drive steady new shop growth, and Q4 m</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221153674/en/Dutch-Bros-Inc.-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrueBlue Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TACOMA, Wash.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--TrueBlue (NYSE:TBI) today announced its fourth quarter and full-year results for 2023. Fourth Quarter 2023 Financial Highlights Revenue decreased 12 percent to $492 million compared to prior year period Fiscal fourth quarter consisted of 14 weeks versus 13 weeks in the fiscal fourth quarter of 2022 Revenue decreased 15 percent on a comparable 13-week basis Net loss of $3 million Adjusted EBITDA1 of $5 million and adjusted net income of $3 million Zero debt, cash</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221160802/en/TrueBlue-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BuzzFeed, Inc. Announces Sale of Complex to NTWRK in All-Cash Deal</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--BuzzFeed, Inc. Announces Sale of Complex to NTWRK in All-Cash Deal</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221201645/en/BuzzFeed-Inc.-Announces-Sale-of-Complex-to-NTWRK-in-All-Cash-Deal/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tandem Diabetes Care Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results and 2024 Financial Guidance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN DIEGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #TandemDiabetes--Tandem Diabetes Care, Inc. (NASDAQ: TNDM), a global insulin delivery and diabetes technology company, today reported its financial results for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2023 and provided its financial guidance for the year ending December 31, 2024. Fourth Quarter and Recent Highlights Worldwide installed base increased 7 percent to approximately 452,000 in-warranty customers compared to the fourth quarter 2022. Launched Tandem Mobi, the world’s smallest</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221234957/en/Tandem-Diabetes-Care-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-and-2024-Financial-Guidance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogers Corporation Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHANDLER, Ariz.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Q4/Year-End 2023 Earnings Release</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221317646/en/Rogers-Corporation-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERISAFE Announces 2023 Fourth Quarter and Year-end Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DERIDDER, La.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--AMERISAFE Reports $62.1 Million of Net Income, Return on Equity of 20.4% and Net Combined Ratio of 85.9% in 2023.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221323970/en/AMERISAFE-Announces-2023-Fourth-Quarter-and-Year-end-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outset Medical Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN JOSE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Outset Medical, Inc. (Nasdaq: OM) (“Outset” or the “Company”), a medical technology company pioneering a first-of-its-kind technology to reduce the cost and complexity of dialysis, today reported financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Fourth Quarter, Year-End Results, and Recent Highlights Recorded net revenue of $30.5 million in the fourth quarter, bringing 2023 revenue to $130.4 million, a 13% increase compared to $11</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221381198/en/Outset-Medical-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bally’s Corporation Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PROVIDENCE, R.I.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bally’s Corporation (NYSE: BALY) today reported financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Fourth Quarter 2023 Results and Operating Highlights Consolidated revenues of $611.7 million, up 6.1% year-over-year and up 8.6% for the full year Casinos &amp;amp; Resorts revenues of $342.3 million, up 7.2% year-over-year International Interactive revenues of $236.0 million, up 2.1% year-over-year North America Interactive revenues of $</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221389554/en/Bally%E2%80%99s-Corporation-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mirum Pharmaceuticals to Announce Fourth Quarter and Year-End 2023 Financial Results and Host Conference Call on February 28, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>FOSTER CITY, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mirum Pharmaceuticals to Announce Fourth Quarter and Year-End 2023 Financial Results and Host Conference Call on February 28, 2024</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221396043/en/Mirum-Pharmaceuticals-to-Announce-Fourth-Quarter-and-Year-End-2023-Financial-Results-and-Host-Conference-Call-on-February-28-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack in the Box Inc. Reports First Quarter 2024 Earnings</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:04:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN DIEGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Jack in the Box Inc. (NASDAQ: JACK) announced financial results for the Jack in the Box and Del Taco brands in the first quarter, ended January 21, 2024. “The first quarter included notable progress on our long-term strategy and objectives we laid out at our recent Investor Day,” said Darin Harris, Jack in the Box Chief Executive Officer. “We were also pleased with the sales rebound for Del Taco, the outperformance of Jack in the Box restaurant level margin, and the</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221077971/en/Jack-in-the-Box-Inc.-Reports-First-Quarter-2024-Earnings/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consensus Cloud Solutions, Inc. Provides Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results (Preliminary and Unaudited); Releases Q1 and Full Year 2024 Guidance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:01:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Consensus Cloud Solutions, Inc. (NASDAQ: CCSI) today reported preliminary financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. “I am pleased with the free cash flow generation in Q4 and full fiscal year 2023. While there have been challenges in growing the revenue, the focus on cost containment, cash generation and debt paydown are bearing fruit. As we look to 2024, we are eliminating inefficient marketing spend and being judicious with our ca</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221316556/en/Consensus-Cloud-Solutions-Inc.-Provides-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-Preliminary-and-Unaudited-Releases-Q1-and-Full-Year-2024-Guidance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McGrath Announces Results for Fourth Quarter 2023 and Announces 33rd Annual Dividend Increase</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:01:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LIVERMORE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--McGrath RentCorp (“McGrath” or the “Company”) (Nasdaq: MGRC), a leading business-to-business rental company in North America, today announced total revenues from continuing operations for the quarter ended December 31, 2023 of $221.6 million, an increase of 21% compared to the fourth quarter of 2022. The Company reported net income from continuing operations of $32.0 million, or $1.30 per diluted share, for the fourth quarter of 2023, compared to net income f</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220559341/en/McGrath-Announces-Results-for-Fourth-Quarter-2023-and-Announces-33rd-Annual-Dividend-Increase/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Recovery Reports Record Full Year and Fourth Quarter Revenue for 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN LEANDRO, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Energy Recovery, Inc. (Nasdaq:ERII) (“Energy Recovery” or the “Company”) today announced its financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. Fiscal Year 2023 Highlights Record annual revenue of $128.3 million, which includes a 79% growth in wastewater and represents nine consecutive years of revenue growth. Record quarterly revenue of $57.2 million, representing a 35% year-on-year growth with strong performance in Energy Recovery’</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221115867/en/Energy-Recovery-Reports-Record-Full-Year-and-Fourth-Quarter-Revenue-for-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGE Energy Reports Fourth-Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Earnings</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:47:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MADISON, Wis.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--MGE Energy Reports Fourth-Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Earnings</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221666232/en/MGE-Energy-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Earnings/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Altria Presents as Part of the Consumer Analyst Group of New York Conference; Reaffirms 2024 Full-Year Earnings Guidance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>RICHMOND, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--ALTRIA PRESENTS AS PART OF THE CONSUMER ANALYST GROUP OF NEW YORK CONFERENCE; REAFFIRMS 2024 FULL-YEAR EARNINGS GUIDANCE</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220907511/en/Altria-Presents-as-Part-of-the-Consumer-Analyst-Group-of-New-York-Conference-Reaffirms-2024-Full-Year-Earnings-Guidance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axway Software (AXW.PA): Renewed Robust Performance in 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:45:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Axway Software's (Paris:AXW) Board of Directors today conducted an in-depth review of the consolidated and annual financial statements1 for the year ended December 31, 2023. As a consequence, Axway’s management team announces: Axway Software: 2023 Full-year results                           Key income statement items*   2023   2022   (€m) (% Rev)   (€m) (% Rev) Revenue   319.0     314.0   Organic growth   + 5.8%         Growth at constant exchange rates</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221248504/en/Axway-Software-AXW.PA-Renewed-Robust-Performance-in-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clasquin : T4 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:45:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LYON, France--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Clasquin (Paris:ALCLA):   FY   T4 T3 T2 T1   2023 2022 Variation à périmètre et changes courants Périmètre et changes Constants ***     T4 2023/ T4 2022 T3 2023/ T3 2022 T2 2023/ T2 2022 T1 2023/ T1 2022 CONSOLIDE (non audité)                   Nombre d’opérations** 334 889 315 742 +6,1% +4,6%   +10,5% +2,5% +6,8% +4,6% Chiffre d'affaires (M€) * 562,1 877,1 -35,9% -42,9%   -18,1% -44,0% -36,7% -40,5% Marge commerciale brute (M€) 143,1 140,0 +2,2%</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221915009/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clasquin: Q4 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:45:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LYON, France--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Clasquin (Paris:ALCLA)   FY   Q4 Q3 Q2 Q1   2023 2022 Change at current scope &amp;amp; exch. rates Like For like ***    Q4 2023/ Q4 2022 Q3 2023/ Q3 2022 Q2 2023/ Q2 2022 Q1 2023/ Q1 2022 CONSOLIDATED (unaudited)                   Number of shipments** 334,889 315,742 +6.1% +4.6%   +10.5% +2.5% +6.8% +4.6% Sales (€m) * 562.1 877.1 -35.9% -42.9%   -18.1% -44.0% -36.7% -40.5% Gross profit (€m) 143.1 140.0 +2.2% -8.5%   +22.4% +0.6% +1.4% -14.1% * Sales</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221915944/en/Clasquin-Q4-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axway Software (AXW.PA) : Nouvelle performance robuste en 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:45:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Le Conseil d’administration d’Axway Software (Paris:AXW) a procédé ce jour à un examen approfondi des états financiers consolidés et des comptes annuels1 relatifs à l’exercice clos le 31 décembre 2023. En conséquence, l’équipe de direction d’Axway annonce : Axway Software : Résultats annuels 2023   Principaux éléments du compte de résultat* 2023   2022 (M€) (% CA)   (M€) (% CA) Chiffre d'Affaires 319,0 314,0 Croissance organique + 5,8% Croissance à chang</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221815820/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winmark Corporation Announces Year End Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:39:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MINNEAPOLIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Winmark Corporation (Nasdaq: WINA) announced today net income for the year ended December 30, 2023 of $40,178,100 or $11.04 per share diluted compared to net income of $39,424,900 or $10.97 per share diluted in 2022. The fourth quarter 2023 net income was $9,716,800 or $2.64 per share diluted, compared to net income of $10,176,600 or $2.86 per share diluted, for the same period last year. Revenues for the year ended December 30, 2023 were $83,243,500, up from $81,4</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221814233/en/Winmark-Corporation-Announces-Year-End-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REV Group to Release First Quarter 2024 Earnings on Wednesday, March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BROOKFIELD, Wis.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--REV Group, Inc. (NYSE: REVG), today announced that it is planning to release its first quarter fiscal 2024 results before market open on Wednesday, March 6, 2024. The results will be discussed during a live webcast later that morning on March 6, 2024, beginning at 10:00 a.m. ET. To access the webcast, investors should go to www.revgroup.com at least 15 minutes prior to the event. Slides for the webcast will be available on the website before the start of the c</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221265910/en/REV-Group-to-Release-First-Quarter-2024-Earnings-on-Wednesday-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChromaDex to Report Fourth Quarter 2023 Financial Results on Wednesday, March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:32:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $CDXC #ChromaDex--ChromaDex Corp. (NASDAQ:CDXC) (“the Company”), a global bioscience company dedicated to healthy aging, announced that it will hold a conference call on Wednesday, March 6, 2024 at 4:30 p.m. ET to discuss its financial results for the fourth quarter, which ended December 31, 2023. The financial results will be reported in a press release after the close of regular stock market trading hours on the same day as the conference call. Investor Conference Call: ChromaDex</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221132898/en/ChromaDex-to-Report-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Financial-Results-on-Wednesday-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrightSpire Capital, Inc. Announces Fourth Quarter &amp;amp; Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--BrightSpire Capital, Inc. (NYSE: BRSP) (“BrightSpire Capital” or the “Company”) today announced its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023 and certain updates. The Company reported fourth quarter 2023 GAAP net loss attributable to common stockholders of ($16.3) million, or ($0.13) per share, Distributable Earnings of $25.4 million, or $0.20 per share, and Adjusted Distributable Earnings of $35.9 million, or $0.28 per share. For</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221379197/en/BrightSpire-Capital-Inc.-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campbell to Report Second Quarter Fiscal 2024 Results on March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CAMDEN, N.J.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Campbell Soup Company (NYSE: CPB) today announced that it will report its second-quarter fiscal 2024 financial results on March 6, 2024. Mark Clouse, President and Chief Executive Officer, and Carrie Anderson, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer will host an investor conference call and webcast at 8:00 a.m. ET to review these results. The company’s second-quarter earnings press release will be distributed prior to the call. All interested parties</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220870210/en/Campbell-to-Report-Second-Quarter-Fiscal-2024-Results-on-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarepta Therapeutics to Announce Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CAMBRIDGE, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Sarepta Therapeutics, Inc. (NASDAQ:SRPT), the leader in precision genetic medicine for rare diseases, will report fourth quarter and full-year 2023 financial results after the Nasdaq Global Market closes on Wednesday, Feb. 28, 2024. Subsequently, at 4:30 p.m. E.T., the Company will host a conference call to discuss its fourth quarter and full-year 2023 financial results and to provide a corporate update. The event will be webcast live under the investor relati</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221930450/en/Sarepta-Therapeutics-to-Announce-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revance to Release Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results on Wednesday February 28, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:01:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NASHVILLE, Tenn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Revance to Release Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results on Wednesday February 28, 2024</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221311035/en/Revance-to-Release-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-on-Wednesday-February-28-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Properties Trust, Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BIRMINGHAM, Ala.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Medical Properties Trust, Inc. (the “Company” or “MPT”) (NYSE: MPW) today announced financial and operating results for the fourth quarter and full-year ended December 31, 2023, as well as certain events occurring subsequent to quarter end. Net loss of ($1.11) and Normalized Funds from Operations (“NFFO”) of $0.36 for the 2023 fourth quarter and net loss of ($0.93) and NFFO of $1.59 for the full-year 2023, all on a per share basis. Included in NFFO is approxim</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220394795/en/Medical-Properties-Trust-Inc.-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alight Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:40:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LINCOLNSHIRE, Ill.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Alight, Inc. (NYSE: ALIT), a leading cloud-based provider of integrated digital human capital and business solutions, today reported results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. “Our three-year transformation has generated significant momentum and enabled Alight to deliver strong 2023 results,” said Chief Executive Officer Stephan Scholl. “Our 2023 highlights include strong demand for our solutions with BPaaS revenue growth of 34%, g</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221905346/en/Alight-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoPark Announces 2P Reserve Replacement of 110%</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOGOTA, Colombia--(BUSINESS WIRE)--GeoPark Limited (“GeoPark” or the “Company”) (NYSE: GPRK), a leading independent Latin American oil and gas explorer, operator and consolidator, today announced its independent oil and gas reserves assessment, certified by DeGolyer and MacNaughton Corp. (D&amp;amp;M) under PRMS methodology, as of December 31, 2023. All reserves included in this release refer to GeoPark working interest before royalties paid in kind, except when specified. All figures are expressed</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240219121435/en/GeoPark-Announces-2P-Reserve-Replacement-of-110/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Group to Report Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Super Group (SGHC) Limited (NYSE: SGHC) (“SGHC” or “Super Group”), the parent company of Betway, a leading online sports betting and gaming business, and Spin, the multi-brand online casino, will report financial results for the fourth quarter and full year end 2023 on Wednesday, March 6, 2024 before the U.S. stock market opens. Management will host a conference call and webcast on the same day at 8:30 a.m. ET to discuss the results. A live audio webcast along with a</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240219368124/en/Super-Group-to-Report-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean Harbors Announces Fourth-Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NORWELL, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Clean Harbors, Inc. (“Clean Harbors”) (NYSE: CLH), the leading provider of environmental and industrial services throughout North America, today announced financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. “Our Environmental Services (ES) segment capped a year of record growth with an outstanding fourth quarter,” said Mike Battles, Co-Chief Executive Officer. “Demand for our ES services remained robust, as steady volumes, healthy project</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221662583/en/Clean-Harbors-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> PHINIA Reports Solid Q4 and Full Year 2023 Results, Introduces 2024 Outlook</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AUBURN HILLS, Mich.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--PHINIA Inc. (NYSE: PHIN), a leader in premium fuel systems, electrical systems, and aftermarket products, today reported its fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023 results. Fourth Quarter Highlights: U.S. GAAP net sales of $882 million, an increase of 3.6% compared with Q4 2022. Excluding $24 million of contract manufacturing sales, sales were up slightly compared to Q4 2022. Positive customer pricing, positive FX and growth in light vehicle o</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221690343/en/%C2%A0PHINIA-Reports-Solid-Q4-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-Introduces-2024-Outlook/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gibraltar Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BUFFALO, N.Y.--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $ROCK #ROCK--Gibraltar Industries, Inc. (Nasdaq: ROCK), a leading manufacturer and provider of products and services for the renewable energy, residential, agtech and infrastructure markets, today reported its financial results for the three-and twelve-month period ended December 31, 2023. “Fourth quarter results reflected a strong finish to a very good year for Gibraltar. We delivered 5% revenue growth, 50 basis points of adjusted operating margin expansion and adjusted EPS</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221275453/en/Gibraltar-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pagaya Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:18:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK &amp; TEL AVIV, Israel--(BUSINESS WIRE)--4Q23 Earnings Release</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220228844/en/Pagaya-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthofix Schedules Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Earnings Release and Conference Call for March 5, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LEWISVILLE, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Orthofix Medical Inc. (NASDAQ:OFIX), a leading global spine and orthopedics company, today announced that it will release its fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results on Tuesday, March 5, 2024 after market close. The Company will host a conference call and webcast to review results at 4:30 p.m. ET the same day. Interested parties may access the conference call by dialing (888) 330-2508 in the U.S., and (240) 789-2735 in all other locations, and ref</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221053940/en/Orthofix-Schedules-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Earnings-Release-and-Conference-Call-for-March-5-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caesarstone Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MP MENASHE, Israel--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Caesarstone Ltd. (NASDAQ: CSTE), a leading developer and manufacturer of high-quality engineered surfaces, today reported financial results for its fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Yos Shiran, Caesarstone’s Chief Executive Officer commented, “In 2023, we implemented a new strategic plan and initiated significant restructuring actions which allowed us to achieve our primary financial objective for 2023, to generate positive cash flow from</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221191174/en/Caesarstone-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analog Devices Reports Fiscal First Quarter 2024 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>WILMINGTON, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Analog Devices, Inc. (Nasdaq: ADI), a global semiconductor leader, today announced financial results for its 14-week fiscal first quarter 2024, which ended February 3, 2024. “ADI delivered first quarter revenue and profitability above the midpoint of our outlook, despite the continued difficult macroeconomic environment,” said Vincent Roche, CEO and Chair. “Consistent with our prior view, we expect customer inventory rationalization to largely subside in our</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221340894/en/Analog-Devices-Reports-Fiscal-First-Quarter-2024-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROG Holdings Reports Fourth Quarter 2023 Results; Initiates Quarterly Cash Dividend</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SALT LAKE CITY--(BUSINESS WIRE)--PROG Holdings, Inc. (NYSE:PRG), the fintech holding company for Progressive Leasing, Vive Financial, Four Technologies, and Build, today announced financial results for the fourth quarter ended December 31, 2023, and the initiation of a quarterly cash dividend for shareholders, as well as a $500 million share repurchase authorization. "We were pleased to finish 2023 with financial results that matched or exceeded our outlook, as strong customer behavior and conv</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221369993/en/PROG-Holdings-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Results-Initiates-Quarterly-Cash-Dividend/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KORU Medical Systems to Report Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results on March 13, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MAHWAH, N.J.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--KORU Medical Systems (NASDAQ: KRMD) (“KORU Medical” or the “Company”), a leading medical technology company focused on the development, manufacturing, and commercialization of innovative and easy-to-use subcutaneous infusion solutions that improve quality of life for patients, today announced that the Company will report fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results on Wednesday, March 13, 2024. KORU Medical’s management will host a conference call and webca</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221482114/en/KORU-Medical-Systems-to-Report-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results-on-March-13-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVgo to Report Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results on March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)--EVgo Inc. (Nasdaq: EVGO), (“EVgo” or the “Company”), one of the nation’s largest public fast charging networks for electric vehicles (EVs), today announced that it will release its fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results on Wednesday, March 6, 2024. This release will be followed by a webcast hosted by members of the EVgo management team at 8:00 a.m. PT (11:00 a.m. ET). EVgo Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Webcast When: Wednesday, March 6, 2024 Time: 8</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221495220/en/EVgo-to-Report-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-on-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Natural Foods to Release Fiscal 2024 Second Quarter Results on March 6, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PROVIDENCE, R.I.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--United Natural Foods, Inc. (NYSE: UNFI) will release financial results for its fiscal 2024 second quarter, ended January 27, 2024, the morning of Wednesday, March 6, 2024. Management will host a conference call that morning at 8:30 a.m. ET to discuss results. To access the conference call, please dial (888) 660 - 6768 (U.S. toll-free) and reference conference ID number 1099581. An audio webcast of the conference call, and materials that will be referenced duri</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221501255/en/United-Natural-Foods-to-Release-Fiscal-2024-Second-Quarter-Results-on-March-6-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expro Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Expro Group Holdings N.V. (NYSE: XPRO) (the “Company” or “Expro”) today reported financial and operational results for the three months and year ended December 31, 2023. Fourth Quarter 2023 Financial Highlights   • Revenue was $407 million compared to revenue of $370 million in the third quarter of 2023, a sequential increase of $37 million, or 10%, primarily driven by a rebound of activity in North and Latin America (“NLA”) and the acquisition of PRT Offshore in the b</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221547118/en/Expro-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProPetro Reports Financial Results for the Fourth Quarter and Full Year of 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MIDLAND, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--ProPetro Reports Financial Results for the Fourth Quarter and Full Year of 2023</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221864965/en/ProPetro-Reports-Financial-Results-for-the-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-of-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bausch + Lomb Announces Fourth-Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Results and Provides 2024 Guidance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:58:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>VAUGHAN, Ontario--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bausch + Lomb Corporation (NYSE/TSX: BLCO), a leading global eye health company dedicated to helping people see better to live better, today announced its fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 financial results. “Revenue growth in 2023, and in the fourth quarter in particular, exceeded our expectations and set the tone for 2024,” said Brent Saunders, chairman and CEO, Bausch + Lomb. “Double-digit growth is always impressive, but even more so when you consider how</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221799323/en/Bausch-Lomb-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-and-Provides-2024-Guidance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funko To Host Fourth Quarter 2023 Financial Results Conference Call On Thursday, March 7, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:57:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>EVERETT, Wash.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Funko, Inc. (Nasdaq: FNKO), a leading pop culture lifestyle brand, today announced that it will host a conference call on Thursday, March 7, 2024, at 4:30 p.m. ET to discuss its financial results for the fourth quarter ended December 31, 2023. The conference call will be webcast and can be accessed on the investor relations section of the Funko website at https://investor.funko.com. After the call, a replay of the webcast will be available on the same website. A</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221926476/en/Funko-To-Host-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Financial-Results-Conference-Call-On-Thursday-March-7-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exelon Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results and Initiates 2024 Financial Outlook</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:50:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Exelon Corporation (Nasdaq: EXC) today reported its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year 2023. “Exelon had another strong year in 2023, both financially and operationally,” said President and CEO Calvin Butler. “We delivered in the top half of our guidance range, achieved best-on-record operational performance at multiple utilities, and advocated for a more affordable and equitable energy transformation for our customers. We successfully competed for</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221832808/en/Exelon-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-and-Initiates-2024-Financial-Outlook/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneSpaWorld Announces Fourth Quarter Fiscal 2023 Financial Results on February 28, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:45:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--OneSpaWorld Holdings Limited, (NASDAQ: OSW), the pre-eminent global provider of health and wellness products and services on board cruise ships and in destination resorts around the world, announced today that it will release its Fourth Quarter Fiscal Year 2023 earnings on Wednesday, February 28th before market open. The Company will conduct a conference call the same day at 10:00 am ET to discuss its quarterly results. What: OneSpaWorld Fourth Quarter Fiscal 2023 fin</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221670243/en/OneSpaWorld-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-Fiscal-2023-Financial-Results-on-February-28-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel + Leisure Co. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Results and Provides 2024 Outlook</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ORLANDO, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $TNL--Travel + Leisure Co. (NYSE:TNL) today reported fourth quarter and full-year 2023 financial results for the period ended December 31, 2023.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221285798/en/Travel-Leisure-Co.-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-and-Provides-2024-Outlook/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NiSource Announces Fourth Quarter 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MERRILLVILLE, Ind.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--NiSource Inc. (NYSE: NI) today announced, on a GAAP basis, 2023 net income available to common shareholders of $661.7 million, or $1.48 diluted earnings per share, compared to net income available to common shareholders of $749.0 million, or $1.70 diluted earnings per share, for the same period of 2022. NiSource also reported 2023 non-GAAP net operating earnings available to common shareholders of $716.3 million, or $1.60 diluted earnings per share, compared</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221574324/en/NiSource-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolverine Worldwide Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results In-Line With Guidance and Provides Outlook for 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ROCKFORD, Mich.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Wolverine World Wide, Inc. (NYSE: WWW) today reported financial results for the fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 ended December 30, 2023. “We are effectively executing our transformation plan with great pace – having largely completed the stabilization phase of our turnaround,” said Chris Hufnagel, President and Chief Executive Officer of Wolverine Worldwide. “We finished the year with revenue and earnings in-line with guidance, and inventory and debt levels b</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221637634/en/Wolverine-Worldwide-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-In-Line-With-Guidance-and-Provides-Outlook-for-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Materialise Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LEUVEN, Belgium--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Materialise NV (NASDAQ:MTLS), a leading provider of additive manufacturing and medical software solutions and of sophisticated 3D printing services, today announced its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Highlights – Fourth Quarter 2023 Total revenue increased 4.1% to 65,295 kEUR for the fourth quarter of 2023 from 62,703 kEUR for the corresponding 2022 period. Total deferred revenues from software maintenance and li</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221218418/en/Materialise-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HF Sinclair Corporation Reports 2023 Fourth Quarter and Full Year Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--HF Sinclair Corporation (NYSE:DINO) (“HF Sinclair” or the “Company”) today reported fourth quarter net loss attributable to HF Sinclair stockholders of $(62.2) million, or $(0.34) per diluted share, for the quarter ended December 31, 2023, compared to net income attributable to HF Sinclair stockholders of $587.0 million, or $2.92 per diluted share, for the quarter ended December 31, 2022. Excluding the adjustments shown in the accompanying earnings release table, adjust</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221326055/en/HF-Sinclair-Corporation-Reports-2023-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSBC Continental Europe: 2023 Annual and Second Half Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: On 20 February 2024, HSBC Continental Europe’s Board of Directors reviewed the second half year results and approved the bank’s consolidated financial statements for 2023. HSBC Continental Europe delivered a strong financial performance in 2023 with growth in wholesale banking revenues supported by the interest rate environment and increased client activity, moderate credit losses and continued cost discipline. We completed the sale of our retail banking</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221272190/en/HSBC-Continental-Europe-2023-Annual-and-Second-Half-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSBC CONTINENTAL EUROPE : RESULTATS ANNUELS ET DU SECOND SEMESTRE 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Le Conseil d'Administration de HSBC Continental Europe, réuni le 20 février 2024, a examiné les résultats du second semestre et arrêté les comptes de la banque pour l’année 2023. HSBC Continental Europe a réalisé de solides performances financières en 2023, avec des revenus des activités de banque de financement et de marchés pour les entreprises en croissance, soutenus par l'environnement de taux d'intérêt et une activité client accrue, des pertes de cr</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221533115/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutor Perini Announces Conference Call to Discuss Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Tutor Perini Corporation (NYSE: TPC) (the “Company”), a leading civil, building and specialty construction company, announced today that it will host a conference call at 2:00 PM Pacific Time on Wednesday, February 28, 2024, to discuss the Company's fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. Speakers on the call from Tutor Perini will be Ronald Tutor, Chairman and CEO; Gary Smalley, President; and Ryan Soroka, Senior Vice President and CFO. The Company plans to iss</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221488236/en/Tutor-Perini-Announces-Conference-Call-to-Discuss-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LivaNova Reports Fourth-Quarter and Full-Year 2023 Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LONDON--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #advancedcirculatorysupport--LivaNova PLC today reported results for the quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023 and issued guidance for 2024.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221387429/en/LivaNova-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Therapeutics Corporation Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 11:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SILVER SPRING, Md. &amp; RESEARCH TRIANGLE PARK, N.C.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--United Therapeutics Corporation (Nasdaq: UTHR), a public benefit corporation, today announced its financial results for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2023. Full year 2023 revenues rose to a record $2.33 billion, reflecting 20% growth over 2022. “Congratulations to the dedicated Unitherians who worked tirelessly to help us achieve our third straight quarter and second straight year of record revenue,” said Martine Roth</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221477756/en/United-Therapeutics-Corporation-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Financial-Results/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vertiv Reports Strong Fourth Quarter Results and Provides Full Year 2024 Outlook</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 10:55:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>COLUMBUS, Ohio--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Vertiv Holdings Co (NYSE: VRT), a global provider of critical digital infrastructure and continuity solutions, today reported financial results for its fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023. Vertiv reported fourth quarter 2023 net sales of $1,865 million, an increase of $211 million, or 13%, compared to fourth quarter 2022 and a 12% organic net sales(1) increase, which excludes the impact of foreign currency. The book-to-bill ratio was 1.3x in the</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220948140/en/Vertiv-Reports-Strong-Fourth-Quarter-Results-and-Provides-Full-Year-2024-Outlook/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riassunto: Bynder nominata una “Leader” nella gestione degli asset digitali da un&amp;apos;azienda indipendente di ricerca</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:53:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AMSTERDAM--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bynder, la piattaforma globale di gestione degli asset digitali (DAM) delle aziende, è stata nominata un “Leader” nel rapporto The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, per il primo trimestre 2024 prodotto da Forrester Research, Inc. Bynder ha ricevuto un punteggio massimo nella categoria dei ricavi, con il rapporto che dichiara che “Bynder investe per avere un ruolo trasformativo nell'economia digital-first”. Negli ultimi due anni dal lancio dell'ultimo</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221038812/it/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bynder nommé « Leader » dans la catégorie gestion d’actifs numériques par un cabinet de recherche indépendant</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:49:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AMSTERDAM--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bynder, la plateforme mondiale de gestion d’actifs numériques (DAM) d’entreprise, a été nommée « Leader » dans le rapport The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, Q1 2024 de Forrester Research, Inc. Bynder a obtenu un score maximal dans le segment des revenus, le rapport indiquant que « Bynder investit pour jouer un rôle transformateur dans l'économie numérique ». Au cours des deux dernières années, depuis la publication du dernier rapport, Bynder a dép</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221045271/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bynder wird von einem unabhängigen Forschungsunternehmen als „Leader“ im Bereich Digital Asset Management ausgezeichnet</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:48:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AMSTERDAM--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bynder, die globale, unternehmensweite Digital Asset Management (DAM)-Plattform, wurde im The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, Q1 2024 Bericht von Forrester Research, Inc. als „Leader“ eingestuft. Bynder erhielt die höchste Punktzahl in der Kategorie Umsatz. In dem Bericht heißt es: „Bynder investiert, um eine transformative Rolle in der digitalen Wirtschaft zu spielen.“ In den vergangenen zwei Jahren seit der Veröffentlichung des letzten Berichts h</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221243449/de/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bynder es &amp;quot;Líder&amp;quot; en gestión de activos digitales según una firma de investigación independiente</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:43:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ÁMSTERDAM--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bynder, la plataforma global y empresarial de gestión de los activos digitales, ha sido nombrada "Líder" en el informe The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems del primer trimestre de 2024 de Forrester Research, Inc. Bynder ha recibido la máxima puntuación en la categoría de ingresos y el informe afirma que "Bynder invierte para desempeñar un papel transformador en la economía que prioriza lo digital (digital-first)". En los últimos dos años desde la pre</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221023095/es/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bynder nomeado &amp;quot;Líder&amp;quot; em Gestão de Ativos Digitais por empresa de pesquisa independente</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:43:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AMSTERDÃ--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bynder, a plataforma mundial de gestão de ativos digitais (DAM) empresarial, foi nomeada "Líder" no relatório The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, 1º trimestre de 2024 da Forrester Research, Inc. A Bynder recebeu a pontuação máxima na categoria de receita, com o relatório afirmando que "a Bynder investe para desempenhar um papel transformador na economia que prioriza o fator digital."Nos últimos dois anos desde o lançamento do último relatório, a Byn</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221852435/pt/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bynder獲獨立研究公司評選為數位資產管理「領導者」</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:36:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>阿姆斯特丹--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美國商業資訊)-- 全球企業數位資產管理 (DAM) 平台Bynder獲Forrester Research, Inc.發布的《Forrester Wave™：數位資產管理系統》2024年第一季度報告評選為「領導者」。 Bynder斬獲收益類別的最高分數，該報告並指出：「Bynder透過投資在數位優先經濟中發揮變革性作用」。從上一份報告發表迄今的兩年間，Bynder的年度經常性收入 (ARR) 已超越1.3億美元，並宣布獲得Thomas H. Lee Partners投入的一筆重大資金，完成兩項併購，開發其企業合作夥伴生態系統，推出逾45種開箱即用的整合，並擴大其產品組合，納入人工智慧及其他可重新定義數位資產管理的新變革。 該報告引述了一則客戶評論如下：「Bynder的人工智慧研究及智慧篩選系統簡化了搜尋特定資產的流程。」這些最近的人工智慧創新展現了該公司的的市場領導力，並帶來新業務、客戶選用率、平台使用率的持續成長。在2023年全年中，Bynder平台上儲存的資產數量締造了38%的年增率，從Bynder平台交付到各網站的資產也增加了2</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221533300/zh-HK/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bynder在独立研究公司最新的数字资产管理评价中荣获“领导者”称号</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:36:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>阿姆斯特丹--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美国商业资讯)-- Bynder，一家全球性的企业级数字资产管理（DAM）平台，在Forrester Research, Inc.发布的《2024年第一季度数字资产管理系统Forrester Wave™报告》中被评为“领导者”。 Bynder在收入类别中获得了最高分，报告指出“Bynder投资于在数字优先经济中扮演变革性角色。”自从上一份报告发布的过去两年里，Bynder的年度经常性收入（ARR）已经超过1.3亿美元，宣布了来自Thomas H. Lee Partners的多数股权投资，完成了两项收购，发展了其企业合作伙伴生态系统，推出了超过45个开箱即用的集成，并扩展了其产品套件，新增了AI功能和其它创新技术，这些都在重新定义数字资产管理（DAM）的概念。 报告中一位客户的评价引述指出：“Bynder的AI搜索和智能筛选系统简化了寻找所需资产的过程。”这些最新的AI创新凸显了公司的市场领导地位，并促进了新业务增长、客户采用率和平台使用率的持续提升。在2023年，Bynder平台上存储的资产数量同比增长了38%，通过Bynder平台向网</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221538134/zh-CN/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synovus wins 25 Greenwich Excellence and Best Brand Awards</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:43:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>COLUMBUS, Ga.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Synovus Bank has been recognized by Coalition Greenwich as a Greenwich Excellence and Best Brands Awards winner.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221525099/en/Synovus-wins-25-Greenwich-Excellence-and-Best-Brand-Awards/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domo’s Mark Boothe Receives Marketing Leadership Award from Utah Business Magazine</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SILICON SLOPES, Utah--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Domo (Nasdaq: DOMO) announced today that Mark Boothe, Domo’s newly-appointed Chief Marketing Officer has been named a Utah Business Magazine Sales &amp;amp; Marketers of the Year (SAMY) award winner for Marketing Leadership. The SAMY Awards program honors Utah’s top sales and marketing professionals who have had a measurable impact on their company’s bottom line. Since joining Domo, Boothe has established new and strengthened existing programs to address custo</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221554132/en/Domo%E2%80%99s-Mark-Boothe-Receives-Marketing-Leadership-Award-from-Utah-Business-Magazine/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq’s Times Square Tower Honors Avangrid’s Top JUST 100 Ranking</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:46:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ORANGE, Conn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #CleanEnergy--Nasdaq’s Times Square Tower Honors Avangrid’s Top JUST 100 Ranking</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221305707/en/Nasdaq%E2%80%99s-Times-Square-Tower-Honors-Avangrid%E2%80%99s-Top-JUST-100-Ranking/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samenvatting: Bynder uitgeroepen tot &amp;quot;Leader&amp;quot; in Digital Asset Management door onafhankelijk onderzoeksbureau</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:32:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AMSTERDAM--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bynder, het wereldwijde bedrijfsplatform voor digital asset management (DAM), is uitgeroepen tot "Leader" in The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, in het rapport voor Q1 2024 van Forrester Research, Inc. Bynder kreeg een topscore in de omzetcategorie, waarbij het rapport stelde dat "Bynder investeert om een transformerende rol te spelen in de digital-first economie". In de afgelopen twee jaar sinds de lancering van het laatste rapport heeft Bynder ja</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221254689/nl/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable Robotics Selected as a Collier Trophy Finalist</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #Automation--Reliable Robotics, a leader in autonomous aircraft systems, today announced that it was shortlisted as one of four contenders for the 2023 Robert J. Collier Trophy. The prestigious industry award has been presented annually by the National Aeronautic Association (NAA) for over a century to the most innovative programs, companies and individuals that demonstrate “the greatest achievement in aeronautics or astronautics in America, with respect to improving</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221862994/en/Reliable-Robotics-Selected-as-a-Collier-Trophy-Finalist/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Goforth Selected for U.S. Bank Law Division Spotlight on Talent Program</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:59:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MINNEAPOLIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Dorsey &amp;amp; Whitney LLP associate Laura Goforth has been selected as one of 14 law firm associates to participate in the 2024 U.S. Bank Spotlight on Talent program. The year-long cohort experience focuses on growing early-career lawyers through professional and leadership development. This year’s program will kick off in Minneapolis at U.S. Bank headquarters with networking, leadership, and goal-setting activities with bank attorneys, its general counsel, its chie</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221466939/en/Laura-Goforth-Selected-for-U.S.-Bank-Law-Division-Spotlight-on-Talent-Program/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serent Capital Named a BluWave 2024 Top Private Equity Innovator</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:44:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AUSTIN, Texas &amp; SAN FRANCISCO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Serent Capital, a growth-focused private equity firm that invests in founder-led B2B SaaS and technology companies, announced today it has been recognized by BluWave as a Top Private Equity Innovator*. The award recognizes the top 2% of private equity firms operating in 2023 that differentially embrace proactive due diligence, transformative value creation, modern private equity firm operations, and corporate citizenship practices. Since its incep</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221695806/en/Serent-Capital-Named-a-BluWave-2024-Top-Private-Equity-Innovator/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbes Advisor’s List of Top 10 Personal Injury Lawyers in Dallas Honors Three from the Law Offices of Frank L. Branson</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:24:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--The Law Offices of Frank L. Branson is pleased to announce that Forbes Advisor has named three of the firm’s attorneys to its list of the Best Personal Injury Lawyers in Dallas for 2024. Founder Frank L. Branson is recognized for excellence in personal injury litigation. Mr. Branson represents plaintiffs in matters involving dangerous products, injuries from gas explosions or electric burns, medical negligence, major trucking accidents and industrial catastrophes. “To h</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221106945/en/Forbes-Advisor%E2%80%99s-List-of-Top-10-Personal-Injury-Lawyers-in-Dallas-Honors-Three-from-the-Law-Offices-of-Frank-L.-Branson/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlueConic Named the Only Challenger in Inaugural 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Customer Data Platforms</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:33:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #AI--Market-leading customer data platform (CDP) BlueConic today announced that it has been recognized as the only Challenger in the inaugural Magic Quadrant for Customer Data Platforms. We believe this industry recognition marks a major milestone for CDPs and the maturity of the space on a global scale. BlueConic differentiates from other vendors for its: Privacy-by-design philosophy: Maintaining responsible data practices is essential for garnering consumer trust, but main</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221318000/en/BlueConic-Named-the-Only-Challenger-in-Inaugural-2024-Gartner%C2%AE-Magic-Quadrant%E2%84%A2-for-Customer-Data-Platforms/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Data Named a Leader in Inaugural Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Customer Data Platforms</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:31:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Treasure Data today announced that it has been named a Leader in the inaugural 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Customer Data Platforms. The report evaluated 17 different CDP vendors on 15 criteria and placed Treasure Data in the Leaders quadrant for its Completeness of Vision and Ability to Execute. “As a true CDP pioneer, we’re proud to build on our heritage and reinvent the CDP with AI, real-time engagement, and journey orchestration all in one platfo</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221863857/en/Treasure-Data-Named-a-Leader-in-Inaugural-Gartner%C2%AE-Magic-Quadrant%E2%84%A2-for-Customer-Data-Platforms/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LearnUpon Debuts as a Strong Performer in Market Evaluation for Learning Management Systems and Experience Platforms</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:23:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DUBLIN--(BUSINESS WIRE)--LearnUpon - a leading Learning Platform, is proud to announce its inclusion in The Forrester Wave™: Learning Management Systems and Experience Platforms, Q1 2024. The report evaluated 11 of the providers that matter most in the Learning Management Systems and Experience Platforms market, and serves as a guide for buyers seeking to evaluate vendors. It aims to provide learning professionals with an objective understanding of how each learning platform provider compares.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221659815/en/LearnUpon-Debuts-as-a-Strong-Performer-in-Market-Evaluation-for-Learning-Management-Systems-and-Experience-Platforms/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 Years Strong: Putnam Investments Earns DALBAR’s Total Client Experience Award Again in 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:16:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MARLBOROUGH, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--DALBAR, Inc., the preeminent auditor of customer service within the financial services industry, proudly continues to unveil the distinguished recipients of the 2023 DALBAR Service Award. For the 13th consecutive year, Putnam Investments* now part of Franklin Templeton, has earned the prestigious Total Client Experience Service Award, in recognition of their outstanding customer service and transaction processing support to their mutual fund shareholders. Th</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221036498/en/13-Years-Strong-Putnam-Investments-Earns-DALBAR%E2%80%99s-Total-Client-Experience-Award-Again-in-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bynder named a “Leader” in Digital Asset Management by independent research firm</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:58:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AMSTERDAM--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Bynder, the global, enterprise digital asset management (DAM) platform, has been named a “Leader” in The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, Q1 2024 report by Forrester Research, Inc. Bynder received a top score in the revenue category, with the report stating that “Bynder invests to play a transformative role in the digital-first economy.” In the past two years since the last report was launched, Bynder has surpassed $130m in ARR, announced a majority</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221482546/en/Bynder-named-a-%E2%80%9CLeader%E2%80%9D-in-Digital-Asset-Management-by-independent-research-firm/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange Logic Named a “Strong Performer” by Independent Research Firm</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:54:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>IRVINE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Orange Logic, the digital asset management platform for innovative enterprises, today announced it has been named a Strong Performer in The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, Q1 2024 report by Chuck Gahun. The report evaluates 13 digital asset management system (DAM) providers based on 26 criteria focused on current offering, strategy, and market presence. According to the report, “Orange Logic tears down silos with a polymorphic DAM…" and it als</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221999334/en/Orange-Logic-Named-a-%E2%80%9CStrong-Performer%E2%80%9D-by-Independent-Research-Firm/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stibo Systems named to Constellation ShortList™ for cloud-native MDM solution and generative AI capabilities</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:37:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AARHUS, Denmark--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Global master data management (MDM) solutions provider Stibo Systems has been named to the Constellation ShortList™ for Master Data Management in Q1 2024. The technology vendors and service providers included in this program deliver critical transformation initiative requirements for early adopters and fast-follower organizations. Stibo Systems has been added to this ShortList “on the strength of its progress in delivering a cloud-native offering on Azure and p</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221196714/en/Stibo-Systems-named-to-Constellation-ShortList%E2%84%A2-for-cloud-native-MDM-solution-and-generative-AI-capabilities/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase Earns 20 Greenwich Excellence and Share Leader Awards for US Small Business and Middle Market Banking</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:34:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--JPMorgan Chase announced today it has received top honors in the prestigious 2023 Greenwich Excellence Awards, including two Greenwich Share Leader distinctions for achieving #1 market share for U.S. Small Business and #1 market share for U.S. Middle Market Banking.1 Overall, the firm earned a combined 20 awards for its best-in-class customer experience provided to small and middle market businesses. Coalition Greenwich, the leading provider of data and analytics on t</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221905068/en/JPMorgan-Chase-Earns-20-Greenwich-Excellence-and-Share-Leader-Awards-for-US-Small-Business-and-Middle-Market-Banking/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enterprises Give Providers Higher CX Scores for 2023, Praise Use of AI Technologies, ISG Study Shows</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>STAMFORD, Conn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $III #CustomerExperience--Enterprise buyers gave technology and business services providers higher CX scores for a second straight year, an ISG research report finds.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221117804/en/Enterprises-Give-Providers-Higher-CX-Scores-for-2023-Praise-Use-of-AI-Technologies-ISG-Study-Shows/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel CEO Pat Gelsinger Receives 2024 Distinguished Executive Leadership Award from JEDEC Board</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ARLINGTON, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--The JEDEC® Board of Directors presented its prestigious 2024 Distinguished Executive Leadership Award to Intel CEO, Pat Gelsinger, in a ceremony held at Intel’s offices in Santa Clara, CA earlier this month. This award stands as JEDEC’s highest honor and recognizes the most distinguished senior executives in the electronics industry who promote and support the advancement of JEDEC standards. “Throughout Pat Gelsinger’s distinguished career, he has consistently c</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221972203/en/Intel-CEO-Pat-Gelsinger-Receives-2024-Distinguished-Executive-Leadership-Award-from-JEDEC-Board/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceMac Recognized by Fannie Mae as a 2023 STAR Performer Award Winner</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>FORT MILL, S.C.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--ServiceMac, an innovative mortgage subservicer and a member of the First American family of companies, today announced the company has been honored as a Fannie Mae 2023 Servicer Total Achievement and Rewards™ (STAR™) Performer award recipient in the General Servicing category. Fannie Mae’s STAR Program recognizes high-performing mortgage servicers for competency, capacity and overall performance. “We founded ServiceMac to eliminate all of the obstacles servicer</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221779561/en/ServiceMac-Recognized-by-Fannie-Mae-as-a-2023-STAR-Performer-Award-Winner/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iQor Earns Customer Service Center of the Year Award for Fifth Consecutive Year and Inbound Sales Champion for 2023</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:20:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>FT. LAUDERDALE, Fla.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #BPOInnovation--iQor Earns Customer Service Center of the Year Award for Fifth Consecutive Year and Inbound Sales Champion for Leading Home Warranty Provider</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221386192/en/iQor-Earns-Customer-Service-Center-of-the-Year-Award-for-Fifth-Consecutive-Year-and-Inbound-Sales-Champion-for-2023/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aprimo Named a Leader in Digital Asset Management by Independent Research Firm</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:07:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Aprimo, the leader in digital asset management and marketing resource management solutions, today announced it has been named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Digital Asset Management Systems, Q1 2024 report by Forrester Research, Inc. “Not surprisingly, the Aprimo DAM excels in several categories; however, several features give it an upper edge: the ability to predict if an asset was influenced by AI; visual search; a dynamic UI that is automatically tuned for users;</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221674221/en/Aprimo-Named-a-Leader-in-Digital-Asset-Management-by-Independent-Research-Firm/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trellix Named to Constellation ShortLists for XDR and Endpoint Protection Platforms</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN JOSE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Trellix, the cybersecurity company delivering the future of extended detection and response (XDR), today announced its recognition on the Constellation ShortList™ for Extended Detection and Response (XDR) Platforms and the Constellation ShortList™ for Endpoint Protection Platforms in Q1 2024. The technology vendors included in this program deliver critical transformation initiative requirements for early adopters and fast-follower organizations. “Constellation</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221363104/en/Trellix-Named-to-Constellation-ShortLists-for-XDR-and-Endpoint-Protection-Platforms/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoLinks Recognized as Gold Winner in the 2024 Merit Awards</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CAMARILLO, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--GeoLinks' ClearFiber™ network wins 2024 Telecom &amp; Wireless Merit Award for Connecting the Unconnected.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221778410/en/GeoLinks-Recognized-as-Gold-Winner-in-the-2024-Merit-Awards/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E Ink Achieves Top 5% Position in S&amp;amp;P Global Sustainability Yearbook, Recognized as an Early Adopter by the Taskforce on Nature-Related Financial Disclosures</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:58:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BILLERICA, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--E Ink (8069.TWO), the originator, pioneer, and global commercial leader in ePaper technology, proudly announces its continued recognition in the S&amp;amp;P Global Sustainability Yearbook 2024. This marks the company's second consecutive year of inclusion, reaffirming its commitment to sustainable practices. Additionally, E Ink has been honored as an Early Adopter by the Taskforce on Nature-related Financial Disclosures (TNFD), further solidifying its dedication t</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220250710/en/E-Ink-Achieves-Top-5-Position-in-SP-Global-Sustainability-Yearbook-Recognized-as-an-Early-Adopter-by-the-Taskforce-on-Nature-Related-Financial-Disclosures/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSG Forte Honored as Top Platform for Payment Gateway Stability in TSG 2024 Real Transaction Metrics Awards</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DENVER--(BUSINESS WIRE)--TSG (The Strawhecker Group) recognized CSG Forte, a leader in complete and customizable digital payments, as the payment gateway provider with the “Lowest Minute Outage” in North America. Based on credit card transaction data and merchants’ perspectives of performance at checkout, CSG Forte earned the top prize for payment gateway stability. TSG’s rigorous, always-on Global Experience Monitoring platform benchmarks gateway performance by conducting 24/7/365 pings to loc</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221032594/en/CSG-Forte-Honored-as-Top-Platform-for-Payment-Gateway-Stability-in-TSG-2024-Real-Transaction-Metrics-Awards/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGCO’s Fendt®, Massey Ferguson®, Precision Planting® &amp;amp; GSI® Offer Expansive, Farmer-Focused Exhibit at 2024 Commodity Classic</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DULUTH, Ga.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #ComClassic--AGCO’s exhibit at the 2024 Commodity Classic will feature award-winning products from across its popular brands.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221410990/en/AGCO%E2%80%99s-Fendt%C2%AE-Massey-Ferguson%C2%AE-Precision-Planting%C2%AE-GSI%C2%AE-Offer-Expansive-Farmer-Focused-Exhibit-at-2024-Commodity-Classic/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SugarCRM Recognized as a Leading Vendor in Constellation ShortList for Sales Force Automation</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SAN FRANCISCO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--SugarCRM, provider of the award-winning AI-driven sales automation platform, today announced it was named to the Constellation ShortList™ for Sales Force Automation in Q1 2024. Constellation evaluated more than 70 solutions to compile its ShortList of 14 vendors, based on client inquiries, partner conversations, customer references, vendor selection projects, market share and internal research. In the ShortList, Constellation Research Vice President and Principal</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221664340/en/SugarCRM-Recognized-as-a-Leading-Vendor-in-Constellation-ShortList-for-Sales-Force-Automation/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merlin Awarded Part 135 Organizational Certification for Air Freight Operations in New Zealand</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:02:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Merlin, the leading developer of safe, autonomous flight technology for fixed-wing aircraft, today announced it received a Part 135 Air Operators Certificate to support future operational freight routes in New Zealand. Upon the Merlin Pilot’s completed product certification by the Civil Aviation Authority of New Zealand (CAA), Merlin will be able to conduct critical data collection flights on selected regional freight routes, as well as leverage its dedicated test facil</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221973905/en/Merlin-Awarded-Part-135-Organizational-Certification-for-Air-Freight-Operations-in-New-Zealand/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SentinelOne® Named to CRN’s 2024 Security 100 List for Seventh Straight Year</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $S #AI--SentinelOne (NYSE: S), a global leader in AI-powered security, today announced that for a seventh straight year, it has been named by CRN®, a brand of The Channel Company, to its Security 100 list, which honors security vendors who demonstrate superior commitment to working with channel partners to protect businesses from cyberthreats. “CRN’s Security 100 list recognizes top-tier companies that provide the IT channel with groundbreaking offerings in a num</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221081300/en/SentinelOne%C2%AE-Named-to-CRN%E2%80%99s-2024-Security-100-List-for-Seventh-Straight-Year/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General John W. Raymond Joins Board of Impulse Space; Company Recently Selected for Two SBIR Awards by SpaceWERX</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>REDONDO BEACH, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Impulse Space, a leader of in-space transportation services, has recently welcomed General John W. “Jay” Raymond to its board of directors, bringing decades of experience in government space operations to the Impulse team. The announcement comes amid a period of strong momentum for Impulse in the government sector, having recently been selected in January for two Small Business Innovation Research Program (SBIR) contracts via the 2023 SpaceWERX Tactically</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221143218/en/General-John-W.-Raymond-Joins-Board-of-Impulse-Space-Company-Recently-Selected-for-Two-SBIR-Awards-by-SpaceWERX/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Drainage Systems Named by Newsweek as one of America’s Most Responsible Companies in 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HILLIARD, Ohio--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Advanced Drainage Systems named to Newsweek's List of America's Most Responsible Companies for the second year in a row</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221236485/en/Advanced-Drainage-Systems-Named-by-Newsweek-as-one-of-America%E2%80%99s-Most-Responsible-Companies-in-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WellRight HRA Earns Re-Certification from NCQA for Wellness and Health Promotion Accreditation</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #corporatewellbeing--WellRight, a corporate wellness leader delivering customizable and complete wellness programs, announced that its Health Risk Assessment has once again received the National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) Measure Certification™ for the Wellness and Health Promotion Accreditation program. WellRight’s HRA captures the critical components of an individual’s health and wellbeing utilizing evidence-based, best-in-class validated tools to improve health and wellness</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221444574/en/WellRight-HRA-Earns-Re-Certification-from-NCQA-for-Wellness-and-Health-Promotion-Accreditation/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seclore’s Justin Endres Recognized as 2024 CRN® Channel Chief</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>SANTA CLARA, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #CRN--Seclore's Chief Revenue Officer, Justin Endres, has been recognized as a 2024 CRN® Channel Chief, for driving data-centric security in the channel.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221578697/en/Seclore%E2%80%99s-Justin-Endres-Recognized-as-2024-CRN%C2%AE-Channel-Chief/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winners of the Lexia LETRS Science of Reading Grant Contest Announced</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Lexia, a Cambium Learning Group brand, has selected the 118 winners of its inaugural Lexia LETRS Science of Reading Grant Contest. Winners comprise K-5 educators in 26 states. Each will receive a grant providing them with no-cost access to the award-winning LETRS (Language Essentials for Teachers of Reading and Spelling) professional learning program. To enter the grant contest, applicants created short videos (60 seconds or less) explaining how LETRS would help transfo</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221834946/en/Winners-of-the-Lexia-LETRS-Science-of-Reading-Grant-Contest-Announced/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netmark Achieves HITRUST Essentials, (e1) Certification Demonstrating Foundational Cybersecurity</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CINCINNATI--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #BusinessProcessOutsourcing--Netmark Business Services has earned Certified status for information security by HITRUST.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240218582543/en/Netmark-Achieves-HITRUST-Essentials-e1-Certification-Demonstrating-Foundational-Cybersecurity/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penbrothers Named 2024 Philippines’ Fastest-Growing Company</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MANILA, Philippines--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #HumanResources--Penbrothers ranks first place in this year's edition of the Philippines’ Growth Champions list by Statista and the Philippine Daily Inquirer</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220564133/en/Penbrothers-Named-2024-Philippines%E2%80%99-Fastest-Growing-Company/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BluWave Recognizes OpenGate Capital with 2024 Top PE Innovator Award</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES &amp; NASHVILLE, Tenn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--BluWave, the Business Builders’ Network that connects the private equity industry with best-in-class talent, industry consultants and service providers, today announced OpenGate Capital as a 2024 Top PE Innovator Award winner*. BluWave’s third annual Top Private Equity Innovator Awards recognize the top 2% of private equity firms that differentially embrace proactive due diligence, transformative value creation, modern private equity firm operati</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221027953/en/BluWave-Recognizes-OpenGate-Capital-with-2024-Top-PE-Innovator-Award/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CACI Named a Fortune World’s Most Admired Company for Seventh Consecutive Year</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>RESTON, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--CACI International Inc (NYSE: CACI) announced today that Fortune magazine has recognized it as one of the World’s Most Admired Companies in 2024, commemorating its seventh consecutive year on the list and its 13th appearance since the list’s inception. CACI received notable results in Fortune’s survey criteria for the quality of its expertise and technology, long-term investment strategy, financial soundness, and social responsibility. CACI was chosen from among ap</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221551709/en/CACI-Named-a-Fortune-World%E2%80%99s-Most-Admired-Company-for-Seventh-Consecutive-Year/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evertas Named 2023 Bloccelerate Portfolio MVP</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MIAMI--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #Bloccelerate--Evertas, the world’s first crypto insurance company, has been named Portfolio MVP for 2023 by Bloccelerate VC, a venture fund backing category-defining companies using the power of blockchain. “We are beyond excited to have presented the 2023 Bloccelerate MVP Award for Portfolio Growth to J. Gdanski and Raymond Zenkich from Evertas,” said Kate (Mitselmakher) Laurence, General Partner, Bloccelerate VC. “This is the fifth consecutive year that Bloccelerate’s awards have re</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221116187/en/Evertas-Named-2023-Bloccelerate-Portfolio-MVP/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kantata Ranks as #1 Supplier of Professional Services Automation for Second Consecutive Year in Annual SPI Research Benchmark Survey</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>IRVINE, Calif. &amp; LONDON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Kantata, a leading global supplier of purpose-built technology for professional services, today announced that it is recognized as the leading provider in the Service Performance Insight’s (SPI) Professional Services Automation (PSA) category in the 2024 edition of the Professional Services Maturity™ Benchmark, marking its second consecutive year at the top of the category. Kantata's solutions are embraced by 200 of the 575 firms surveyed in the 2024 SP</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221855650/en/Kantata-Ranks-as-1-Supplier-of-Professional-Services-Automation-for-Second-Consecutive-Year-in-Annual-SPI-Research-Benchmark-Survey/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellos Recognized as a Top 50 TSX Venture Exchange Company</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Satellos Bioscience Inc. (“Satellos” or the “Company”) (TSX: MSCL), a public biotech company developing new small molecule therapeutic approaches to improve the treatment of muscle diseases and disorders, announced today that it has been named as one of the top performers on the TSX Venture Exchange. The 2024 TSX Venture 50 celebrates the strongest performance on the TSX Venture Exchange (the “TSXV” or “the Exchange”) over the last year. Comprised of 10 companies from</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221365454/en/Satellos-Recognized-as-a-Top-50-TSX-Venture-Exchange-Company/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Equity Firms Recognized by BluWave’s 2024 Top PE Innovator Awards Point to Growth-Minded Action</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:06:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NASHVILLE, Tenn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--BluWave, the Business Builders’ Network that connects the private equity industry with best-in-class talent, industry consultants and service providers, today announced the recipients of the third annual Top Private Equity Innovator Awards and the Private Equity Innovator of the Year*. The Top Private Equity Innovator awards recognize the top 2% of private equity firms that differentially embrace proactive due diligence, transformative value creation, modern p</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221054988/en/Private-Equity-Firms-Recognized-by-BluWave%E2%80%99s-2024-Top-PE-Innovator-Awards-Point-to-Growth-Minded-Action/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECS President John Heneghan Named Wash100 Award Winner</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:04:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>FAIRFAX, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #ECS--ECS President John Heneghan Named Wash100 Award Winner</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240222889937/en/ECS-President-John-Heneghan-Named-Wash100-Award-Winner/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amplified Industries, Inc. Recognized by Darcy Partners Among the Top Innovators of 2023 in the O&amp;amp;G Category</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Amplified Industries, Inc. (formerly Acoustic Wells, Inc.), a pioneering provider of industrial intelligence and control solutions, is proud to announce its selection as a Top Innovator by Darcy Partners in the production category for 2023. This recognition underscores Amplified Industries' commitment to excellence and innovation in revolutionizing the landscape for oil &amp;amp; gas production optimization technologies, allowing our customers to get insight into and contro</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221224821/en/Amplified-Industries-Inc.-Recognized-by-Darcy-Partners-Among-the-Top-Innovators-of-2023-in-the-OG-Category/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premier Packaging obtiene la condición de empresa propiedad de mujeres</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:55:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOUISVILLE, Kentucky--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Premier Packaging se enorgullece de anunciar que ha completado un importante requisito previo que permitirá a la empresa solicitar la certificación oficial Women Business Enterprise (WBE). A partir del 1 de marzo de 2024, Jill Gaynor asumirá las funciones de directora ejecutiva y accionista mayoritaria de la empresa de fabricación y distribución. En cuanto Jill Gaynor, actual directora de Marketing, asuma sus nuevas funciones, John Gaynor, actual propietar</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221539900/es/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premier Packaging Becomes Woman-Owned Business Enterprise</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 08:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOUISVILLE, Ky.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #Packaging--Premier Packaging is excited to announce it is seeking its official Women Business Enterprise (WBE) certification.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221179747/en/Premier-Packaging-Becomes-Woman-Owned-Business-Enterprise/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-YuSr57erpAIbLeyuQLuxVtJ97jVXUEoD5vq_ZlWtJI2z51RgqIO9jteeI1Kq_zxBxjUZ7-9_1AgxnhqXMh__QehJxdQLfq8lvnoBbJhjyX2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthpeak Properties Stockholders and Physicians Realty Trust Shareholders Approve Merger</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DENVER &amp; MILWAUKEE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Healthpeak Properties, Inc. (NYSE: PEAK) (“Healthpeak”) and Physicians Realty Trust (NYSE: DOC) (“Physicians Realty Trust”) today announced that Healthpeak stockholders and Physicians Realty Trust shareholders have voted to approve the proposals necessary for the closing of the proposed merger at their respective special meetings held virtually today, February 21, 2024. The transaction is expected to close on or about March 1, 2024, subject to the satisfacti</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221106437/en/Healthpeak-Properties-Stockholders-and-Physicians-Realty-Trust-Shareholders-Approve-Merger/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthpeak Properties Stockholders and Physicians Realty Trust Shareholders Approve Merger</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DENVER &amp; MILWAUKEE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Healthpeak Properties, Inc. (NYSE: PEAK) (“Healthpeak”) and Physicians Realty Trust (NYSE: DOC) (“Physicians Realty Trust”) today announced that Healthpeak stockholders and Physicians Realty Trust shareholders have voted to approve the proposals necessary for the closing of the proposed merger at their respective special meetings held virtually today, February 21, 2024. The transaction is expected to close on or about March 1, 2024, subject to the satisfacti</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221387514/en/Healthpeak-Properties-Stockholders-and-Physicians-Realty-Trust-Shareholders-Approve-Merger/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratus Properties Inc. Responds to Unsolicited, Non-Binding Acquisition Proposal</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>AUSTIN, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Stratus Properties Inc. (NASDAQ: STRS) (“Stratus” or the “Company”) today confirmed that on January 24, 2024 it received an unsolicited, non-binding proposal from NXSTEP Opportunity Partners (“NXSTEP”) to acquire Stratus for $27.18 per share in cash, subject to adjustments. NXSTEP’s proposal was subject to a number of conditions and assumptions, including important assumptions that were incorrect. Stratus’ Board of Directors (“Board”) considered the proposal and</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221907954/en/Stratus-Properties-Inc.-Responds-to-Unsolicited-Non-Binding-Acquisition-Proposal/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise to Acquire Interest in Panola NGL Pipeline From Western Midstream</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:10:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Enterprise Products Partners L.P. (NYSE: EPD) today announced that its affiliate has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire member interests in Panola Pipeline Company, LLC (“Panola”) from an affiliate of Western Midstream Partners, LP (“Western”) in a debt-free transaction for $25 million in cash consideration. Enterprise executed a definitive agreement to acquire Western’s 15 percent equity interest in Panola. Panola owns a 253-mile pipeline that transports m</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221600440/en/Enterprise-to-Acquire-Interest-in-Panola-NGL-Pipeline-From-Western-Midstream/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTWRK Acquires Complex to Build Next Generation Content and Shopping Experience</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK &amp; LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)--NTWRK, the premium live-video shopping platform and curated marketplace serving buyers and sellers, today announced that it has signed an agreement to acquire publisher Complex to create a new destination for “superfan” culture that will define the future of commerce, digital media, and music. The acquisition marks the next generation of Complex’s leadership as a publication reaching young audiences about the trends, products, and style they love. By mar</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221932558/en/NTWRK-Acquires-Complex-to-Build-Next-Generation-Content-and-Shopping-Experience/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Acquires Joint Venture Interests From Western Midstream</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:05:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Enterprise Products Partners L.P. (NYSE: EPD) today announced that certain of its affiliates have acquired interests in Whitethorn Pipeline Company LLC (“Whitethorn”) and Enterprise EF78 LLC (“EF78”) from affiliates of Western Midstream Partners, LP (“Western”) in a series of debt-free transactions for $375 million in total cash consideration. Enterprise completed the acquisition of Western’s 20 percent equity interest in Whitethorn, which owns the 620,000 barrel per d</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221257200/en/Enterprise-Acquires-Joint-Venture-Interests-From-Western-Midstream/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groupe SEB Embarks on a New Culinary Excellence Chapter and Begins the Process of Acquiring Groupe Sofilac and Its Iconic Brands Lacanche and Charvet</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ECULLY, France--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: The Groupe SEB (Paris:SK) aims to build on its expertise in the high-end cooking equipment segment and continue its growth in professional and semi-professional markets. Sofilac is a family-owned French group, majority-held by the members of the Augagneur family. It designs, manufactures and markets cooking equipment for high-end semi-professional (Lacanche brand) and professional (especially with the Charvet brand) customers. Lacanche, a Living</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221167461/en/Groupe-SEB-Embarks-on-a-New-Culinary-Excellence-Chapter-and-Begins-the-Process-of-Acquiring-Groupe-Sofilac-and-Its-Iconic-Brands-Lacanche-and-Charvet/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Groupe SEB ouvre un nouveau chapitre culinaire d&amp;apos;excellence et engage le processus d’acquisition du Groupe Sofilac et de ses marques emblématiques Lacanche et Charvet</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ECULLY, France--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $SK--Regulatory News: Le Groupe SEB (Paris:SK) souhaite renforcer son expertise sur le segment de la cuisson haut de gamme et poursuivre ainsi sa croissance dans les marchés professionnels et semi-professionnels. Sofilac est un groupe familial français détenu en majorité par les membres de la famille Augagneur. Il conçoit, fabrique, et distribue des équipements de cuisson haut de gamme semi-professionnels (marque Lacanche) et professionnels (notamment avec la marque</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221635204/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manifest Acquires Nerve To Democratize Banking For All Creators &amp;amp; Entrepreneurs</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:02:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Manifest Financial, Inc. (“Manifest”), has acquired Nerve Tech, Inc. (“Nerve”), an innovative banking platform serving the unique needs of creators and entrepreneurs. Nerve co-founders, John Waupsh and Ben Morrison drew upon their 20+ year backgrounds as consumer banking and fintech innovators to create a streamlined solution tailored to meet the financial service needs of creators and their platforms. Manifest will build on the foundation laid by Nerve with plans</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221372385/en/Manifest-Acquires-Nerve-To-Democratize-Banking-For-All-Creators-Entrepreneurs/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Point Prepares the Foundation for SBG Holdings Exit</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHARLOTTE, N.C.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Blue Point Capital Partners is pleased to announce the exit of SBG Holdings (“SBG”), a BPCP III portfolio company, in a sale to Charger Investment Partners. SBG Holdings, the parent company of SASE Company and Bartell Global, is a leading provider of consumables and associated equipment for the conversion and ongoing maintenance of concrete flooring and other hardscapes. The platform offers a comprehensive portfolio of world-class products covering the entire c</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221877170/en/Blue-Point-Prepares-the-Foundation-for-SBG-Holdings-Exit/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charger Investment Partners Announces Acquisition of SBG</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LOS ANGELES--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #investments--Charger Investment Partners (“Charger”) announced today it has partnered with management to complete the acquisition of SBG Holdings, Inc. (“SBG”), a leading manufacturer of consumables and highly specialized equipment used in the maintenance, conversion, and placement of polished concrete flooring. Financial terms of the transaction were not disclosed. Headquartered in Rockford, TN, SBG serves its addressable markets through its industry-leading brands of SASE® an</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221638288/en/Charger-Investment-Partners-Announces-Acquisition-of-SBG/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sopra Steria: Clarification of the Group&amp;apos;s Strategy and Plan to Focus on Digital Services and Solutions</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Sopra Steria (Paris:SOP), a major tech player in Europe, announces its intention to sell most of Sopra Banking Software’s operations to Axway Software, representing annual sales of around €340m, for an enterprise value of €330m. As part of this project, Sopra Steria also intends to sell 3.619 million of Axway shares to Sopra GMT, at a price of €26.5 per share for an amount of €95.9m. Sopra Steria is actively pursuing an independent model that creates sus</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221074415/en/Sopra-Steria-Clarification-of-the-Groups-Strategy-and-Plan-to-Focus-on-Digital-Services-and-Solutions/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axway Announces Entering Into Exclusive Discussions to Acquire Most of Sopra Banking Software Activities</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Axway (Paris:AXW) today announces entering into exclusive discussions regarding the potential acquisition of most of Sopra Banking Software (“SBS”) activities, which are currently part of Sopra Steria Group. This acquisition would fit perfectly Axway’s medium-term strategic roadmap, as outlined by the company over the last few years, creating a new enterprise software house with critical scale. Axway is constantly analyzing the different strategic option</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221819993/en/Axway-Announces-Entering-Into-Exclusive-Discussions-to-Acquire-Most-of-Sopra-Banking-Software-Activities/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sopra Steria : Clarification de la stratégie et projet de concentrer les activités du Groupe sur les services et solutions numériques</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Sopra Steria (Paris:SOP), acteur majeur de la Tech en Europe, annonce le projet de cession à Axway Software de la plupart des activités de Sopra Banking Software, représentant un périmètre d’environ 340 M€ de chiffre d’affaires, pour une valeur d’entreprise de 330 M€. Cette décision s’accompagne du projet de cession à Sopra GMT de 3,619 millions de titres Axway actuellement détenus par Sopra Steria à un prix de 26,5€ par action pour un montant de 95,9 M€</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221980184/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axway annonce entrer en discussions exclusives en vue d&amp;apos;acquérir une part significative des activités de Sopra Banking Software</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PARIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Regulatory News: Axway (Paris:AXW) annonce ce jour être entré en discussions exclusives concernant la possible acquisition d’une part significative des activités de Sopra Banking Software (« SBS »), jusqu’alors intégrées au Groupe Sopra Steria. Cette acquisition s'inscrirait parfaitement dans la feuille de route stratégique à moyen terme d'Axway, telle que décrite par la société au cours des dernières années, et donnerait naissance à un nouvel éditeur de taille critique</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221960598/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novaria Group Acquires Anillo Industries</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:38:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>FORT WORTH, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Novaria Group Acquires Anillo Industries</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221556548/en/Novaria-Group-Acquires-Anillo-Industries/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McNally Capital Completes Sale of Advanced Micro Instruments, Inc. to Enpro Inc.</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #PrivateEquity--McNally Capital, a private equity firm, announces it has completed the previously announced sale of Advanced Micro Instruments, Inc. to Enpro Inc.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221926342/en/McNally-Capital-Completes-Sale-of-Advanced-Micro-Instruments-Inc.-to-Enpro-Inc./?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tufin Acquires AKIPS to Bring Customers Enhanced Visibility into Network Operations and Performance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BOSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #AKIPS--Network and cloud security policy automation company Tufin has acquired network monitoring company AKIPS.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221072283/en/Tufin-Acquires-AKIPS-to-Bring-Customers-Enhanced-Visibility-into-Network-Operations-and-Performance/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Water Company Files Application To Acquire 3009 Water Company</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CANYON LAKE, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--The Texas Water Company files application to acquire 3009 Water Company in Comal County, Texas.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220953003/en/Texas-Water-Company-Files-Application-To-Acquire-3009-Water-Company/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esperanza and Andros Capital Partners Announce Acquisition of Ursa Princess from ExxonMobil and Formation of Deepwater Gulf of Mexico Joint Venture</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Esperanza Capital Partners (“Esperanza” or “ECP”) and Andros Capital Partners LLC (“Andros”) today announced the execution of a definitive purchase agreement to acquire Exxon Mobil Corporation’s (“ExxonMobil”) assets in the Ursa and Princess Fields (“Ursa”) and the formation of a strategic joint venture focused on the acquisition and development of upstream and infrastructure assets located in the Deepwater Gulf of Mexico (“Deepwater GOM”). Ursa is located approximatel</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240220907562/en/Esperanza-and-Andros-Capital-Partners-Announce-Acquisition-of-Ursa-Princess-from-ExxonMobil-and-Formation-of-Deepwater-Gulf-of-Mexico-Joint-Venture/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloyes Gear &amp;amp; Products Announces Acquisition of Automotive Tensioners, Inc.</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>FORT SMITH, Ark.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Cloyes Gear &amp;amp; Products, Inc. (“Cloyes”), the global leader and designer of mission-critical timing drive systems and components for the automotive aftermarket, today announced the acquisition of Denton, TX based Automotive Tensioners, Inc. (“ATI”), a leading front-end accessory drive pulley and tensioner supplier to the automotive aftermarket. This acquisition marks Cloyes’ second acquisition in the past four months and further strengthens the platform’s v</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221766286/en/Cloyes-Gear-Products-Announces-Acquisition-of-Automotive-Tensioners-Inc./?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyelit Technologies Acquires Optessa Software</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>LEWISVILLE, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Eyelit Technologies, a leader in Manufacturing Operations Management (MOM), Manufacturing Execution (MES), Quality Management (QMS), and Factory Automation solutions, has acquired Optessa, a pioneer in optimization and AI-powered advanced planning and scheduling software. The acquisition extends Eyelit Technologies’ footprint into the automotive sector, where Optessa solutions are in use at four of the top 10 automotive original equipment manufacturers. Optes</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221913449/en/Eyelit-Technologies-Acquires-Optessa-Software/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Yonder收購製造和供應鏈規劃科技領導者Flexis</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:46:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>亞利桑那州斯科次代爾--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美國商業資訊)-- 首屈一指的供應鏈解決方案供應商Blue Yonder今天宣布收購專門從事生產最佳化和運輸規劃與執行的靈活創新軟體科技供應商flexis AG。flexis在汽車和工業專業委託代工 (OEM) 領域擁有強大的客戶群，它強化了Blue Yonder的能力，協助擁有高度可自行設定的產品和大量供應商的公司規劃和優化其複雜的生產設施和網絡架構。 Blue Yonder執行長Duncan Angove表示：「透過動態計畫和靈活的訂單分配和排序，flexis的功能使企業能夠為他們的客戶提供堪稱典範的服務，進而為現代製造挑戰提供精細的解決方案。Flexis成熟的解決方案深受一些世界領先的汽車和工業OEM品牌的信賴。他們的專業完美地滿足了當今汽車產業不斷變化的需求，其特點是電動汽車生產、數位化採購模式以及強化接單組裝的客製化選項之蓬勃發展。他們的願景和產品將成為Blue Yonder產品組合的重要新成員，透過整個規劃和執行的週期解鎖新的商機並增加附加價值，含進階規劃和調度 - 包括訂單分配、訂單排序和詳細調度模組 - 銷售和</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240206102028/zh-HK/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-Rc4vIAVcHHkbDcwJimU8QtrtlakeQ9hNboBqTAWIjTge3KWq9s9jif-UkBjBsFRyYAbRTSLTc1mgvhPlnaBA55M-oupQnbXnhKsYk8RmHF_kAy2gZikaX3QWV6xOvgFlA==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UXLINK Social Infrastructure Breaks New Records, Attracts 230,000 New OKX Wallet Registrations in 14 Days, 72% Deposit RateBlockchain &amp; CryptocurrencyCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835443/uxlink-social-infrastructure-breaks-new-records-attracts-230000-new-okx-wallet-registrations-in-14-days-72-deposit-rate</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T23:50:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SINGAPORE / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / From February 2nd to February 16th,UXLINK , a Web3 social infrastructure with a unique "Real World Social" and "group" model, launched a two-week joint campaign with OKX Web3 wallet, and it was reported that in the two weeks since the campaign went live, more than 230,000 OKX Web3 wallet addresses have been created and linked to UXLINK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Solar Sales: Remote Solar Launches to Empower Sales Professionals in the Digital EraBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/833943/revolutionizing-solar-sales-remote-solar-launches-to-empower-sales-professionals-in-the-digital-era</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T23:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SALT LAKE CITY, UT / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Remote Solar, a pioneering force in the solar industry, is proud to announce its official launch, marking a significant milestone in the realm of remote sales and marketing for solar professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinka Gold Launches New Japanese Tokenized Gold $XNK Blockchain &amp; CryptocurrencyCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835460/kinka-gold-launches-new-japanese-tokenized-gold-xnk</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T23:40:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TOKYO, JAPAN / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Kinka Gold has issued its first tranche of $XNK tokens onto the market, opening retail adoption with its first listing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital Value Securities Unveils Emerging AI Investment Trends and Future Tech IPO Insights for 2024Banking &amp; Financial ServicesProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/826818/capital-value-securities-unveils-emerging-ai-investment-trends-and-future-tech-ipo-insights-for-2024</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T23:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>ADELAIDE, SOUTH AUSTRALIA / ACCESSWIRE / January 21, 2024 / In an era where technology reshapes every aspect of our lives, Artificial Intelligence (AI) emerges as a pivotal force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount Insights' "Reflecting Me" Survey FindingsTelecommunicationsDiversity, Equity and Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835703/paramount-insights-reflecting-me-survey-findings</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T21:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Paramount</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUETTI Launches SwapSolar on Indiegogo, Elevating Your Outdoor ExperienceConsumer &amp; Retail ProductsProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835702/bluetti-launches-swapsolar-on-indiegogo-elevating-your-outdoor-experience</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T21:40:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / After the huge success of the BLUETTI AC500, which set a crowdfunding record of $12 million on Indiegogo, BLUETTI is back to shake things up by launching its first ecosystem SwapSolar on February 22 at AEDT 1 am. First unveiled at CES 2024, the SwapSolar includes the world's first LFP-powered MultiCooler portable fridge and the AC180T hot-swappable battery power station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cedar Grove Chiropractic Office Introduces Innovative TRT Softwave Therapy to Enhance Patient CareHealthcare &amp; PharmaceuticalCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835598/cedar-grove-chiropractic-office-introduces-innovative-trt-softwave-therapy-to-enhance-patient-care</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T21:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CEDAR GROVE, NJ / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / The Chiropractic Source is proud to offer the TRT/MTS Softwave Therapy, a noninvasive therapeutic device that uses a patented breakthrough method of shock-wave generation. It brings unprecedented advantages to sports and regenerative medicine. It rapidly relieves chronic pain and greatly accelerates recoveries with sustaining results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TG Venture Acquisition Corp. Announces Change of Date of its Special MeetingBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesShareholder Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835686/tg-venture-acquisition-corp-announces-change-of-date-of-its-special-meeting</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T19:20:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / TG Venture Acquisition Corp. (NASDAQ:TGVC) ("TGVC"), a special purpose acquisition company sponsored by Tsangs Group Holdings Limited, announced today that the date and time of its special meeting of stockholders ("Special Meeting") will be moved from its scheduled time of 11:00 a.m. Eastern Time on February 22, 2024 to 11:00 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Shaul Partners with Robert Ben Shushan to Launch Premier Israeli Model and Talent Management Firm, 'Roberto,' in Los Angeles Sports, Leisure &amp; EntertainmentCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835667/adam-shaul-partners-with-robert-ben-shushan-to-launch-premier-israeli-model-and-talent-management-firm-roberto-in-los-angeles</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T18:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>LOS ANGELES, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Roberto, in collaboration with West Hollywood-based entrepreneur Adam Shaul, proudly announces the opening of its Los Angeles branch. This expansion signifies a significant leap for the renowned agency, bringing its unparalleled talent discovery and model management expertise from Israel to the heart of the entertainment industry in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signalxchange.com Launches Worldwide, Bringing Education and Strategies to the Modern Trader Business &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835674/signalxchangecom-launches-worldwide-bringing-education-and-strategies-to-the-modern-trader</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T18:35:00.000Z</date>
      <description>LEHI, UT / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 /Signalxchange.com , a fintech online platform, has begun providing day traders of all levels with training on the stock trading process. Co-founded by Will Vigil and Brett Simberkoff, Signalxchange.com aims to improve the quality of trading resources through its educational hub, which allows individuals to get in-depth answers to questions from seasoned traders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Healthcare.com Announces New EMR Launch For Elderly PakistanisBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835670/human-healthcarecom-announces-new-emr-launch-for-elderly-pakistanis</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T18:20:00.000Z</date>
      <description>KARACHI, PAKISTAN / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 /Human-Healthcare.com , a Pakistan-based health tech and services startup, is announcing their new launch of a cloud-based secure EMR (Electronic Medical Record) exclusively available to their clients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexa Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial ResultsMetals &amp; MiningEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835659/nexa-reports-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2023-financial-results</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T18:10:00.000Z</date>
      <description>LUXEMBOURG / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Nexa Resources S.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Private Property Rights Amid Regulatory Overreach: A Response to The Post and Courier EditorialPublishing &amp; MediaEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835567/defending-private-property-rights-amid-regulatory-overreach-a-response-to-the-post-and-courier-editorial</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T18:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CHARLESTON, SC / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / In a contentious editorial published on February 19, The Post and Courier levied unfounded accusations against a private citizen, alleging violations of state laws regarding the construction of seawalls on barrier island beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tylers Coffees(R) Launches New Affiliate Program and Expansion PlansBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835666/tylers-coffees-launches-new-affiliate-program-and-expansion-plans</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:55:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TUCSON, AZ / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Tylers Coffees®, a company that produces acid-free coffee utilizing a proprietary roasting technique, has announced the launch of its new affiliate program. This initiative is designed to reward coffee enthusiasts, influencers, and healthcare professionals for sharing the health benefits of Tylers Coffees® with their communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trane® Fort Smith Plant Recognized for Significant Safety AchievementConsumer &amp; Retail ProductsEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835663/trane-fort-smith-plant-recognized-for-significant-safety-achievement</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>FORT SMITH, AR / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Trane® - by Trane Technologies (NYSE: TT), a global climate innovator -celebrated a significant safety milestone at its Commercial HVAC manufacturing facility in Fort Smith, Arkansas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCL Industries Announces Strong Fourth Quarter and 2023 Results Consumer &amp; Retail ProductsEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835439/ccl-industries-announces-strong-fourth-quarter-and-2023-results</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TORONTO, ON / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / CCL Industries Inc. (TSX:CCL.A)(TSX:CCL.B) ("the Company"), a world leader in specialty label, security and packaging solutions for global corporations, government institutions, small businesses and consumers, today reported fourth quarter and annual financial results for 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Más de la mitad de las juventudes LGBTQ+ en México consideraron el suicidio el año pasado: The Trevor ProjectEducationDiversity, Equity and Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835422/ms-de-la-mitad-de-las-juventudes-lgbtq-en-mxico-consideraron-el-suicidio-el-ao-pasado-the-trevor-project</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:27:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CIUDAD DE MEXICO, MEXICO / ACCESSWIRE / a 21 de febrero de 2024 / En un esfuerzo encabezado por The Trevor Project, organización líder en intervención en crisis y prevención del suicidio para las juventudes LGBTQ+, en colaboración con organizaciones aliadas e investigadorxs en el ámbito de la salud mental se ha realizado la Encuesta 2024 sobre la Salud Mental de las Juventudes LGBTQ+, amplificando las experiencias de más de 10,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosaic Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 ResultsAgricultureEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835641/mosaic-announces-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2023-results</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TAMPA, FL / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / The Mosaic Company (NYSE:MOS) released its financial results for fourth quarter and full year 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Research Announces a $5.0 Million Contract Expansion with a Global Pharmaceutical CompanyBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835433/think-research-announces-a-50-million-contract-expansion-with-a-global-pharmaceutical-company</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TORONTO, ON / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Think Research Corporation (TSXV:THNK) ("Think" or the "Company"), a company focused on transforming healthcare through digital health software solutions, is pleased to announce that it has expanded its original contract with a long-term global pharmaceutical client with an additional agreement worth approximately $5.0 million, bringing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New England Journal of Medicine Publishes Results of Positive Randomized Phase 2 REVIVE Trial of Rusfertide in Treatment of Polycythemia VeraHealthcare &amp; PharmaceuticalCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835611/new-england-journal-of-medicine-publishes-results-of-positive-randomized-phase-2-revive-trial-of-rusfertide-in-treatment-of-polycythemia-vera</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEWARK, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Protagonist Therapeutics, Inc. (NASDAQ:PTGX) ("Protagonist" or the "Company") today announced publication in the New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM) of the REVIVE Phase 2 study (NCT04057040) results evaluating the efficacy and safety of rusfertide in polycythemia vera (PV), a myeloproliferative neoplasm affecting approximately 160,000 patients in the United States (US).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC Announces New Board of DirectorsComputers, Technology &amp; InternetCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835635/ddc-announces-new-board-of-directors</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>WINDOW ROCK, AZ / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Diné Development Corporation (DDC) is pleased to announce the appointment of three distinguished professionals to its Board of Directors: Mark Freeland, Sam Rosenfeld, and Brad Preber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armada Supply Chain Solutions Announces Expansion With New Facility in Flower Mound, TXTransportationCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835658/armada-supply-chain-solutions-announces-expansion-with-new-facility-in-flower-mound-tx</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>PITTSBURGH, PA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Armada, a leading logistics solutions provider to the food industry, is pleased to announce the official opening of their new warehouse facility located at 101 Enterprise Drive in Flower Mound, Texas. This new Hub will enable Armada's business expansion to better serve clients, the marketplace, and boost efficiency and capacity for the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landscaping Group Goat Gang Announces Another Major GiveawayGoat GangPublishing &amp; MediaCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835656/landscaping-group-goat-gang-announces-another-major-giveaway</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T17:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SAN JOSE, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / The leader in helping individuals and existing landscape companies scale their business, Goat Gang, is announcing another massive giveaway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immediate Attention Required: ACA Recipient Copy Deadline Approaching in Less Than 2 WeeksComputers, Technology &amp; InternetCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835636/immediate-attention-required-aca-recipient-copy-deadline-approaching-in-less-than-2-weeks</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:40:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CORPUS CHRISTI, TX / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / With the deadline for furnishing Affordable Care Act (ACA) recipient copies now less than two weeks away, employers and health coverage providers are urged to take immediate action to ensure compliance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yunhong Green CTI Ltd. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Financial Results Business &amp; Professional ServicesEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835458/yunhong-green-cti-ltd-reports-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2023-financial-results</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>LAKE BARRINGTON, IL / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Yunhong Green CTI Ltd. (Nasdaq:YHGJ) ("Yunhong CTI" or the "Company"), a leading manufacturer of custom film packaging products, novelty balloons, candy and balloon-inspired gift solutions, and continued development of compostable material solutions, today announced its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury Rental Company VILLAWAY Prepares to Launch All New AI-Enhanced Website MarketplaceReal EstateCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835628/luxury-rental-company-villaway-prepares-to-launch-all-new-ai-enhanced-website-marketplace</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:25:00.000Z</date>
      <description>LOS ANGELES, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Luxury vacation rental marketplace VILLAWAY has announced that it recently launched an all-new AI-enhanced website. VILLAWAY has a curated portfolio of hand-picked and professionally managed premium vacation and private villa rentals all over the world and has recently acquired details about multiple new properties to add to its roster. These include over 500 villas in St.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dril-Quip, Inc. Schedules Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Earnings Release and Conference CallOil, Gas &amp; EnergyEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835631/dril-quip-inc-schedules-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2023-earnings-release-and-conference-call</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>HOUSTON, TX / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Dril-Quip, Inc. (NYSE:DRQ), (the "Company" or "Dril-Quip") announced today that it will release its fourth quarter and full year 2023 earnings results on February 26, 2024, after the close of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havertys Reports Operating Results For Fourth Quarter 2023Consumer &amp; Retail ProductsEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835516/havertys-reports-operating-results-for-fourth-quarter-2023</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:11:00.000Z</date>
      <description>ATLANTA, GA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / HAVERTYS (NYSE:HVT) and (NYSE:HVT.A), today reported its operating results for the fourth quarter ended December 31, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gladstone Commercial Corporation Reports Results for the Fourth Quarter and Year Ended December 31, 2023 Real EstateEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835482/gladstone-commercial-corporation-reports-results-for-the-fourth-quarter-and-year-ended-december-31-2023</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:10:00.000Z</date>
      <description>MCLEAN, VA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Gladstone Commercial Corporation (Nasdaq:GOOD) ("Gladstone Commercial" or the "Company") today reported financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange County Bancorp, Inc. Declares Cash Dividend Banking &amp; Financial ServicesDividends</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835513/orange-county-bancorp-inc-declares-cash-dividend</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:10:00.000Z</date>
      <description>MIDDLETOWN, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / On February 15, 2024, the Board of Directors of Orange County Bancorp, Inc., the parent company of Orange Bank &amp; Trust Company and Hudson Valley Investment Advisors, Inc., declared a $0.23 cash dividend per share of its common stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroVision to Announce Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results on February 28, 2024Computers, Technology &amp; InternetConference Call</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835630/microvision-to-announce-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2023-results-on-february-28-2024</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:08:00.000Z</date>
      <description>REDMOND, WA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / MicroVision, Inc. (NASDAQ:MVIS), a leader in MEMS-based solid-state automotive lidar technology and ADAS solutions, today announced that it will report its fourth quarter and full year 2023 results on Wednesday, February 28, 2024 after the market close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Medical Announces Closing of $10 Million Public OfferingHealthcare &amp; PharmaceuticalCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835565/modular-medical-announces-closing-of-10-million-public-offering</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:05:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SAN DIEGO, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Modular Medical, Inc. (NASDAQ:MODD) ("Modular Medical" or the "Company"), a development stage insulin delivery technology company seeking to launch the next generation of easy to use and affordable insulin pump technology, announced today the closing of its previously announced underwritten public offering (the "offering") of 9,090,910 shares of its common stock, led by Manchester</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World-Leading Schizophrenia Expert Dr. Jeffrey A. Lieberman  Unravels the Mysteries of Schizophrenia on The People’s Pharmacy Healthcare &amp; PharmaceuticalCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835560/world-leading-schizophrenia-expert-dr-jeffrey-a-lieberman-unravels-the-mysteries-of-schizophrenia-on-the-peoples-pharmacy</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T16:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Millions of Americans live with schizophrenia, a complex and long misunderstood behavioral brain disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelle Pelle's Return to Project Show: Celebrating 46 Years of Leather and LegacyComputers, Technology &amp; InternetCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835626/pelle-pelles-return-to-project-show-celebrating-46-years-of-leather-and-legacy</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T15:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>LAS VEGAS, NV / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Amid the glitz and glamor of Las Vegas from February 13 to February 15, the renowned Project Show played host to a legendary label that has seamlessly stitched its name into the vibrant fabric of hip hop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversation with CEO Mark Harding in Chicago on March 15, 2024UtilitiesConferences</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835582/conversation-with-ceo-mark-harding-in-chicago-on-march-15-2024</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T14:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>DENVER, CO / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Pure Cycle Corporation (NASDAQ Capital Market:PCYO) announced its President and CEO will host an investor meeting in Chicago at NASDAQ's office (1 N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevating UK Podcast Excellence: Evergreen Podcasts Teams Up With Crowd NetworkPublishing &amp; MediaPartnerships</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835586/elevating-uk-podcast-excellence-evergreen-podcasts-teams-up-with-crowd-network</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T14:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CLEVELAND, OH / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Evergreen Podcasts (Evergreen) proudly announces a partnership with Crowd Network, an independent podcast network based in the UK and renowned for unforgettable stories and personalities. Evergreen introduces outstanding shows from Crowd Network, notably, We Didn't Start The Fire, a pop culture history podcast inspired by Billy Joel's song.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Closes Final Tranche Of Private PlacementMetals &amp; MiningCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835595/falcon-closes-final-tranche-of-private-placement</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T14:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / FALCON GOLD CORP. (TSX-V:FG)(FSE:3FA)(OTCQB:FGLDF) (the "Company") announces that it has closed the final tranche of its previously announced non-brokered private placement (the "Private Placement") by issuing 5,315,167 units (the "Units") at $0.03 per Unit for gross proceeds of $159,455.01 (the "Final Tranche").</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Courses to Communities, Dow and WM Drive SustainabilityIndustrial &amp; ManufacturingEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835592/from-courses-to-communities-dow-and-wm-drive-sustainability</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T14:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Given golf's intrinsic connection to nature, the significance of advancing sustainability in the sport cannot be overstated. And there's a growing responsibility to ensure its impact on the environment aligns with modern values for futureproofing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Tilly Analysis: Federal Supplier Climate Risks and Resilience Proposed Rule Introduces Heightened GHG Emissions Reporting for Federal ContractorsJulia SmithBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835593/baker-tilly-analysis-federal-supplier-climate-risks-and-resilience-proposed-rule-introduces-heightened-ghg-emissions-reporting-for-federal-contractors</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T14:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Baker TillyAuthored by Julia Smith and Brianna Hardy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Staffing Announces New Leadership for All Female Executive TeamBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesManagement Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835583/star-staffing-announces-new-leadership-for-all-female-executive-team</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T14:27:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SANTA ROSA, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / With record growth, Star Staffing announces the expansion of its leadership team with five new management leads to continue its legacy leading the employment industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tidal Wave Auto Spa Heads West With First Idaho Location, Adds Sixth Missouri WashAutomotiveCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835558/tidal-wave-auto-spa-heads-west-with-first-idaho-location-adds-sixth-missouri-wash</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>THOMASTON, GA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Tidal Wave Auto Spa, one of the nation's fastest-growing express car wash companies, celebrated the grand opening of two brand-new locations this week in Mountain Home, ID, and Independence, MO. The Mountain Home location is the company's first Idaho express wash and extends Tidal Wave's footprint to 25 states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanjeev Singh Sahni Affirms Commitment to B2B E-Commerce Leadership With Tastemakers AwardsPublishing &amp; MediaCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835555/sanjeev-singh-sahni-affirms-commitment-to-b2b-e-commerce-leadership-with-tastemakers-awards</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>WIXOM, MI / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Amid the recent restructuring efforts at Wayfair, including the layoff of 1,650 employees or 13% of its global workforce, Sanjeev Singh Sahni, leader of B2B business at Wayfair, has reaffirmed the company's dedication to excellence and innovation in the B2B e-commerce landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herring Global Highlights Massive Demand for Connecting DEXs and CEXsPublishing &amp; MediaCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835547/herring-global-highlights-massive-demand-for-connecting-dexs-and-cexs</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Herring Global, the Architects of Resilient Digital Assets Liquidity, continues to expand its services as the need for advanced market-making hinders new and existing web3 companies and projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comcast Celebrates the 2024 Lunar New Year With a Curated Collection of Asian and Asian American EntertainmentBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesDiversity, Equity and Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835550/comcast-celebrates-the-2024-lunar-new-year-with-a-curated-collection-of-asian-and-asian-american-entertainment</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>PHILADELPHIA, PA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / To celebrate Lunar New Year, Xfinity is launching a new, curated collection of Asian and Asian American entertainment across all its devices, including Xfinity X1, Xfinity Flex, and Xumo Stream Box.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon and Discovery Education Partner To Help Students Explore Cutting-Edge Careers and TechnologyTelecommunicationsEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835551/amazon-and-discovery-education-partner-to-help-students-explore-cutting-edge-careers-and-technology</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CHARLOTTE, NC / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Amazon and Discovery Education today announced a new partnership bringing Amazon Career Tours to classrooms nationwide. Amazon Career Tours offers free and interactive resources aligned to learning standards exploring the cutting-edge careers of the future by showcasing the innovative people and technology behind Amazon's innovations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKnightedXP and Forever Warriors Join Forces to Combat Military and Veteran SuicideAutomotivePartnerships</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835507/uknightedxp-and-forever-warriors-join-forces-to-combat-military-and-veteran-suicide</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>PENSACOLA, FL / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / UKnightedXP and Forever Warriors, powered by Step One Automotive Group, will be at PENSACON to provide key insights Leveraging Gaming and Gaming Culture to support Military and Veteran Suicide Awareness and Prevention. Mental health challenges and high suicide rates among Veterans and Active Duty have raised alarms across the Department of Defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buc-ee's to Debut New Travel Center in Johnstown, CO, on March 18Food &amp; Beverage ProductsCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835546/buc-ees-to-debut-new-travel-center-in-johnstown-co-on-march-18</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>JOHNSTOWN, CO / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Buc-ee's, home of the world's cleanest bathrooms, freshest food and friendliest beaver, will unveil its newest travel center in Johnstown, CO, on Monday, March 18, 2024. Doors will open to the public at 6 a.m. MDT, and a ribbon-cutting ceremony will follow at 11:00 a.m. MDT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurturing the Pioneering Spirit in Diverse CommunitiesOriginally published by Fortune on brand-studio.fortune.comIndustrial &amp; ManufacturingEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835548/nurturing-the-pioneering-spirit-in-diverse-communities</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T13:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / HenkelOriginally published by Fortune on brand-studio.fortune.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia Green Biotechnology Corp. Announces Agreement to Acquire Burton Growers Ltd. and Green Sight Agri-Holdings Ltd.Healthcare &amp; PharmaceuticalMergers and Acquisitions</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835512/asia-green-biotechnology-corp-announces-agreement-to-acquire-burton-growers-ltd-and-green-sight-agri-holdings-ltd</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T12:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CALGARY, AB / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / ASIA GREEN BIOTECHNOLOGY CORP. (CSE:ASIA) ("Asia Green" or the "Company") is pleased to announce that it has entered into a non-binding letter of intent ("LOI") to acquire all of the issued and outstanding shares of Burton Growers Ltd. ("Burton Growers") and Green Sight Agri-Holdings Inc. ("Green Sight"),</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cytex Launches CloakedPrivacy, First-Ever Cybersecurity and Encrypted VPN Mobile App For SmartphonesBlockchain &amp; CryptocurrencyProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835514/cytex-launches-cloakedprivacy-first-ever-cybersecurity-and-encrypted-vpn-mobile-app-for-smartphones</link>
      <date>2024-02-21T12:05:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 21, 2024 / Cytex, Inc., a SaaS-based, full-spectrum industry leader in enterprise cybersecurity solutions, announces CloakedPrivacy, a first-of-its-kind app that provides state-of-the-art encrypted VPN for mobile devices, protecting users from potential breaches and cyberthreats while giving them unparalleled control over their personal data across third-party applications.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>