<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss>
  <channel>
    <title>allwires</title>
    <link>[{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJaF1hQVQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFtRXw=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEF9YXA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtVVQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFtRWA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFxRXA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGV1SXw=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtYWA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtWXQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFxQWQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtYWQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://www.globenewswire.com/RssFeed/country/United%20States/feedTitle/GlobeNewswire%20-%20News%20from%20United%20States"},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEF5XWA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://www.prnewswire.com/rss/news-releases-list.rss"},{"blogUrl":"https://www.accesswire.com/newsroom","container":".article-box","header":"a","description":".html-embed-21.w-embed","link":"a","date":".article-date","loadType":"puppeteer"}]</link>
    <description>feed for allwires</description>
    <item>
      <title>Graham Holdings Company Reports 2023 and Fourth Quarter Earnings</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:33:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ARLINGTON, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Graham Holdings Company (NYSE: GHC) today reported its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year of 2023. The Company also filed its Form 10-K today for the year ended December 31, 2023 with the Securities and Exchange Commission. Division Operating Results Revenue for 2023 was $4,414.9 million, up 12% from $3,924.5 million in 2022. Revenues increased at education, healthcare and automotive, partially offset by declines at television broadcasting, m</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240222861262/en/Graham-Holdings-Company-Reports-2023-and-Fourth-Quarter-Earnings/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Home &amp;amp; Finance Holding Company to Announce Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results on March 28, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Better Home &amp;amp; Finance Holding Company (NASDAQ: BETR) intends to announce its fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results prior to the market opening on Thursday, March 28, 2024. A conference call and webcast to discuss those results will be held on the same day at 8:30 a.m. ET. Details to register for the live webcast and to listen to the call by phone will be available on the Company’s investor relations website located at investors.better.com and are inc</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223961092/en/Better-Home-Finance-Holding-Company-to-Announce-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-on-March-28-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crawford &amp;amp; Company® Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Earnings Conference Call</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ATLANTA--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #earnings--Crawford &amp;amp; Company® (NYSE: CRD-A and CRD-B) will issue its earnings release for its fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023, on Monday, March 4, 2024, at 4:15 p.m. Eastern Time. The quarterly conference call, to discuss Crawford’s quarterly and full year earnings and other developments, will be held on Tuesday, March 5, 2024, at 8:30 a.m. Eastern Time. For audio access only, the call can be accessed by dialing 1-888-259-6580, Conference ID: 83186255. F</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223741859/en/Crawford-Company%C2%AE-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Earnings-Conference-Call/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Douglas Elliman Inc. to Host Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results Conference Call</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MIAMI--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Douglas Elliman Inc. (NYSE: DOUG) will conduct a conference call and webcast to discuss its fourth quarter and full year 2023 results on Friday, March 1, 2024 at 8:00 a.m. (ET). Investors may access the call via live webcast at https://join.eventcastplus.com/eventcastplus/Douglas-Elliman-Inc-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Conference-Call. Please join the webcast at least 10 minutes prior to start time. A replay of the call will be available shortly after the call ends</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240222705740/en/Douglas-Elliman-Inc.-to-Host-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-Conference-Call/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AbCellera Announces Resignation of Board Member</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>VANCOUVER, British Columbia--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $ABCL--AbCellera (Nasdaq: ABCL) today announced that Peter Thiel has notified the Company of his intention to resign from the Company’s Board of Directors for personal reasons, effective March 7, 2024. “AbCellera continues to expand the frontier of biotech, a nefariously difficult and vital field,” said Peter Thiel. “I am proud to have helped them with their mission.” Mr. Thiel joined AbCellera’s Board of Directors in November 2020 and served as the Chairm</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223923459/en/AbCellera-Announces-Resignation-of-Board-Member/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie C. Lind Elected to Albany International Corp. Board of Directors</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:19:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ROCHESTER, N.H.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Albany International Corp. (NYSE:AIN) announced today that Bonnie C. Lind has been elected to its Board of Directors and that Director John R. Scannell has been appointed Chairman of the Board. Ms. Lind, age 65, served as Sr. Vice President, CFO &amp;amp; Treasurer of Neenah Inc. following its spinoff from Kimberly-Clark Corporation in 2004 until October 2020. Prior to that, from 1984 she held a number of increasingly senior financial and operational positions with</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223880692/en/Bonnie-C.-Lind-Elected-to-Albany-International-Corp.-Board-of-Directors/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Ryan Joins the Board of Directors of Dine Brands Global, Inc.</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PASADENA, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Dine Brands Global, Inc. (NYSE: DIN), the parent company of Applebee's Neighborhood Grill + Bar®, IHOP® and Fuzzy’s Taco Shop® restaurants, announced today that Matt Ryan will be joining as a new independent member of its Board of Directors. Matt currently serves as Chief Executive Officer of Soli Organic, the market leader in organic controlled environment agriculture. He leads the nation’s largest commercial indoor organic grower, redefining how fresh, organ</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223303050/en/Matt-Ryan-Joins-the-Board-of-Directors-of-Dine-Brands-Global-Inc./?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monica Richardson Appointed USA TODAY Senior Vice President</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 19:38:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MCLEAN, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Gannett Co., Inc. (NYSE: GCI) today announced Monica R. Richardson will join Gannett to lead USA TODAY’s award-winning newsroom as Senior Vice President effective April 1. Reporting to the Chief Content Officer, Richardson will work closely to extend the reach of the Nation’s Newspaper and invigorate USA TODAY’s portfolio. Richardson most recently served as Vice President of Local News and Large Markets for McClatchy. As a seasoned professional with a proven 30-yea</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223710950/en/Monica-Richardson-Appointed-USA-TODAY-Senior-Vice-President/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electra Participating in Upcoming North American Critical Minerals Industry &amp;amp; Investment Events</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $ELBM--Electra Battery Materials Corporation (NASDAQ: ELBM; TSX-V: ELBM) (“Electra”, “Company”) is pleased to announce senior management will be participating in the several investment and industry conferences: BMO Global Metals, Mining &amp;amp; Critical Minerals Conference, February 25-28 CEO, Trent Mell, will be available for one-on-one meetings with institutional and industry peers throughout the conference to discuss Electra’s near-term plans. Red Cloud’s Pre-PDAC Showcase –</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240224009017/en/Electra-Participating-in-Upcoming-North-American-Critical-Minerals-Industry-Investment-Events/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBC Bearings to Participate in the 14th Annual Alembic Global Advisors Investor Conference</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 22:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>OXFORD, Conn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--RBC Bearings Incorporated (NYSE: RBC, RBCP), a leading international manufacturer of highly engineered precision bearings, components and essential systems for the industrial, defense and aerospace industries, today announced that it will participate in the Alembic Global Advisors Investor Conference on February 28, 2024, in Deer Valley, Utah. Materials shared during the conference will be available online at: http://investor.rbcbearings.com. Vice President and C</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223372225/en/RBC-Bearings-to-Participate-in-the-14th-Annual-Alembic-Global-Advisors-Investor-Conference/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quanterix to Present at Cowen’s 44th Annual Health Care Conference</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BILLERICA, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Quanterix Corporation (NASDAQ: QTRX), a company fueling scientific discovery through ultrasensitive biomarker detection, today announced that Chief Executive Officer Masoud Toloue will present at Cowen’s 44th Annual Health Care Conference. Quanterix’s session will take place on Monday, March 4, 2024, at 12:50 p.m. EST and will be made available to attendees and, via webcast, the general public. In addition to the session, Quanterix will also host one-on-one me</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223277311/en/Quanterix-to-Present-at-Cowen%E2%80%99s-44th-Annual-Health-Care-Conference/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASRT CLASS ACTION ANNOUNCEMENT: Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp; Check, LLP Announces Securities Class Action Lawsuit Filed Against Assertio Holdings, Inc. (ASRT)</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;RADNOR, Pa., Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The law firm of &lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=Jg25yn_EgRzKQKR5YQfFb6ZAsiEsPGPnaaI5WXlRnOr9RTTanlaqWKQInrh0Coa2-wTkKsy3aLSFxegz2jGf_do39RwUY8FmMzA48InL4ZLY7s2C8nWZgGQNj7hEJzGp6GOMqq4MyU9QeejNVWCa_GjxIlOg4-5pzE2GweSZtsMgih3OLT0INtEuIxAmsTh7CsQkhLaazd8AHcbtUFGGDLLIYKKQzprjLL2TvBeNJ_o=" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title="Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp;amp; Check, LLP"&gt;Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp;amp; Check, LLP&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=jNwK12_eklc-zcNWLg7lwitvb_T0C2iA7sxncITKMNsoet1g8yJOn-n1fA_hRrAfieOqTN-IpDIGPuwJdZOaTw==" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title="www.ktmc.com"&gt;www.ktmc.com&lt;/a&gt;) informs investors that a securities class action lawsuit has been filed in the United States District Court for the Northern District of Illinois against Assertio Holdings, Inc. (“Assertio”) (&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=v3GLSmsSDSxSvN9FK0hn992QnpAjX5RZvP3UDKKMMUXZHNQQM9C-1kH0WovEZ_vS0xocQtiKJa42oymI_-7ZL8ZDxIreo75nXgWhpSVlCs2fjvQ1geqv_u0NvEBps9il9eZyNekt2TCqw6hT21kmtg==" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;NASDAQ: ASRT&lt;/a&gt;). The action charges Assertio with violations of the federal securities laws, including omissions and fraudulent misrepresentations relating to the company’s business, operations, and prospects. As a result of Assertio’ s materially misleading statements and omissions to the public, Assertio’ s investors have suffered significant losses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/25/2834748/0/en/ASRT-CLASS-ACTION-ANNOUNCEMENT-Kessler-Topaz-Meltzer-Check-LLP-Announces-Securities-Class-Action-Lawsuit-Filed-Against-Assertio-Holdings-Inc-ASRT.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP RANKED ROSEN LAW FIRM Encourages Thoughtworks Holding, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – TWKS</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Thoughtworks Holding, Inc. (NASDAQ: TWKS) resulting from allegations that Thoughtworks may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834743/673/en/TOP-RANKED-ROSEN-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Thoughtworks-Holding-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-TWKS.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONALLY RANKED ROSEN LAW FIRM Encourages Envoy Medical, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – COCH</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Envoy Medical, Inc. (NASDAQ: COCH) resulting from allegations that Envoy may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834742/673/en/NATIONALLY-RANKED-ROSEN-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Envoy-Medical-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-COCH.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A TOP RANKED LAW FIRM, Encourages Renovaro Biosciences Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – RENB</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Renovaro Biosciences Inc. (NASDAQ: RENB) resulting from allegations that Renovaro may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834741/673/en/ROSEN-A-TOP-RANKED-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Renovaro-Biosciences-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-RENB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING INVESTOR RIGHTS LAW FIRM, Encourages Altimmune, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – ALT</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces an investigation of potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Altimmune, Inc. (NASDAQ: ALT) resulting from allegations that Altimmune may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834740/673/en/ROSEN-A-LEADING-INVESTOR-RIGHTS-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Altimmune-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-ALT.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, TRUSTED NATIONAL TRIAL COUNSEL, Encourages The Chemours Company Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – CC</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY:&lt;/strong&gt; Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces an investigation of potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of The Chemours Company (NYSE: CC) resulting from allegations that Chemours may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834739/673/en/ROSEN-TRUSTED-NATIONAL-TRIAL-COUNSEL-Encourages-The-Chemours-Company-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-CC.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages Archer-Daniels-Midland Company Investors with Losses to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action – ADM</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 17:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of common stock of Archer-Daniels-Midland Company (NYSE: ADM) between April 30, 2020 and January 22, 2024, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 25, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834738/673/en/ROSEN-A-LEADING-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Archer-Daniels-Midland-Company-Investors-with-Losses-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-ADM.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages British American Tobacco p.l.c Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action First Filed by the Firm – BTI</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY:&lt;/strong&gt; Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of the securities of British American Tobacco p.l.c. (NYSE: BTI) between February 9, 2023 and December 6, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important&lt;strong&gt; March 25, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline &lt;/strong&gt;in the securities class action commenced by the Firm.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834737/673/en/ROSEN-A-LEADING-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-British-American-Tobacco-p-l-c-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-First-Filed-by-the-Firm-BTI.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, TRUSTED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages BioVie Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action – BIVI</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of securities of BioVie Inc. (NASDAQ: BIVI) between August 5, 2021 and November 29, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 19, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834736/673/en/ROSEN-TRUSTED-INVESTOR-COUNSEL-Encourages-BioVie-Inc-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-BIVI.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNTX 截止日期提醒：值得信賴的投資者法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵蒙受損失的 BioNTech SE 投資者在對 BNTX 提出證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 3 月 12 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  25, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事由：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒於 2022 年 3 月 30 日至 2023 年 10 月 13 日（含上述兩日期，簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買 BioNTech SE (NASDAQ: BNTX)證券之人士注意，&lt;strong&gt;首席原告的&lt;/strong&gt;重要&lt;strong&gt;截止日期為 2024 年 3 月 12 日。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834734/673/zh-hant/BNTX-%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F%E6%8F%90%E9%86%92-%E5%80%BC%E5%BE%97%E4%BF%A1%E8%B3%B4%E7%9A%84%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5%E8%92%99%E5%8F%97%E6%90%8D%E5%A4%B1%E7%9A%84-BioNTech-SE-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E5%B0%8D-BNTX-%E6%8F%90%E5%87%BA%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-3-%E6%9C%88-12-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSS 截止日期提醒：全球頂尖法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵損失逾 10 萬美元的 Maison Solutions Inc. 投資者在對 MSS 提出證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 3 月 4 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事因：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒 Maison Solutions Inc. (NASDAQ: MSS) 以下證券的購買者：(1) 根據就 Maison Solutions 2023 年 10 月首次公開招股（「IPO」）而發布的註冊聲明及招股章程（合稱「註冊聲明」）和／或可追溯至該聲明而購買其 A 類普通股之人士；和／或 (2) 於 2023 年 10 月 5 日至 2023 年 12 月 15 日期間（含上述兩日期，簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買其證券之人士，注意&lt;strong&gt;首席原告的&lt;/strong&gt;重要&lt;strong&gt;截止日期為 2024 年 3 月 4 日&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834733/673/zh-hant/MSS-%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F%E6%8F%90%E9%86%92-%E5%85%A8%E7%90%83%E9%A0%82%E5%B0%96%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5%E6%90%8D%E5%A4%B1%E9%80%BE-10-%E8%90%AC%E7%BE%8E%E5%85%83%E7%9A%84-Maison-Solutions-Inc-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E5%B0%8D-MSS-%E6%8F%90%E5%87%BA%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-3-%E6%9C%88-4-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>首屈一指的投資者法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵損失超過 10 萬美元的 Dada Nexus Limited 投資者在該律所對 DADA 首次提起證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 3 月 11 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事因：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒於 2023 年 5 月 11 日至 2024 年 1 月 8 日（含上述兩日期）期間（簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買 Dada Nexus Limited (NASDAQ: DADA) 證券之人士注意，由該律所首次提起的證券集體訴訟中，&lt;strong&gt;首席原告的&lt;/strong&gt;重要&lt;strong&gt;截止日期是 2024 年 3 月 11 日&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834732/673/zh-hant/%E9%A6%96%E5%B1%88%E4%B8%80%E6%8C%87%E7%9A%84%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5%E6%90%8D%E5%A4%B1%E8%B6%85%E9%81%8E-10-%E8%90%AC%E7%BE%8E%E5%85%83%E7%9A%84-Dada-Nexus-Limited-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E8%A9%B2%E5%BE%8B%E6%89%80%E5%B0%8D-DADA-%E9%A6%96%E6%AC%A1%E6%8F%90%E8%B5%B7%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-3-%E6%9C%88-11-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VNET 重要截止日期：全球投資者法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵 VNET Group, Inc. 投資者在對 VNET 提出證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 2 月 26 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事因：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒於 2022 年 4 月 8 日至 2023 年 2 月 15 日期間（含上述兩日期，簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買 VNET Group, Inc. (NASDAQ: VNET)證券之人士注意 &lt;strong&gt;2024 年 2 月 26 日這一&lt;/strong&gt;重要的&lt;strong&gt;首席原告截止日期&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834731/673/zh-hant/VNET-%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-%E5%85%A8%E7%90%83%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5-VNET-Group-Inc-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E5%B0%8D-VNET-%E6%8F%90%E5%87%BA%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-2-%E6%9C%88-26-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, SKILLED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages B. Riley Financial, Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action – RILY</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY:&lt;/strong&gt; Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of common stock of B. Riley Financial, Inc. (NASDAQ: RILY) between May 10, 2023 and November 9, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 25, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834729/673/en/ROSEN-SKILLED-INVESTOR-COUNSEL-Encourages-B-Riley-Financial-Inc-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-RILY.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, SKILLED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages Cummins Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action First Filed by the Firm – CMI</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of the securities of Cummins Inc. (NYSE: CMI) between April 30, 2019 and December 21, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 15, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline &lt;/strong&gt;in the securities class action first filed by the Firm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834727/673/en/ROSEN-SKILLED-INVESTOR-COUNSEL-Encourages-Cummins-Inc-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-First-Filed-by-the-Firm-CMI.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention CMI Shareholders: Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp;amp; Check, LLP Reminds Shareholders of Securities Fraud Class Action Lawsuit Filed against Cummins Inc. (CMI) and Encourages Investors to Contact the Firm</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 02:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RADNOR, Pa., Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- The law firm of Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp; Check, LLP (www.ktmc.com) informs investors that a securities class action lawsuit has been filed against Cummins Inc. ("Cummins") (NYSE: CMI). The action charges Cummins with violations of the federal...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/attention-cmi-shareholders-kessler-topaz-meltzer--check-llp-reminds-shareholders-of-securities-fraud-class-action-lawsuit-filed-against-cummins-inc-cmi-and-encourages-investors-to-contact-the-firm-302070273.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBLY CLASS ACTION NOTICE:  Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp;amp; Check, LLP Reminds Mobileye Global Inc. (MBLY) Shareholders of Securities Fraud Class Action Lawsuit and Encourages Investors with Substantial Losses to Contact the Firm</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RADNOR, Pa., Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- The law firm of Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp; Check, LLP (www.ktmc.com) informs investors that a securities class action lawsuit has been filed against Mobileye Global Inc. ("Mobileye") (NASDAQ: MBLY). The action charges Mobileye with violations of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/mbly-class-action-notice--kessler-topaz-meltzer--check-llp-reminds-mobileye-global-inc-mbly-shareholders-of-securities-fraud-class-action-lawsuit-and-encourages-investors-with-substantial-losses-to-contact-the-firm-302070279.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A GLOBALLY RESPECTED LAW FIRM, Encourages GrafTech International Ltd. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action - EAF</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of common stock of GrafTech International Ltd. (NYSE: EAF) between February 8, 2019 and August 3, 2023, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the important March 25,...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-a-globally-respected-law-firm-encourages-graftech-international-ltd-investors-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action--eaf-302070271.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING INVESTOR RIGHTS LAW FIRM, Encourages Hut 8 Corp. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action - HUT</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of securities of Hut 8 Corp. (NASDAQ: HUT) between November 9, 2023 and January 18, 2024, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the April 8, 2024 lead plaintiff...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-a-leading-investor-rights-law-firm-encourages-hut-8-corp-investors-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action--hut-302070044.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, RECOGNIZED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages Future FinTech Group Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action First Filed by the Firm - FTFT</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of the securities of Future FinTech Group Inc. (NASDAQ: FTFT) between March 10, 2020 and January 11, 2024, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the important March...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-recognized-investor-counsel-encourages-future-fintech-group-inc-investors-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action-first-filed-by-the-firm--ftft-302070042.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNTX DEADLINE NOTICE: ROSEN, A LEADING NATIONAL FIRM, Encourages BioNTech SE Investors with Losses in Excess of $100K to Secure Counsel Before Important March 12 Deadline in Securities Class Action - BNTX</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of securities of BioNTech SE (NASDAQ: BNTX) between March 30, 2022 and October 13, 2023, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the important March 12, 2024 lead...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bntx-deadline-notice-rosen-a-leading-national-firm-encourages-biontech-se-investors-with-losses-in-excess-of-100k-to-secure-counsel-before-important-march-12-deadline-in-securities-class-action--bntx-302070017.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A GLOBAL AND LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages Innodata Inc. Investors with Losses to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action - INOD</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces the filing of a class action lawsuit on behalf of purchasers of common stock of Innodata Inc. (NASDAQ: INOD) between May 9, 2019 and February 14, 2024, both dates inclusive (the...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-a-global-and-leading-law-firm-encourages-innodata-inc-investors-with-losses-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action--inod-302070244.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, LEADING TRIAL ATTORNEYS, Encourages Hywin Holdings Ltd. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation - HYW</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Hywin Holdings Ltd. (NASDAQ: HYW) resulting from allegations that Hywin Holdings may have issued materially...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-leading-trial-attorneys-encourages-hywin-holdings-ltd-investors-to-inquire-about-securities-class-action-investigation--hyw-302070312.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, LEADING TRIAL ATTORNEYS, Encourages Fluence Energy, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation - FLNC</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces an investigation of potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Fluence Energy, Inc. (NASDAQ: FLNC) resulting from allegations that Fluence Energy may have issued...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-leading-trial-attorneys-encourages-fluence-energy-inc-investors-to-inquire-about-securities-class-action-investigation--flnc-302070050.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSS DEADLINE NOTICE: ROSEN, A LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages Maison Solutions Inc. Investors with Losses in Excess of $100K to Secure Counsel Before Important March 4 Deadline in Securities Class Action - MSS</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of Maison Solutions Inc. (NASDAQ: MSS): (1) Class A common stock pursuant and/or traceable to the registration statement and prospectus (collectively, the "Registration...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/mss-deadline-notice-rosen-a-leading-law-firm-encourages-maison-solutions-inc-investors-with-losses-in-excess-of-100k-to-secure-counsel-before-important-march-4-deadline-in-securities-class-action--mss-302070005.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havertys Announces First Quarter Cash Dividend Consumer &amp; Retail ProductsDividends</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836217/havertys-announces-first-quarter-cash-dividend</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:11:00.000Z</date>
      <description>ATLANTA, GA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / HAVERTYS (NYSE:HVT)(NYSE:HVT.A) announced today that its board of directors declared a cash dividend to be paid on the outstanding shares of the two classes of $1 par value common stock of the company at a rate of $0.30 per share on the common stock and $0.28 per share on the Class A common stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHG Capital Corporation Announces Additional Contribution to Trust Account to Extend Period to Consummate Business CombinationBanking &amp; Financial ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836099/hhg-capital-corporation-announces-additional-contribution-to-trust-account-to-extend-period-to-consummate-business-combination</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:10:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / HHG Capital Corporation (the "Company") (NASDAQ:HHGC) announced today that the Company made a deposit on February 23, 2024 to the trust account and extended the amount of time it has available to complete a business combination from February 23, 2024 to March 23, 2024, by depositing $0.0333 for each issued and outstanding company ordinary share issued in the Company's initial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Month-End Portfolio Data Now Available for Ares Dynamic Credit Allocation Fund, Inc.www.arespublicfunds.comBanking &amp; Financial ServicesEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836015/month-end-portfolio-data-now-available-for-ares-dynamic-credit-allocation-fund-inc</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T14:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Ares Capital Management II LLC today announced that monthly fund composition and performance data for Ares Dynamic Credit Allocation Fund, Inc. (NYSE:ARDC) as of January 31, 2024 is now available via www.arespublicfunds.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Clorox Company Named Barron's Most Sustainable U.S. Company for Second Year in a RowIndustrial &amp; ManufacturingEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836255/the-clorox-company-named-barrons-most-sustainable-us-company-for-second-year-in-a-row</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>OAKLAND, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / The Clorox Company (NYSE:CLX) has earned the top ranking on Barron's 2024 100 Most Sustainable Companies list - its second consecutive year in the top spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network-1 Declares Semi-Annual DividendClean TechnologyDividends</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836215/network-1-declares-semi-annual-dividend</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T12:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW CANAAN, CT / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Network-1 Technologies, Inc. (NYSE American:NTIP) today announced that its Board of Directors has declared a semi-annual cash dividend of $0.05 per common share pursuant to its dividend policy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>