<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss>
  <channel>
    <title>allwires</title>
    <link>[{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJaF1hQVQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFtRXw=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEF9YXA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtVVQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFtRWA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFxRXA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGV1SXw=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtYWA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtWXQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEFxQWQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeGVtYWQ=="},{"blogUrl":"https://www.globenewswire.com/RssFeed/country/United%20States/feedTitle/GlobeNewswire%20-%20News%20from%20United%20States"},{"blogUrl":"https://feed.businesswire.com/rss/home/?rss=G1QFDERJXkJeEF5XWA=="},{"blogUrl":"https://www.prnewswire.com/rss/news-releases-list.rss"},{"blogUrl":"https://www.accesswire.com/newsroom","container":".article-box","header":"a","description":".html-embed-21.w-embed","link":"a","date":".article-date","loadType":"puppeteer"}]</link>
    <description>feed for allwires</description>
    <item>
      <title>Berkshire Hathaway Inc. News Release</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>OMAHA, Neb.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(BRK.A; BRK.B) – Berkshire’s operating results for the fourth quarter and full year of 2023 and 2022 are summarized in the following paragraphs. However, we urge investors and reporters to read our 2023 Annual Report, which has been posted at www.berkshirehathaway.com. The limited information that follows in this press release is not adequate for making an informed investment judgment. Earnings (losses) of Berkshire Hathaway Inc. and its consolidated subsidiaries f</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240224643700/en/Berkshire-Hathaway-Inc.-News-Release/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graham Holdings Company Reports 2023 and Fourth Quarter Earnings</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:33:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ARLINGTON, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Graham Holdings Company (NYSE: GHC) today reported its financial results for the fourth quarter and full year of 2023. The Company also filed its Form 10-K today for the year ended December 31, 2023 with the Securities and Exchange Commission. Division Operating Results Revenue for 2023 was $4,414.9 million, up 12% from $3,924.5 million in 2022. Revenues increased at education, healthcare and automotive, partially offset by declines at television broadcasting, m</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240222861262/en/Graham-Holdings-Company-Reports-2023-and-Fourth-Quarter-Earnings/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Home &amp;amp; Finance Holding Company to Announce Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results on March 28, 2024</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Better Home &amp;amp; Finance Holding Company (NASDAQ: BETR) intends to announce its fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results prior to the market opening on Thursday, March 28, 2024. A conference call and webcast to discuss those results will be held on the same day at 8:30 a.m. ET. Details to register for the live webcast and to listen to the call by phone will be available on the Company’s investor relations website located at investors.better.com and are inc</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223961092/en/Better-Home-Finance-Holding-Company-to-Announce-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-on-March-28-2024/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crawford &amp;amp; Company® Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Earnings Conference Call</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ATLANTA--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #earnings--Crawford &amp;amp; Company® (NYSE: CRD-A and CRD-B) will issue its earnings release for its fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2023, on Monday, March 4, 2024, at 4:15 p.m. Eastern Time. The quarterly conference call, to discuss Crawford’s quarterly and full year earnings and other developments, will be held on Tuesday, March 5, 2024, at 8:30 a.m. Eastern Time. For audio access only, the call can be accessed by dialing 1-888-259-6580, Conference ID: 83186255. F</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223741859/en/Crawford-Company%C2%AE-Announces-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Earnings-Conference-Call/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Douglas Elliman Inc. to Host Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2023 Results Conference Call</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MIAMI--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Douglas Elliman Inc. (NYSE: DOUG) will conduct a conference call and webcast to discuss its fourth quarter and full year 2023 results on Friday, March 1, 2024 at 8:00 a.m. (ET). Investors may access the call via live webcast at https://join.eventcastplus.com/eventcastplus/Douglas-Elliman-Inc-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Conference-Call. Please join the webcast at least 10 minutes prior to start time. A replay of the call will be available shortly after the call ends</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240222705740/en/Douglas-Elliman-Inc.-to-Host-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023-Results-Conference-Call/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fZYqiffDpHIASjea2DwvsWD1w08bW43U_zsPK9s38B4rCOi9QzgjCezTS3Nw_X6kJUrpSBm-Hav1w-UkdSlG3nBCddZ7R8TUqSJPYIyhFzD7nKdfLXU1CD0fwzlM5l88g==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Phoenix Vice Provost Doris Savron Is a Featured Guest on The EdUp Experience Podcast</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PHOENIX--(BUSINESS WIRE)--University of Phoenix is pleased to share that Doris Savron, vice provost of Colleges, Curriculum and Assessment, was a featured guest of The EdUp Experience podcast. Hosted by co-founder Joe Sallustino, Ed.D., the podcast was recorded onsite at the 2024 InsightsEDU Conference held in Phoenix, Arizona, in an episode with Savron that explored the career focus for working adult learners at University of Phoenix and related trends in higher education. “Our mission to serv</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240224702323/en/University-of-Phoenix-Vice-Provost-Doris-Savron-Is-a-Featured-Guest-on-The-EdUp-Experience-Podcast/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AbCellera Announces Resignation of Board Member</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>VANCOUVER, British Columbia--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $ABCL--AbCellera (Nasdaq: ABCL) today announced that Peter Thiel has notified the Company of his intention to resign from the Company’s Board of Directors for personal reasons, effective March 7, 2024. “AbCellera continues to expand the frontier of biotech, a nefariously difficult and vital field,” said Peter Thiel. “I am proud to have helped them with their mission.” Mr. Thiel joined AbCellera’s Board of Directors in November 2020 and served as the Chairm</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223923459/en/AbCellera-Announces-Resignation-of-Board-Member/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie C. Lind Elected to Albany International Corp. Board of Directors</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:19:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>ROCHESTER, N.H.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Albany International Corp. (NYSE:AIN) announced today that Bonnie C. Lind has been elected to its Board of Directors and that Director John R. Scannell has been appointed Chairman of the Board. Ms. Lind, age 65, served as Sr. Vice President, CFO &amp;amp; Treasurer of Neenah Inc. following its spinoff from Kimberly-Clark Corporation in 2004 until October 2020. Prior to that, from 1984 she held a number of increasingly senior financial and operational positions with</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223880692/en/Bonnie-C.-Lind-Elected-to-Albany-International-Corp.-Board-of-Directors/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Ryan Joins the Board of Directors of Dine Brands Global, Inc.</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PASADENA, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Dine Brands Global, Inc. (NYSE: DIN), the parent company of Applebee's Neighborhood Grill + Bar®, IHOP® and Fuzzy’s Taco Shop® restaurants, announced today that Matt Ryan will be joining as a new independent member of its Board of Directors. Matt currently serves as Chief Executive Officer of Soli Organic, the market leader in organic controlled environment agriculture. He leads the nation’s largest commercial indoor organic grower, redefining how fresh, organ</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223303050/en/Matt-Ryan-Joins-the-Board-of-Directors-of-Dine-Brands-Global-Inc./?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monica Richardson Appointed USA TODAY Senior Vice President</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 19:38:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MCLEAN, Va.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Gannett Co., Inc. (NYSE: GCI) today announced Monica R. Richardson will join Gannett to lead USA TODAY’s award-winning newsroom as Senior Vice President effective April 1. Reporting to the Chief Content Officer, Richardson will work closely to extend the reach of the Nation’s Newspaper and invigorate USA TODAY’s portfolio. Richardson most recently served as Vice President of Local News and Large Markets for McClatchy. As a seasoned professional with a proven 30-yea</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223710950/en/Monica-Richardson-Appointed-USA-TODAY-Senior-Vice-President/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chickasaw Community Bank Names Bill Schonacher as CEO</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 19:19:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>OKLAHOMA CITY--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Chickasaw Community Bank announces the hiring of Bill Schonacher as its new Chief Executive Officer.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223680552/en/Chickasaw-Community-Bank-Names-Bill-Schonacher-as-CEO/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Rebar Technology Appoints Josh Mathers as Interim CEO</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:40:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>CHICAGO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Rebar Technology, a privately held company providing custom recurring billing and payment solutions for merchants and service providers, announced that Josh Mathers, Vice President of Product at Rebar, has been appointed Interim Chief Executive Officer effective immediately. In connection with the appointment, Nick Fredrick has stepped down as President &amp;amp; CEO of Rebar Technology. As Interim CEO of Rebar, Josh Mathers will work with Rebar Technology Board Members an</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223142815/en/%C2%A0Rebar-Technology-Appoints-Josh-Mathers-as-Interim-CEO/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears Law Announces Appointment of Chief Operating Officer</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:27:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Fears Law, a national law firm based in Dallas, with a proven track record for achieving favorable verdicts and resolutions on behalf of clients, proudly announces the appointment of Debbie Ames as its new Chief Operating Officer (COO). Debbie’s appointment signifies the firm's unwavering commitment to provide exceptional client service and to follow the highest principles of professionalism. In her role as COO, Ms. Ames will spearhead the acceleration of the firm’s gro</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223584961/en/Fears-Law-Announces-Appointment-of-Chief-Operating-Officer/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-ed20Xeg3m02ke7wLHzR0vhC-PaDxm2AxJabicA7iw7ievRMp3sIgu8q3wq1OF24lT93qbEzrwa15HGbLqMObxZyOJkysC5Ezh0qTiBmuAAj_MB0k7bSxuNDrJ9ITS1Yyw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Phoenix Vice Provost Doris Savron Is a Featured Guest on The EdUp Experience Podcast</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PHOENIX--(BUSINESS WIRE)--University of Phoenix is pleased to share that Doris Savron, vice provost of Colleges, Curriculum and Assessment, was a featured guest of The EdUp Experience podcast. Hosted by co-founder Joe Sallustino, Ed.D., the podcast was recorded onsite at the 2024 InsightsEDU Conference held in Phoenix, Arizona, in an episode with Savron that explored the career focus for working adult learners at University of Phoenix and related trends in higher education. “Our mission to serv</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240224702323/en/University-of-Phoenix-Vice-Provost-Doris-Savron-Is-a-Featured-Guest-on-The-EdUp-Experience-Podcast/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fI1LKiRF8kvOi6mZc0mLuEN0wLKKnrViSFiO4T0aislWNiRUTqhnC0rF0EY-oNxAhUHaNHdlJeZqVEj0aPvPUXU121C5pmgB6vWtBIdSa8GKIq8OW1CzdXUuJs9GinlrzkRDlv9quRr6zgX7hvSIvI=</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>York University Academic Workers Vote to Strike Monday</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:40:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Three thousand contract instructors, teaching assistants and graduate assistants at York University will be on strike Monday morning unless their employer comes back to the table with a real plan to address the affordability crisis. “We’re struggling to make ends meet. Basic needs like housing and food have skyrocketed in price, but the wages for people who do the majority of teaching at York have been falling further and further behind,” said Erin McIntosh, PhD Studen</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223198343/en/York-University-Academic-Workers-Vote-to-Strike-Monday/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fI1LKiRF8kvOi6mZc0mLuEN0wLKKnrViSFiO4T0aislWNiRUTqhnC0rF0EY-oNxAhUHaNHdlJeZqVEj0aPvPUXU121C5pmgB6vWtBIdSa8GKIq8OW1CzdXUuJs9GinlrzkRDlv9quRr6zgX7hvSIvI=</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARC Ltd. and Milliman Award Scholarships to Empower Africa&amp;apos;s Next Generation of Climate Change Leaders</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 19:46:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NAIROBI, Kenya--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Five exceptional African students are set to become sustainability changemakers as the first recipients of fully funded climate change scholarships from African Risk Capacity (ARC) Limited and Milliman Inc. The Africa Scholarship Programme aims to empower the next generation of leaders to drive solutions to Africa's climate threats. The recipients stood out among 15 finalists for their academic excellence, community activism, demonstrated leadership, and passion</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221924351/en/ARC-Ltd.-and-Milliman-Award-Scholarships-to-Empower-Africas-Next-Generation-of-Climate-Change-Leaders/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fI1LKiRF8kvOi6mZc0mLuEN0wLKKnrViSFiO4T0aislWNiRUTqhnC0rF0EY-oNxAhUHaNHdlJeZqVEj0aPvPUXU121C5pmgB6vWtBIdSa8GKIq8OW1CzdXUuJs9GinlrzkRDlv9quRr6zgX7hvSIvI=</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Phoenix Leadership to Present at Greater Phoenix Chamber Event</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 19:26:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>PHOENIX--(BUSINESS WIRE)--University of Phoenix proudly presents its distinguished leaders as featured speakers at the Greater Phoenix Chamber's quarterly Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion (DEI) Forum. University of Phoenix Vice President, Accreditation &amp;amp; Regulatory Compliance, McCeil Johnson, along with Vice Provost for Colleges, Assessment, and Curriculum, Doris Savron will be speaking about the importance of social capital in diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) initiatives. The event,</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223215916/en/University-of-Phoenix-Leadership-to-Present-at-Greater-Phoenix-Chamber-Event/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fI1LKiRF8kvOi6mZc0mLuEN0wLKKnrViSFiO4T0aislWNiRUTqhnC0rF0EY-oNxAhUHaNHdlJeZqVEj0aPvPUXU121C5pmgB6vWtBIdSa8GKIq8OW1CzdXUuJs9GinlrzkRDlv9quRr6zgX7hvSIvI=</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support workers at University of Toronto vote in support of strike action</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:03:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)--A thousand workers at the University of Toronto, including maintenance workers, caretakers, groundskeepers, veterinary technologists, casual workers, student residence and foodservice staff, and others voted 93% to strike if their employer does not take action to address the rising cost of living and provide a living wage. “The cost of rent keeps going up. The price of food, of gas, of transit are all going up. More and more, we can’t afford to live in the city we work</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223789809/en/Support-workers-at-University-of-Toronto-vote-in-support-of-strike-action/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fI1LKiRF8kvOi6mZc0mLuEN0wLKKnrViSFiO4T0aislWNiRUTqhnC0rF0EY-oNxAhUHaNHdlJeZqVEj0aPvPUXU121C5pmgB6vWtBIdSa8GKIq8OW1CzdXUuJs9GinlrzkRDlv9quRr6zgX7hvSIvI=</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samenvatting: Mavenir levert in samenwerking met Intel geoptimaliseerde prestaties en energie-efficiëntie voor 4G en 5G Open vRAN-oplossing</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:08:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BARCELONA, Spanje--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mavenir, de leverancier van cloud-native netwerkinfrastructuur die bouwt aan netwerken van de toekomst, kondigt vandaag aan dat het zijn baanbrekende Open vRAN-oplossing nu kan leveren. Deze wordt ondersteund door 4e generatie Intel Xeon Scalable processors met Intel vRAN Boost en biedt hoge prestates en energiezuinige toepassingen in de cloud voor latentie-gevoelige en rekenintensieve mobiele netwerktoepassingen. Mavenir's overstap naar Intel's recente proce</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223503037/nl/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavenir與Intel合作，為4G和5G Open vRAN解決方案提供最佳化的效能和功率效率</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:07:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>西班牙巴塞隆納--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美國商業資訊)-- 致力於建構未來網路的雲端原生網路基礎設施供應商Mavenir今天宣布推出整合Intel vRAN Boost的第四代Intel Xeon可擴展處理器所支援的尖端Open vRAN解決方案，為延遲敏感型和運算密集型行動網路應用提供雲端原生、高性能和高能效的解決方案。Mavenir最近轉向使用Intel的新型處理器來支援vRAN，這代表其解決方案的最新最佳化。Mavenir透過三代Intel Xeon可擴展處理器推動了Open RAN的發展動力。 Mavenir的Open vRAN解決方案由整合Intel vRAN Boost的第四代Intel Xeon可擴展處理器提供支援，為下一代4G和5G網路提供了一套卓越的效能、功能和整合的人工智慧(AI)和機器學習(ML)應用。Mavenir與Intel建立了密切的長期科技合作關係，透過採用英特爾處理器，能夠開發出更高效、更具成本效益的RAN。這些最佳化是透過提供更大容量的處理能力來實現的，從而減少了每個基地台所需的內核或伺服器數量。 Mavenir的Open vRAN解決方</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223012991/zh-HK/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavenir携手英特尔为4G和5G开放式vRAN解决方案优化性能和能效</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:04:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>西班牙巴塞罗那--(BUSINESS WIRE)--(美国商业资讯)-- Mavenir是一家从事未来网络建设的云原生网络基础设施提供商，今天宣布推出先进的开放式vRAN解决方案，依托采用英特尔® vRAN Boost的第四代英特尔至强可扩展处理器，为延迟敏感型和计算密集型的移动网络应用提供节能高效的云原生高性能解决方案。为vRAN解决方案采用英特尔公司最新款的处理器，标志着Mavenir在解决方案优化方面更进一步，跨越整整三代英特尔至强可扩展处理器推动着开放式RAN的前进。 Mavenir的开放式vRAN解决方案依托采用英特尔vRAN Boost的第四代英特尔至强可扩展处理器，为下一代4G和5G网络提供卓越且全面的性能、功能并集成了人工智能和机器学习应用。Mavenir与英特尔建立了长期的紧密技术合作，采用英特尔处理器有利于开发更高效、更经济的RAN。这些优化是通过提供更多处理能力以及更大的容量，从而可以减少单个基站所需的核心或服务器数量来实现的。 Mavenir的开放式vRAN解决方案由虚拟化的分布式单元(vDU)和中央单元(vCU)组成，支持所有代系的移动网络（2G、4G、5G）</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223862684/zh-CN/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavenir en colaboración con Intel brinda rendimiento optimizado y eficiencia energética para las soluciones vRAN abiertas 4G y 5G</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:46:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BARCELONA, España--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mavenir, el proveedor de infraestructura de redes nativas de la nube que construye el futuro de las redes, anuncia hoy el lanzamiento de su solución vRAN abierta de vanguardia con tecnología de los procesadores escalables Intel Xeon de 4.° generación con Intel vRAN Boost, de ese modo brinda una solución de eficiencia energética, alto rendimiento y nativa de la nube para aplicaciones de redes móviles con uso intensivo de los recursos informáticos y de sensibil</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223815900/es/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavenir em cooperação com Intel oferece desempenho otimizado e eficiência energética para solução Open vRAN 4G e 5G</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:32:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BARCELONA, Espanha--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mavenir, provedor de infraestrutura de rede nativa em nuvem que está construindo o futuro das redes, anuncia hoje a disponibilidade de sua solução Open vRAN de ponta, equipada com processadores escaláveis Intel Xeon de 4ª geração com Intel vRAN Boost, oferecendo uma solução nativa em nuvem, de alto desempenho e eficiência energética para aplicativos de rede móvel sensíveis à latência e com uso intensivo de computação. A mudança para os recentes processadores</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223857758/pt/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riassunto: Mavenir in collaborazione con Intel offre prestazioni ottimizzate ed efficienza di alimentazione per la soluzione Open vRAN 4G e 5G</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:28:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BARCELLONA, Spagna--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mavenir, il fornitore di infrastrutture di rete cloud-native che sviluppa il futuro delle reti, ha annunciato oggi la disponibilità della sua innovativa soluzione Open vRAN alimentata dai processori Intel Xeon Scalable di 4ª generazione con Intel vRAN Boost, in grado di offrire una soluzione cloud-native, ad alte prestazioni ed efficiente dal punto di vista energetico per applicazioni di rete mobili sensibili alla latenza e ad alta intensità di calcolo. Il p</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223967588/it/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavenir, en collaboration avec Intel, fournit une performance et une écoefficience accrues pour les solutions Open vRAN 4G et 5G</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:25:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BARCELONE, Espagne--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mavenir, le fournisseur d’infrastructure réseau natif cloud qui construit l’avenir des réseaux, annonce aujourd’hui la disponibilité de sa solution de pointe Open vRAN, optimisée par des processeurs Intel Xeon Scalable de 4e génération avec Intel vRAN Boost, offrant une solution native cloud, haute performance et écoefficiente pour les applications de réseau mobile sensibles à la latence et à forte intensité de calcul. Le passage aux processeurs récents d’In</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223420447/fr/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavenir liefert in Zusammenarbeit mit Intel eine 4G und 5G Open vRAN-Lösung mit optimierter Leistung und Energieeffizienz</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:21:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BARCELONA, Spanien--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Mavenir, der Anbieter von Cloud-nativer Funknetzinfrastruktur, der die Zukunft der Funknetze gestaltet, meldet heute die Markteinführung seiner richtungsweisenden Open vRAN-Lösung, die auf skalierbaren Intel Xeon Prozessoren der 4. Generation mit Intel vRAN Boost basiert. Damit bietet das Unternehmen eine Cloud-native, leistungsstarke und energieeffiziente Lösung für latenzempfindliche und rechenintensive Mobilfunknetzanwendungen. Bei dem Umstieg auf die akt</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223970729/de/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electra Participating in Upcoming North American Critical Minerals Industry &amp;amp; Investment Events</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 13:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>TORONTO--(BUSINESS WIRE)---- $ELBM--Electra Battery Materials Corporation (NASDAQ: ELBM; TSX-V: ELBM) (“Electra”, “Company”) is pleased to announce senior management will be participating in the several investment and industry conferences: BMO Global Metals, Mining &amp;amp; Critical Minerals Conference, February 25-28 CEO, Trent Mell, will be available for one-on-one meetings with institutional and industry peers throughout the conference to discuss Electra’s near-term plans. Red Cloud’s Pre-PDAC Showcase –</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240224009017/en/Electra-Participating-in-Upcoming-North-American-Critical-Minerals-Industry-Investment-Events/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavenir in Collaboration with Intel Delivers Optimised Performance and Power Efficiency for 4G and 5G Open vRAN Solution</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 11:37:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BARCELONA, Spain--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- #4G--Mavenir's Open vRAN, driven by 4th Gen Intel Xeon Scalable processors, offers ideal performance, functionality &amp; integrated AI/ML for 4G/5G networks.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223458554/en/Mavenir-in-Collaboration-with-Intel-Delivers-Optimised-Performance-and-Power-Efficiency-for-4G-and-5G-Open-vRAN-Solution/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orca Bio Presents Promising Data on Orca-T in Two Oral Presentations at the 2024 Tandem Meetings of ASTCT® and CIBMTR®</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 22:15:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>MENLO PARK, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Orca Bio, a late-stage biotechnology company developing high-precision cell therapies for the treatment of cancer, autoimmune diseases and genetic blood disorders, today announced positive data on its lead investigational high-precision cell therapy, Orca-T, presented at the 2024 Tandem Meetings, Transplantation &amp;amp; Cellular Therapy Meetings of the American Society for Transplantation and Cellular Therapy (ASTCT) and the Center for International Blood and</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240222904836/en/Orca-Bio-Presents-Promising-Data-on-Orca-T-in-Two-Oral-Presentations-at-the-2024-Tandem-Meetings-of-ASTCT%C2%AE-and-CIBMTR%C2%AE/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBC Bearings to Participate in the 14th Annual Alembic Global Advisors Investor Conference</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 22:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>OXFORD, Conn.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--RBC Bearings Incorporated (NYSE: RBC, RBCP), a leading international manufacturer of highly engineered precision bearings, components and essential systems for the industrial, defense and aerospace industries, today announced that it will participate in the Alembic Global Advisors Investor Conference on February 28, 2024, in Deer Valley, Utah. Materials shared during the conference will be available online at: http://investor.rbcbearings.com. Vice President and C</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223372225/en/RBC-Bearings-to-Participate-in-the-14th-Annual-Alembic-Global-Advisors-Investor-Conference/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORRECTING and REPLACING Shoptalk Announces Speaker Lineup for 2024 Event in Las Vegas</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:42:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Shoptalk announced the speaker lineup for its 2024 conference taking place March 17–20 at Mandalay Bay in Las Vegas.</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240221543622/en/CORRECTING-and-REPLACING-Shoptalk-Announces-Speaker-Lineup-for-2024-Event-in-Las-Vegas/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quanterix to Present at Cowen’s 44th Annual Health Care Conference</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:30:00 UT</pubDate>
      <description>BILLERICA, Mass.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Quanterix Corporation (NASDAQ: QTRX), a company fueling scientific discovery through ultrasensitive biomarker detection, today announced that Chief Executive Officer Masoud Toloue will present at Cowen’s 44th Annual Health Care Conference. Quanterix’s session will take place on Monday, March 4, 2024, at 12:50 p.m. EST and will be made available to attendees and, via webcast, the general public. In addition to the session, Quanterix will also host one-on-one me</description>
      <link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240223277311/en/Quanterix-to-Present-at-Cowen%E2%80%99s-44th-Annual-Health-Care-Conference/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-fTiTHZ_tL7veK4k7YjFBuWKa1ah7uC6RdZY8DBvigxR7fxFuNFTHSunhvli30RlBNXya2izy9YOgHlBiZQk2LPgxNjXHjsNmKaXEz4koEK2b14xTzGINXzl6XdKCab6Yw==</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASRT CLASS ACTION ANNOUNCEMENT: Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp; Check, LLP Announces Securities Class Action Lawsuit Filed Against Assertio Holdings, Inc. (ASRT)</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;RADNOR, Pa., Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The law firm of &lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=Jg25yn_EgRzKQKR5YQfFb6ZAsiEsPGPnaaI5WXlRnOr9RTTanlaqWKQInrh0Coa2-wTkKsy3aLSFxegz2jGf_do39RwUY8FmMzA48InL4ZLY7s2C8nWZgGQNj7hEJzGp6GOMqq4MyU9QeejNVWCa_GjxIlOg4-5pzE2GweSZtsMgih3OLT0INtEuIxAmsTh7CsQkhLaazd8AHcbtUFGGDLLIYKKQzprjLL2TvBeNJ_o=" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title="Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp;amp; Check, LLP"&gt;Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp;amp; Check, LLP&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=jNwK12_eklc-zcNWLg7lwitvb_T0C2iA7sxncITKMNsoet1g8yJOn-n1fA_hRrAfieOqTN-IpDIGPuwJdZOaTw==" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title="www.ktmc.com"&gt;www.ktmc.com&lt;/a&gt;) informs investors that a securities class action lawsuit has been filed in the United States District Court for the Northern District of Illinois against Assertio Holdings, Inc. (“Assertio”) (&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=v3GLSmsSDSxSvN9FK0hn992QnpAjX5RZvP3UDKKMMUXZHNQQM9C-1kH0WovEZ_vS0xocQtiKJa42oymI_-7ZL8ZDxIreo75nXgWhpSVlCs2fjvQ1geqv_u0NvEBps9il9eZyNekt2TCqw6hT21kmtg==" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;NASDAQ: ASRT&lt;/a&gt;). The action charges Assertio with violations of the federal securities laws, including omissions and fraudulent misrepresentations relating to the company’s business, operations, and prospects. As a result of Assertio’ s materially misleading statements and omissions to the public, Assertio’ s investors have suffered significant losses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/25/2834748/0/en/ASRT-CLASS-ACTION-ANNOUNCEMENT-Kessler-Topaz-Meltzer-Check-LLP-Announces-Securities-Class-Action-Lawsuit-Filed-Against-Assertio-Holdings-Inc-ASRT.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celldex Therapeutics Presents Positive 12 Week Results from Barzolvolimab Phase 2 Study in Chronic Spontaneous Urticaria</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 19:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Primary and secondary endpoints met with clinically meaningful and statistically significant decreases in urticaria disease activity across multiple dose groups -&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Sustained activity with rapid onset within 2 weeks -&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Similar improvement in omalizumab-experienced/refractory and omalizumab-naïve disease consistent with unique mechanism of action -&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Favorable safety profile -&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- 52 week results and Phase 3 CSU trial initiations anticipated in 2024 -&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Company to host webcast February 25th at 9:45 am ET-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834744/24180/en/Celldex-Therapeutics-Presents-Positive-12-Week-Results-from-Barzolvolimab-Phase-2-Study-in-Chronic-Spontaneous-Urticaria.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP RANKED ROSEN LAW FIRM Encourages Thoughtworks Holding, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – TWKS</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Thoughtworks Holding, Inc. (NASDAQ: TWKS) resulting from allegations that Thoughtworks may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834743/673/en/TOP-RANKED-ROSEN-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Thoughtworks-Holding-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-TWKS.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONALLY RANKED ROSEN LAW FIRM Encourages Envoy Medical, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – COCH</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Envoy Medical, Inc. (NASDAQ: COCH) resulting from allegations that Envoy may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834742/673/en/NATIONALLY-RANKED-ROSEN-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Envoy-Medical-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-COCH.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A TOP RANKED LAW FIRM, Encourages Renovaro Biosciences Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – RENB</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Renovaro Biosciences Inc. (NASDAQ: RENB) resulting from allegations that Renovaro may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834741/673/en/ROSEN-A-TOP-RANKED-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Renovaro-Biosciences-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-RENB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING INVESTOR RIGHTS LAW FIRM, Encourages Altimmune, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – ALT</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces an investigation of potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Altimmune, Inc. (NASDAQ: ALT) resulting from allegations that Altimmune may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834740/673/en/ROSEN-A-LEADING-INVESTOR-RIGHTS-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Altimmune-Inc-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-ALT.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, TRUSTED NATIONAL TRIAL COUNSEL, Encourages The Chemours Company Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation – CC</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY:&lt;/strong&gt; Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces an investigation of potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of The Chemours Company (NYSE: CC) resulting from allegations that Chemours may have issued materially misleading business information to the investing public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834739/673/en/ROSEN-TRUSTED-NATIONAL-TRIAL-COUNSEL-Encourages-The-Chemours-Company-Investors-to-Inquire-About-Securities-Class-Action-Investigation-CC.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages Archer-Daniels-Midland Company Investors with Losses to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action – ADM</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 17:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of common stock of Archer-Daniels-Midland Company (NYSE: ADM) between April 30, 2020 and January 22, 2024, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 25, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834738/673/en/ROSEN-A-LEADING-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-Archer-Daniels-Midland-Company-Investors-with-Losses-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-ADM.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages British American Tobacco p.l.c Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action First Filed by the Firm – BTI</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY:&lt;/strong&gt; Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of the securities of British American Tobacco p.l.c. (NYSE: BTI) between February 9, 2023 and December 6, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important&lt;strong&gt; March 25, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline &lt;/strong&gt;in the securities class action commenced by the Firm.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834737/673/en/ROSEN-A-LEADING-LAW-FIRM-Encourages-British-American-Tobacco-p-l-c-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-First-Filed-by-the-Firm-BTI.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, TRUSTED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages BioVie Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action – BIVI</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of securities of BioVie Inc. (NASDAQ: BIVI) between August 5, 2021 and November 29, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 19, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834736/673/en/ROSEN-TRUSTED-INVESTOR-COUNSEL-Encourages-BioVie-Inc-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-BIVI.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>全國知名投資者法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵蒙受損失的 Evolution AB (publ) 投資者在對 EVVTY 提起證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  25, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事因：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒於 2019 年 2 月 14 日至 2023 年 10 月 25 日期間（含上述兩日期，簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買 Evolution AB (publ) (OTC: EVVTY) 的美國存托股份 (ADS) 之人士注意，&lt;strong&gt;首席原告的&lt;/strong&gt;重要&lt;strong&gt;截止日期為 2024 年 3 月 25 日。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834735/673/zh-hant/%E5%85%A8%E5%9C%8B%E7%9F%A5%E5%90%8D%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5%E8%92%99%E5%8F%97%E6%90%8D%E5%A4%B1%E7%9A%84-Evolution-AB-publ-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E5%B0%8D-EVVTY-%E6%8F%90%E8%B5%B7%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNTX 截止日期提醒：值得信賴的投資者法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵蒙受損失的 BioNTech SE 投資者在對 BNTX 提出證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 3 月 12 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  25, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事由：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒於 2022 年 3 月 30 日至 2023 年 10 月 13 日（含上述兩日期，簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買 BioNTech SE (NASDAQ: BNTX)證券之人士注意，&lt;strong&gt;首席原告的&lt;/strong&gt;重要&lt;strong&gt;截止日期為 2024 年 3 月 12 日。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834734/673/zh-hant/BNTX-%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F%E6%8F%90%E9%86%92-%E5%80%BC%E5%BE%97%E4%BF%A1%E8%B3%B4%E7%9A%84%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5%E8%92%99%E5%8F%97%E6%90%8D%E5%A4%B1%E7%9A%84-BioNTech-SE-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E5%B0%8D-BNTX-%E6%8F%90%E5%87%BA%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-3-%E6%9C%88-12-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSS 截止日期提醒：全球頂尖法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵損失逾 10 萬美元的 Maison Solutions Inc. 投資者在對 MSS 提出證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 3 月 4 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事因：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒 Maison Solutions Inc. (NASDAQ: MSS) 以下證券的購買者：(1) 根據就 Maison Solutions 2023 年 10 月首次公開招股（「IPO」）而發布的註冊聲明及招股章程（合稱「註冊聲明」）和／或可追溯至該聲明而購買其 A 類普通股之人士；和／或 (2) 於 2023 年 10 月 5 日至 2023 年 12 月 15 日期間（含上述兩日期，簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買其證券之人士，注意&lt;strong&gt;首席原告的&lt;/strong&gt;重要&lt;strong&gt;截止日期為 2024 年 3 月 4 日&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834733/673/zh-hant/MSS-%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F%E6%8F%90%E9%86%92-%E5%85%A8%E7%90%83%E9%A0%82%E5%B0%96%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5%E6%90%8D%E5%A4%B1%E9%80%BE-10-%E8%90%AC%E7%BE%8E%E5%85%83%E7%9A%84-Maison-Solutions-Inc-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E5%B0%8D-MSS-%E6%8F%90%E5%87%BA%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-3-%E6%9C%88-4-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>首屈一指的投資者法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵損失超過 10 萬美元的 Dada Nexus Limited 投資者在該律所對 DADA 首次提起證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 3 月 11 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事因：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒於 2023 年 5 月 11 日至 2024 年 1 月 8 日（含上述兩日期）期間（簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買 Dada Nexus Limited (NASDAQ: DADA) 證券之人士注意，由該律所首次提起的證券集體訴訟中，&lt;strong&gt;首席原告的&lt;/strong&gt;重要&lt;strong&gt;截止日期是 2024 年 3 月 11 日&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834732/673/zh-hant/%E9%A6%96%E5%B1%88%E4%B8%80%E6%8C%87%E7%9A%84%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5%E6%90%8D%E5%A4%B1%E8%B6%85%E9%81%8E-10-%E8%90%AC%E7%BE%8E%E5%85%83%E7%9A%84-Dada-Nexus-Limited-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E8%A9%B2%E5%BE%8B%E6%89%80%E5%B0%8D-DADA-%E9%A6%96%E6%AC%A1%E6%8F%90%E8%B5%B7%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-3-%E6%9C%88-11-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VNET 重要截止日期：全球投資者法律顧問 ROSEN 鼓勵 VNET Group, Inc. 投資者在對 VNET 提出證券集體訴訟的重要截止日期 2 月 26 日前聘請律師</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;紐約, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;strong&gt;事因：&lt;/strong&gt;全球投資者權益律師事務所 Rosen Law Firm 提醒於 2022 年 4 月 8 日至 2023 年 2 月 15 日期間（含上述兩日期，簡稱「集體訴訟期」）購買 VNET Group, Inc. (NASDAQ: VNET)證券之人士注意 &lt;strong&gt;2024 年 2 月 26 日這一&lt;/strong&gt;重要的&lt;strong&gt;首席原告截止日期&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834731/673/zh-hant/VNET-%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-%E5%85%A8%E7%90%83%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E6%B3%95%E5%BE%8B%E9%A1%A7%E5%95%8F-ROSEN-%E9%BC%93%E5%8B%B5-VNET-Group-Inc-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%80%85%E5%9C%A8%E5%B0%8D-VNET-%E6%8F%90%E5%87%BA%E8%AD%89%E5%88%B8%E9%9B%86%E9%AB%94%E8%A8%B4%E8%A8%9F%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E8%A6%81%E6%88%AA%E6%AD%A2%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%9F-2-%E6%9C%88-26-%E6%97%A5%E5%89%8D%E8%81%98%E8%AB%8B%E5%BE%8B%E5%B8%AB.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDER UPDATE: Halper Sadeh LLC Investigates AVRO, CTLT, DOOR, FANG</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Halper Sadeh LLC, an investor rights law firm, is investigating the following companies for potential violations of the federal securities laws and/or breaches of fiduciary duties to shareholders relating to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834730/0/en/SHAREHOLDER-UPDATE-Halper-Sadeh-LLC-Investigates-AVRO-CTLT-DOOR-FANG.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, SKILLED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages B. Riley Financial, Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action – RILY</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY:&lt;/strong&gt; Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of common stock of B. Riley Financial, Inc. (NASDAQ: RILY) between May 10, 2023 and November 9, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 25, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834729/673/en/ROSEN-SKILLED-INVESTOR-COUNSEL-Encourages-B-Riley-Financial-Inc-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-RILY.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, SKILLED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages Cummins Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action First Filed by the Firm – CMI</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="left"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p align="justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: &lt;/strong&gt;Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of the securities of Cummins Inc. (NYSE: CMI) between April 30, 2019 and December 21, 2023, both dates inclusive (the “Class Period”), of the important &lt;strong&gt;March 15, 2024 lead plaintiff deadline &lt;/strong&gt;in the securities class action first filed by the Firm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834727/673/en/ROSEN-SKILLED-INVESTOR-COUNSEL-Encourages-Cummins-Inc-Investors-to-Secure-Counsel-Before-Important-Deadline-in-Securities-Class-Action-First-Filed-by-the-Firm-CMI.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDER UPDATE: Halper Sadeh LLC Investigates AXNX, KAMN, BATL, JNPR</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Halper Sadeh LLC, an investor rights law firm, is investigating the following companies for potential violations of the federal securities laws and/or breaches of fiduciary duties to shareholders relating to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834726/0/en/SHAREHOLDER-UPDATE-Halper-Sadeh-LLC-Investigates-AXNX-KAMN-BATL-JNPR.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDER UPDATE: Halper Sadeh LLC Investigates CBAY, IONM, WISH, FREE</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p align="justify"&gt;NEW YORK, Feb.  24, 2024  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Halper Sadeh LLC, an investor rights law firm, is investigating the following companies for potential violations of the federal securities laws and/or breaches of fiduciary duties to shareholders relating to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/02/24/2834725/0/en/SHAREHOLDER-UPDATE-Halper-Sadeh-LLC-Investigates-CBAY-IONM-WISH-FREE.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBLY CLASS ACTION NOTICE:  Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp;amp; Check, LLP Reminds Mobileye Global Inc. (MBLY) Shareholders of Securities Fraud Class Action Lawsuit and Encourages Investors with Substantial Losses to Contact the Firm</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RADNOR, Pa., Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- The law firm of Kessler Topaz Meltzer &amp; Check, LLP (www.ktmc.com) informs investors that a securities class action lawsuit has been filed against Mobileye Global Inc. ("Mobileye") (NASDAQ: MBLY). The action charges Mobileye with violations of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/mbly-class-action-notice--kessler-topaz-meltzer--check-llp-reminds-mobileye-global-inc-mbly-shareholders-of-securities-fraud-class-action-lawsuit-and-encourages-investors-with-substantial-losses-to-contact-the-firm-302070279.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING INVESTOR RIGHTS LAW FIRM, Encourages Hut 8 Corp. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action - HUT</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of securities of Hut 8 Corp. (NASDAQ: HUT) between November 9, 2023 and January 18, 2024, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the April 8, 2024 lead plaintiff...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-a-leading-investor-rights-law-firm-encourages-hut-8-corp-investors-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action--hut-302070044.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A GLOBALLY RESPECTED LAW FIRM, Encourages GrafTech International Ltd. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action - EAF</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of common stock of GrafTech International Ltd. (NYSE: EAF) between February 8, 2019 and August 3, 2023, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the important March 25,...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-a-globally-respected-law-firm-encourages-graftech-international-ltd-investors-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action--eaf-302070271.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratolaunch Completes 2nd Captive Carry Flight with TA-1 Test Vehicle</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 21:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MOJAVE, Calif., Feb 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- Stratolaunch announces the completion of a second captive carry flight with the first powered Talon-A hypersonic vehicle, TA-1. The flight was the thirteenth for the company's launch platform Roc and the second in which the aircraft carried a...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/stratolaunch-completes-2nd-captive-carry-flight-with-ta-1-test-vehicle-302070394.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, RECOGNIZED INVESTOR COUNSEL, Encourages Future FinTech Group Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action First Filed by the Firm - FTFT</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of the securities of Future FinTech Group Inc. (NASDAQ: FTFT) between March 10, 2020 and January 11, 2024, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the important March...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-recognized-investor-counsel-encourages-future-fintech-group-inc-investors-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action-first-filed-by-the-firm--ftft-302070042.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating a 'Transformative Figure in Sports and Leadership'</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;USPS Dedicates Forever Stamp Honoring UCLA Coach John Wooden LOS ANGELES, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- John Wooden's extraordinary and enduring contributions to college basketball and the athletic community worldwide were lauded during the Postal Service's dedication ceremony for the new...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/celebrating-a-transformative-figure-in-sports-and-leadership-302070315.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZTE brengt schitterende 5G-A hoogtepunten naar MWC 2024 en rolt de slimme toekomst uit</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BARCELONA, Spanje, 24 februari 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- ZTE Corporation (0763.HK / 000063.SZ), een wereldwijd toonaangevende leverancier van oplossingen voor informatie- en communicatietechnologie, presenteert met trots de hoogtepunten van 5G-A tijdens het Mobile World Congress 2024. Dit...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/zte-brengt-schitterende-5g-a-hoogtepunten-naar-mwc-2024-en-rolt-de-slimme-toekomst-uit-302070385.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNTX DEADLINE NOTICE: ROSEN, A LEADING NATIONAL FIRM, Encourages BioNTech SE Investors with Losses in Excess of $100K to Secure Counsel Before Important March 12 Deadline in Securities Class Action - BNTX</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of securities of BioNTech SE (NASDAQ: BNTX) between March 30, 2022 and October 13, 2023, both dates inclusive (the "Class Period"), of the important March 12, 2024 lead...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bntx-deadline-notice-rosen-a-leading-national-firm-encourages-biontech-se-investors-with-losses-in-excess-of-100k-to-secure-counsel-before-important-march-12-deadline-in-securities-class-action--bntx-302070017.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash News: OKX Hosts 'Manta Trading Campaign' Featuring USD20,000 Manta Token Prize Pool</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SINGAPORE, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- OKX, a leading Web3 technology company, has issued updates for February 24, 2024. OKX Hosts 'Manta Trading Campaign' Featuring USD20,000 Manta Token Prize Pool OKX today announced the launch of its 'Manta Trading Campaign,' giving users who...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/flash-news-okx-hosts-manta-trading-campaign-featuring-usd20-000-manta-token-prize-pool-302070380.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZTE s'apprête à apporter au MWC 2024 les points forts de la 5G-A, pour un avenir intelligent</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BARCELONE, Espagne, 24 février 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- ZTE Corporation (0763.HK / 000063.SZ), l'un des principaux fournisseurs mondiaux de solutions de technologies de l'information et de la communication, est fier de dévoiler les points forts de la 5G-A lors du Mobile World Congress 2024....&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/zte-sapprete-a-apporter-au-mwc-2024-les-points-forts-de-la-5g-a-pour-un-avenir-intelligent-302070376.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A GLOBAL AND LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages Innodata Inc. Investors with Losses to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action - INOD</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces the filing of a class action lawsuit on behalf of purchasers of common stock of Innodata Inc. (NASDAQ: INOD) between May 9, 2019 and February 14, 2024, both dates inclusive (the...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-a-global-and-leading-law-firm-encourages-innodata-inc-investors-with-losses-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action--inod-302070244.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZTE präsentiert brillante 5G-A-Highlights auf dem MWC 2024 und enthüllt die intelligente Zukunft</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BARCELONA, Spanien, 24. Februar 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- ZTE Corporation (0763.HK / 000063.SZ), ein weltweit führender Anbieter von Informations- und Kommunikationstechnologielösungen, ist stolz darauf, die 5G-A-Highlights auf dem Mobile World Congress 2024 zu enthüllen. Diese Initiative...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/zte-prasentiert-brillante-5g-a-highlights-auf-dem-mwc-2024-und-enthullt-die-intelligente-zukunft-302070375.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGTN: CMG 2024 Lantern Festival Gala captivates audience with blend of tradition and technology</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BEIJING, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- As twilight descends upon the 15th day of the Chinese New Year, the maiden full moon of the Year of the Dragon rises in the sky, commencing a new lunar cycle. The Chinese Lantern Festival, also known as Yuan Xiao Jie, marks the end of Chinese New...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cgtn-cmg-2024-lantern-festival-gala-captivates-audience-with-blend-of-tradition-and-technology-302070368.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, LEADING TRIAL ATTORNEYS, Encourages Hywin Holdings Ltd. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation - HYW</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Hywin Holdings Ltd. (NASDAQ: HYW) resulting from allegations that Hywin Holdings may have issued materially...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-leading-trial-attorneys-encourages-hywin-holdings-ltd-investors-to-inquire-about-securities-class-action-investigation--hyw-302070312.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>84 Lumber Celebrates New, Bigger Sarasota, Florida Location</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Building materials supplier makes $100,000 donation to the Bay Pines Fisher House EIGHTY FOUR, Pa., Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- 84 Lumber, the nation's largest privately held building materials supplier, celebrated the opening of its new location at 1315 17th Street East, Palmetto,...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/84-lumber-celebrates-new-bigger-sarasota-florida-location-302070364.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGTN: CMG 2024 Lantern Festival Gala captivates audience with blend of tradition and technology</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BEIJING, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- As twilight descends upon the 15th day of the Chinese New Year, the maiden full moon of the Year of the Dragon rises in the sky, commencing a new lunar cycle. The Chinese Lantern Festival, also known as Yuan Xiao Jie, marks the end of Chinese New...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cgtn-cmg-2024-lantern-festival-gala-captivates-audience-with-blend-of-tradition-and-technology-302070366.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, LEADING TRIAL ATTORNEYS, Encourages Fluence Energy, Inc. Investors to Inquire About Securities Class Action Investigation - FLNC</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces an investigation of potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of Fluence Energy, Inc. (NASDAQ: FLNC) resulting from allegations that Fluence Energy may have issued...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-leading-trial-attorneys-encourages-fluence-energy-inc-investors-to-inquire-about-securities-class-action-investigation--flnc-302070050.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSS DEADLINE NOTICE: ROSEN, A LEADING LAW FIRM, Encourages Maison Solutions Inc. Investors with Losses in Excess of $100K to Secure Counsel Before Important March 4 Deadline in Securities Class Action - MSS</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, reminds purchasers of Maison Solutions Inc. (NASDAQ: MSS): (1) Class A common stock pursuant and/or traceable to the registration statement and prospectus (collectively, the "Registration...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/mss-deadline-notice-rosen-a-leading-law-firm-encourages-maison-solutions-inc-investors-with-losses-in-excess-of-100k-to-secure-counsel-before-important-march-4-deadline-in-securities-class-action--mss-302070005.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSEN, A LEADING AND RANKED FIRM, Encourages Amplitude, Inc. Investors to Secure Counsel Before Important Deadline in Securities Class Action - AMPL</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, announces the filing of a class action lawsuit on behalf of purchasers of stock of Amplitude, Inc. (NASDAQ: AMPL) between September 21, 2021 and February 16, 2022, both dates inclusive (the...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/rosen-a-leading-and-ranked-firm-encourages-amplitude-inc-investors-to-secure-counsel-before-important-deadline-in-securities-class-action--ampl-302070311.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America-China Chamber of Commerce and Asia International M&amp;amp;A Fund sign strategic cooperation agreement</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHICAGO, Feb. 24, 2024 /PRNewswire/ -- At the invitation of Mr. Siva Yam, President of the United States of America-China Chamber of Commerce, Mr. Zhang Zhiguo, the CEO of Asia International Mergers and Acquisitions Fund for China, along with his delegation, arrived in Chicago, the...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/america-china-chamber-of-commerce-and-asia-international-ma-fund-sign-strategic-cooperation-agreement-302070357.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AstraAI: Redefining Innovation with the Ultimate AI Ecosystem in BlockchainBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836357/astraai-redefining-innovation-with-the-ultimate-ai-ecosystem-in-blockchain</link>
      <date>2024-02-24T15:25:00.000Z</date>
      <description>DUBAI, UAE / ACCESSWIRE / February 24, 2024 / In a mere 100 days since its launch,AstraAIhas not only demonstrated its prowess in the cryptocurrency market but has also established itself as a beacon of innovation with the rollout of a suite of groundbreaking AI tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavion Energy Empowers Clients with Tax-Free Earnings for Enhanced Financial GrowthBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836356/xavion-energy-empowers-clients-with-tax-free-earnings-for-enhanced-financial-growth</link>
      <date>2024-02-24T15:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>WIGAN, ENGLAND / ACCESSWIRE / February 24, 2024 / Xavion Energy, a pioneering financial services provider, has achieved a significant milestone by securing approval for tax-free earnings for its valued clients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Future of Trading: Green-Ultra.com Review Broker Emerges with Secret TechnologyBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836355/unveiling-the-future-of-trading-green-ultracom-review-broker-emerges-with-secret-technology</link>
      <date>2024-02-24T15:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>BIRMINGHAM, ENGLAND / ACCESSWIRE / February 24, 2024 / A new player has emerged in the World of Online Trading, promising to change the paradigm of how traders interact with the financial markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinnUp Makes Business Loans Faster and Easier with AI-Powered Platform LaunchBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836349/finnup-makes-business-loans-faster-and-easier-with-ai-powered-platform-launch</link>
      <date>2024-02-24T10:35:00.000Z</date>
      <description>MUMBAI, INDIA / ACCESSWIRE / February 24, 2024 / FinnUp, a new B2B debt marketplace, a platform that uses artificial intelligence (AI) to match businesses with lenders in just 4-5 hours, saving weeks of waiting and uncertainty, was launched on 14th February 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lemko Announces Technology Partnership With Wytec Intl to Enhance Small Cell CapabilitiesTelecommunicationsPartnerships</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836254/lemko-announces-technology-partnership-with-wytec-intl-to-enhance-small-cell-capabilities</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T21:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SCHAUMBURG, IL / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Lemko Corporation ("Lemko") with its patented Distributed Mobile Architecture (DMA) announced today a partnership with Wytec International ("Wytec"), a fully reporting non-listed company and leading developer and integrator of patented mobile wireless and smart sensor solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Update: Sells Orillia Stone QuarryMetals &amp; MiningCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836348/rogue-update-sells-orillia-stone-quarry</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T20:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TORONTO, ON / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Rogue Resources Inc. (TSX-V:RRS) ("Rogue" or the "Company") is pleased to announce the sale of its Orillia quarry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moodrink(TM) Achieves Remarkable Success and Reception With Canada-Wide Launch, Selling Out in Select Stores and Prompting Bettermoo(d) To Plan Second Production RunFood &amp; Beverage ProductsCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836305/moodrink-achieves-remarkable-success-and-reception-with-canada-wide-launch-selling-out-in-select-stores-and-prompting-bettermood-to-plan-second-production-run</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T19:25:00.000Z</date>
      <description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / bettermoo(d) Food Corporation (CSE:MOOO)(OTCQB:MOOOF)(Frankfurt:0I5A) (WKN: A3D8PP) (the "Company" or "bettermoo(d)") is pleased to announce that following the successful nationwide launch of Moodrink™ (the "Product") (see press release dated February</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Minerals Engages Independent Trading Group As Market MakerMetals &amp; MiningCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836346/troy-minerals-engages-independent-trading-group-as-market-maker</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T19:10:00.000Z</date>
      <description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / TroyMinerals Inc. ("Troy" or the "Company") (CSE:TROY);(OTCQB:TROYF);(FSE:VJ3) is pleased to announce it has engaged the services of Independent Trading Group ("ITG") to provide market-making services in accordance with policies of the Canadian Securities Exchange ("CSE").</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Education Communities Corp. Reports Director Election ResultsBanking &amp; Financial ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836342/global-education-communities-corp-reports-director-election-results</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T19:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Global Education Communities Corp. (TSX:GEC)(OTCQX:GECSF) ("GECC") reports the director election voting results from its annual general meeting held today. All of the director nominees, as listed in the management information circular dated January 8, 2024, were elected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELEHEAR Leads Collaboration with CaringKind and Sunrise for a Tour of MoMA to Champion Hearing Health in the Fight Against Alzheimer's on World Hearing DayBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesPartnerships</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836134/elehear-leads-collaboration-with-caringkind-and-sunrise-for-a-tour-of-moma-to-champion-hearing-health-in-the-fight-against-alzheimers-on-world-hearing-day</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T18:25:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / In a groundbreaking effort to raise awareness about the vital connection between hearing loss prevention and Alzheimer's disease,ELEHEAR , a trailblazing hearing aid company, has joined forces with CaringKind and Sunrise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tirios, Real Estate Investment Platform, Files With the SEC Under Regulation A+ (Mini-IPO)TiriosReal EstateRegulatory</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836325/tirios-real-estate-investment-platform-files-with-the-sec-under-regulation-a-mini-ipo</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T17:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>AUSTIN, TX / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Tirios, a real estate investment platform, is announcing its recent filing with the SEC under Regulation A+ (Mini-IPO).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPR Cell Phone Repair Debuts New Store in Chula Vista, CABusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836314/cpr-cell-phone-repair-debuts-new-store-in-chula-vista-ca</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T17:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CHULA VISTA, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / CPR Cell Phone Repair, a frontrunner in the electronics repair industry, is thrilled to welcome its latest addition, CPR Cell Phone Repair Chula Vista, located at 1750 E Palomar St, Suite 4, Chula Vista, CA, 91913.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban-American Designer Michelle Garcia to Showcase Collection at EPN New York Fashion WeekConsumer &amp; Retail ProductsCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836311/cuban-american-designer-michelle-garcia-to-showcase-collection-at-epn-new-york-fashion-week</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:50:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Esteemed Cuban-American fashion designer Michelle Garcia is set to captivate the runway at the highly anticipated EPN New York Fashion Week, featuring her "Timeless Luxe" Collection. With her unique blend of cultural influences and innovative designs, Garcia promises to deliver a mesmerizing , high quality collection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runaway New York Announces Its First Solo Showcase in MiamiConsumer &amp; Retail ProductsCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836295/runaway-new-york-announces-its-first-solo-showcase-in-miami</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:35:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Runaway New York, a contemporary clothing label known for its cut and sewn apparel and pop-ups around the world, is thrilled to announce its first solo showcase in Miami, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newor Media and PrestoSports Team Up Across Thousands of Premium Sports PropertiesPublishing &amp; MediaPartnerships</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836306/newor-media-and-prestosports-team-up-across-thousands-of-premium-sports-properties</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Newor Media and PrestoSports announce they are teaming up to maximize the value of over a thousand official sports websites of top colleges, universities, regional sports conferences, leagues, semi-professional teams and other organizations from around the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techvestor Adds 120th Property to Its Growing Portfolio of Short-Term Rentals for Families, Groups, and More Business &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836300/techvestor-adds-120th-property-to-its-growing-portfolio-of-short-term-rentals-for-families-groups-and-more</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CLEARWATER, FL / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 /Techvestor , whose proprietary software analyzes over 18MM data points and 250+ short-term rental markets every month, has now added its 120th property to its portfolio over the last few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havertys Announces First Quarter Cash Dividend Consumer &amp; Retail ProductsDividends</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836217/havertys-announces-first-quarter-cash-dividend</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:11:00.000Z</date>
      <description>ATLANTA, GA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / HAVERTYS (NYSE:HVT)(NYSE:HVT.A) announced today that its board of directors declared a cash dividend to be paid on the outstanding shares of the two classes of $1 par value common stock of the company at a rate of $0.30 per share on the common stock and $0.28 per share on the Class A common stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHG Capital Corporation Announces Additional Contribution to Trust Account to Extend Period to Consummate Business CombinationBanking &amp; Financial ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836099/hhg-capital-corporation-announces-additional-contribution-to-trust-account-to-extend-period-to-consummate-business-combination</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:10:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / HHG Capital Corporation (the "Company") (NASDAQ:HHGC) announced today that the Company made a deposit on February 23, 2024 to the trust account and extended the amount of time it has available to complete a business combination from February 23, 2024 to March 23, 2024, by depositing $0.0333 for each issued and outstanding company ordinary share issued in the Company's initial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNH Expands Sustainable Innovation Through Investment in AI Company Bem AgroIndustrial &amp; ManufacturingEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836292/cnh-expands-sustainable-innovation-through-investment-in-ai-company-bem-agro</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:10:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / CNH continues to strengthen its tech stack with Ag Tech solutions that make farming easier, more efficient, and more sustainable for farmers around the globe. CNH Ventures, the investment arm of the company, has taken a minority stake in Bem Agro - a Brazilian startup and existing supplier to CNH.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Stress and Increase Well-Being: VAST Coaching Launches 12-Week Private Co-Regulation Cohort for LeadersBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836286/reduce-stress-and-increase-well-being-vast-coaching-launches-12-week-private-co-regulation-cohort-for-leaders</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T16:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>IRVINE, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 /VAST Coaching , which restores the passion of executives by helping them to prioritize their personal well-being and uniqueness, has announced its pilot coaching program for leaders. The 12-week private group coaching cohort, which will begin online on March 5, 2024, will focus on solutions for the frustrations, fears, and challenges that executives typically struggle with on the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Milestone for Iran's Startup Ecosystem: Tapsi Acquired in Landmark Stock Market TransactionTransportationMergers and Acquisitions</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836163/a-milestone-for-irans-startup-ecosystem-tapsi-acquired-in-landmark-stock-market-transaction</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T15:40:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TEHRAN, IRAN / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / In a historic development for Iran's technology sector, a major player in the country's FMCG and retail industry has acquired a 70% stake in Tapsi, a prominent ride-hailing service, for approximately 2.1 trillion Iranian Rials ($38 million).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$16,620,625 Raised on Initial Closing. Books Now Re-Open for a Final Closing on April 12, 2024Banking &amp; Financial ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836277/16620625-raised-on-initial-closing-books-now-re-open-for-a-final-closing-on-april-12-2024</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T15:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Maple Leaf Critical Minerals 2024 Enhanced Flow-Through Limited Partnership (the "Partnership") is pleased to announce that it has completed its initial closing on February 23, 2024 for gross proceeds of $16,620,625. The books are now reopened and will close on Thursday, April 11, 2024 at 12:00 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omega Protein and Ocean Harvesters: Supporting Menhaden ScienceBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836270/omega-protein-and-ocean-harvesters-supporting-menhaden-science</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T15:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>REEDVILLE, VA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Omega Protein and its fishing partner Ocean Harvesters have long supported research projects that improve understanding of the Atlantic menhaden population and its ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xuirin Finance (XUIRIN) Launches Presale, Aiming to Transform the DeFi SectorBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836278/xuirin-finance-xuirin-launches-presale-aiming-to-transform-the-defi-sector</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T15:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>BANKSTOWN, AUSTRALIA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / In a significant stride towards revolutionizing the decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape, Xuirin Finance is thrilled to announce the launch of its presale, effective immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Broadus Collection by Shante &amp; Snoop Dogg, a Luxury Scarf Line, Making an Appearance at the Atlanta Bronner Bros ShowConsumer &amp; Retail ProductsPartnerships</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836271/the-broadus-collection-by-shante-snoop-dogg-a-luxury-scarf-line-making-an-appearance-at-the-atlanta-bronner-bros-show</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T15:05:00.000Z</date>
      <description>ATLANTA, GA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Shante "Boss Lady" Broadus, entrepreneur, philanthropist, and CEO of Boss Lady Entertainment, where she is the Official Executive Team Manager of husband Snoop Dogg, will be featuring their Broadus Collection Scarfs at the Bronner Bros show in Atlanta on Feb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGFNS International Unveils New Think Tank to Advance Health Workforce Development Scholarship and Solutions Worldwide Healthcare &amp; PharmaceuticalCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836266/cgfns-international-unveils-new-think-tank-to-advance-health-workforce-development-scholarship-and-solutions-worldwide</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T15:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>PHILADELPHIA, PA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / CGFNS International announced today it has established a Global Health Workforce Development Institute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omega Protein and Ocean Harvesters: Committed to SustainabilityBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836258/omega-protein-and-ocean-harvesters-committed-to-sustainability</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T14:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>REEDVILLE, VA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23 2024 / The menhaden fishery has operated continuously out of Reedville, Virginia for 145 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Radio Host, Marc James Benarzyk, Shares Highlights from His 20 Year CareerComputers, Technology &amp; InternetCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836262/sports-radio-host-marc-james-benarzyk-shares-highlights-from-his-20-year-career</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T14:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TAMPA, FL / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Sports Radio Host Marc James Benarzyk shares highlights that encapsulate his remarkable 20-year career in the sports media industry. One pivotal moment occurred in 2017 when NESN welcomed James as an On-Air Personality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Month-End Portfolio Data Now Available for Ares Dynamic Credit Allocation Fund, Inc.www.arespublicfunds.comBanking &amp; Financial ServicesEarnings</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836015/month-end-portfolio-data-now-available-for-ares-dynamic-credit-allocation-fund-inc</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T14:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Ares Capital Management II LLC today announced that monthly fund composition and performance data for Ares Dynamic Credit Allocation Fund, Inc. (NYSE:ARDC) as of January 31, 2024 is now available via www.arespublicfunds.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan Announces Receivership Application Defeat, Update Re Corporate Milestones Real EstateCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836264/caravan-announces-receivership-application-defeat-update-re-corporate-milestones</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T14:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CALGARY, AB / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Caravan Trailer Lodges of Alberta Ltd. (the "Company" or "Caravan") is pleased to announce that the previously announced application to appoint a receiver has been dismissed. That application was brought by Herb Styles, on his own and without the support of the Board of Caravan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omega Protein and Ocean Harvesters: Virginia's Economic Engine with a Global ReachBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836252/omega-protein-and-ocean-harvesters-virginias-economic-engine-with-a-global-reach</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T14:05:00.000Z</date>
      <description>REEDVILLE, VA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Omega Protein and our fishing partners Ocean Harvesters are at the center of one of the most important fisheries in America, the Atlantic menhaden fishery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omega Protein and Ocean Harvesters: Who We AreBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836236/omega-protein-and-ocean-harvesters-who-we-are</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>REEDVILLE, VA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / For 145 years, Virginia has been the center of one of America's largest fisheries, the Atlantic menhaden fishery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Clorox Company Named Barron's Most Sustainable U.S. Company for Second Year in a RowIndustrial &amp; ManufacturingEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836255/the-clorox-company-named-barrons-most-sustainable-us-company-for-second-year-in-a-row</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>OAKLAND, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / The Clorox Company (NYSE:CLX) has earned the top ranking on Barron's 2024 100 Most Sustainable Companies list - its second consecutive year in the top spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exciting New Season of 'Bible in a Year With Jack Graham' on Pray.com Tops Religion Podcasts Charts, Inviting Listeners to Dive Deeper With GodPublishing &amp; MediaProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836240/exciting-new-season-of-bible-in-a-year-with-jack-graham-on-praycom-tops-religion-podcasts-charts-inviting-listeners-to-dive-deeper-with-god</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>LOS ANGELES, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Pray.com, the leading app for prayer and faith-based audio content, announces season 2 of "Bible in a Year with Jack Graham" has hit No. 1 on Apple among religious podcasts as it invites listeners to embark on an epic journey that will deepen their understanding of Scripture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternationalReserve Unveils Key Strategies for Modern Investors to Navigate Evolving Financial MarketsComputers, Technology &amp; InternetCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836246/internationalreserve-unveils-key-strategies-for-modern-investors-to-navigate-evolving-financial-markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>TORONTO, ON / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / In response to the ever-evolving landscape of global finance, InternationalReserve today unveiled critical insights aimed at equipping investors with the knowledge and strategies needed to navigate the complexities of today's financial markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unstoppable and Pudgy Penguins Join Forces to Launch First NFT Community-Focused Web3 DomainsUnstoppable DomainsPudgy PenguinsBlockchain &amp; CryptocurrencyProduct Announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835939/unstoppable-and-pudgy-penguins-join-forces-to-launch-first-nft-community-focused-web3-domains</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>PARIS, FRANCE / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Leading web3 domain names and digital identity provider Unstoppable Domains (UD) today announced a new groundbreaking partnership with widely popular Web3 brand Pudgy Penguins, with the addition of ".pudgy," the 10th top-level domain (TLD) in UD's partner portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albertsons Companies' Jewel-Osco Division Hosts 25th Annual Black History Month CelebrationConsumer &amp; Retail ProductsDiversity, Equity and Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836238/albertsons-companies-jewel-osco-division-hosts-25th-annual-black-history-month-celebration</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CHICAGO, IL / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Albertsons Companies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nuts and Bolts of an Award-Winning CareerAirlines for AmericaTravelEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836239/the-nuts-and-bolts-of-an-award-winning-career</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SAN DIEGO, CA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / American Airlines aviation maintenance technician (AMT) Ken MacTiernan was honored with the Airlines for America (A4A) Nuts and Bolts award, marking the first time an AMT has received the award while actively working in the profession since the award launched in 1967.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carry Protocol Unveils Transition Plans to Web3 Game Infrastructure with Community EndorsementPublishing &amp; MediaCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836098/carry-protocol-unveils-transition-plans-to-web3-game-infrastructure-with-community-endorsement</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T13:07:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / In a groundbreaking development, the Carry Protocol, renowned for its innovative intersection of game development and Web3 advertising, has released a comprehensive white paper today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kohler's Week of Service Honors MLK's Legacy, Inspires Action for Community GoodBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836229/kohlers-week-of-service-honors-mlks-legacy-inspires-action-for-community-good</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T12:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Kohler Co.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jiu Jitsu Champion Makes Strategic Investment in Panhwar Crypto, Secures Panhwar TokensPublishing &amp; MediaCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/835445/jiu-jitsu-champion-makes-strategic-investment-in-panhwar-crypto-secures-panhwar-tokens</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T12:42:00.000Z</date>
      <description>SALT LAKE CITY, UT / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Panhwar Crypto, the groundbreaking force in the world of cryptocurrency, proudly announces the addition of a distinguished investor to its ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network-1 Declares Semi-Annual DividendClean TechnologyDividends</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836215/network-1-declares-semi-annual-dividend</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T12:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW CANAAN, CT / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Network-1 Technologies, Inc. (NYSE American:NTIP) today announced that its Board of Directors has declared a semi-annual cash dividend of $0.05 per common share pursuant to its dividend policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Pacific Metals Corp. Announces Private Placement Financing and Proposal to Issue Replacement Convertible DebenturesMetals &amp; MiningCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836218/south-pacific-metals-corp-announces-private-placement-financing-and-proposal-to-issue-replacement-convertible-debentures</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T12:25:00.000Z</date>
      <description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / South Pacific Metals Corp. (TSX-V:SPMC)(FSE: 6J00) ("SPMC" or the "Company") announces a non-brokered private placement financing of up to 7,500,000 common shares in the capital of the Company (the "Shares") at a price of C$0.20 per Share for gross proceeds of up to C$1,500,000 (the "Offering").</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freedom Reads Brings Literary Presentation to Men’s and Women's Prisons in Rhode IslandEducationCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836175/freedom-reads-brings-literary-presentation-to-mens-and-womens-prisons-in-rhode-island</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T12:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>HAMDEN, CT / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / The national non-profit Freedom Reads today brings its first events to Rhode Island prisons. At both the John J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europacific Appoints New CFO and Corporate SecretaryMetals &amp; MiningManagement Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836211/europacific-appoints-new-cfo-and-corporate-secretary</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T11:45:00.000Z</date>
      <description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / EuroPacific Metals Inc (TSXV:EUP) ("the Company" or "Europacific") is pleased to announce the appointment of Mr. Brian Crawford as Chief Financial Officer and Corporate Secretary to the Company effective immediately. Mr. Crawford replaces Mr. Mihai Draguleasa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelloPrenup Named One of the '24 Startups to Watch in Boston in 2024' by BostInnoComputers, Technology &amp; InternetAwards</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836187/helloprenup-named-one-of-the-24-startups-to-watch-in-boston-in-2024-by-bostinno</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T11:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>BOSTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / BostInno's annual list celebrates the most promising startups driving innovation and growth in the vibrant Boston entrepreneurial ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living Our Purpose - Ivelisse LugoHealthcare &amp; PharmaceuticalEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836200/living-our-purpose-ivelisse-lugo</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T11:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / As the Chairman, CEO, and President of Quest Diagnostics, Jim Davis receives plenty of messages from various customers, business partners, and patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KFC Levelling the Playing Field for Over 800 KidsTravelEnvironmental, Social and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836186/kfc-levelling-the-playing-field-for-over-800-kids</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T11:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NORTHAMPTON, MA / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / Yum! Brands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celligence's Angel Ai Shows Nothing to Fear From AIReal EstateDiversity, Equity and Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836180/celligences-angel-ai-shows-nothing-to-fear-from-ai</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T11:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / The Angel Ai engineering team ("the Brillianeers") has built a neural network model in the form of a business-user-friendly spreadsheet. This spreadsheet has all the formulae exposed and is easy to understand. After a quick study, everyone will realize that there is nothing to fear because AI is just some form of addition, subtraction, multiplication, and division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Presidente Intercontinental Cancun Hotel Offers Rooms for Corporate EventsBusiness &amp; Professional ServicesCompany Update</title>
      <link>https://www.accesswire.com/836183/the-presidente-intercontinental-cancun-hotel-offers-rooms-for-corporate-events</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T11:00:00.000Z</date>
      <description>MEXICO CITY, MEXICO / ACCESSWIRE / February 23, 2024 / With its stunning beaches, world-class resorts, and vibrant culture, Cancun offers the perfect blend of business and leisure.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>