<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss>
  <channel>
    <title>business</title>
    <link>[{"blogUrl":"https://www.barrons.com/topics/markets?mod=BOL_TOPNAV","container":"article","header":"h3 a span","description":".BarronsTheme--summary--3UHA7uDx span","link":"h3 a","date":".BarronsTheme--timestamp--1QcAFHpF p","loadType":"puppeteer"},{"blogUrl":"https://www.wsj.com/business/deals","container":".css-bdm6mo","header":"h3 a span p","description":".css-m54ll1","link":"h3 a","date":".es486sg0","loadType":"puppeteer"}]</link>
    <description>feed for business</description>
    <item>
      <title>This UBS Leader Likes a Lot About the Future, Including the Prospects for Stocks, Alternatives, and ESG</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/this-ubs-leader-likes-a-lot-about-the-future-including-the-prospects-for-stocks-alternatives-and-esg-ad4981a4?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T05:30:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Suni Harford, head of UBS’ asset-management arm, is retiring after 40 years on Wall Street. What she learned, and what she likes now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan’s Market Finally Hit New Record. Why It May Not Be Too Late to Get In.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/japans-market-new-record-bd0344e3?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T05:01:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Strong prospects for Japan’s technology sector, earnings growth, plus structural economic changes could mean further gains ahead for Japanese stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Sells $125 Million of Stock</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/jpmorgan-dimon-sells-stock-b568fc86?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T00:40:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Jamie Dimon sold $125 million of JPMorgan stock through a plan, while his wife Judith Kent sold $25 million of stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“What’s the Rush?” to Cut Interest Rates, Asks Fed Gov. Waller</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/fed-gov-waller-urges-caution-on-lowering-interest-rates-d8b275a9?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-23T00:36:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Higher-than-expected January inflation and a strong economy mean the Fed should wait to lower interest rates, Waller said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intuitive Machines Makes History With Moon Landing</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intuitive-machines-stock-moon-landing-ceed6402?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T23:56:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Intuitive Machines makes history Thursday with a landing near the south pole of the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Stock Soars After Earnings to Set a New High—and a Market Cap Record</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-earnings-rally-ai-91a22302?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T22:08:00.000Z</date>
      <description>The bar was high for Nvidia’s earnings, and yet the company cleared it easily. These were the key points from the chip maker's earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia, Super Micro, Rivian, Lucid, Synopsys, Moderna, Sunrun, Royal Caribbean, and More Stock Market Movers</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-market-movers-6219b841?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T21:37:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Fourth-quarter revenue at Nvidia jumps 265% from a year earlier and data-center revenue surges more than 400%, while shares of Rivian and Lucid fall sharply after the electric-vehicle makers issue production guidance below analysts’ estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novavax Stock Soars 25%. A Vaccine Purchase Settlement Is One Reason Why.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/novavax-stock-covid-vaccine-purchase-settlement-4bd47eb9?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T18:39:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Novavax reaches a settlement related to an advance purchase agreement with Gavi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia’s AI Boom Spurs Tons of Other Stocks</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-ai-boom-amd-arm-super-micro-palantir-stock-price-29554905?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T17:54:00.000Z</date>
      <description>CEO Jen-Hsun Huang said AI is “enabling a whole new industry.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nice Gets an AI Boost to Earnings and Its Call-Center Software</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nice-earnings-ai-stock-price-9af17ddd?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T17:38:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Call-center-systems provider Nice posted a strong first quarter, along with robust guidance. It sees new opportunities with the application of artificial intelligence to its core offerings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderna Stock Jumps on Surprise Profit After Earnings Beat. What to Expect in 2024.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/moderna-stock-price-earnings-4fbeba26?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T17:21:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Moderna reports a profit of 55 cents a share on revenue of $2.8 billion in the fourth quarter, beating analysts’ expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Stock Is Outperforming EV Rivals as Musk Takes Swipe at Rivian</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-stock-price-today-f6a4dbb1?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T16:48:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Rivian and Lucid disappointed Wall Street with their production guidance. Their EVs are priced higher than Tesla’s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VinFast’s Stock Falls on Strong Guidance. The Drop Is Nothing Like Rivian’s.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/vinfast-earnings-stock-price-e12f6fa0?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T16:46:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Vietnamese EV start-up VinFast reports fourth-quarter sales of $437 million. Wall Street was looking for about $528 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Shows the AI Stock Rally Is Real. Worries Are, Too.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-stocks-market-rally-nvidia-magnificent-seven-964a7be5?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T16:16:00.000Z</date>
      <description>A fresh wave of tech optimism is fueling Thursday’s surge. J.P. Morgan warns that bulls won’t always be in charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian and Lucid Stocks Are Diving. The EV Story’s New Twist.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/rivian-stock-lucid-ev-earnings-5899bb78?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T16:15:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Electric-vehicle start-ups Rivian and Lucid both provided disappointing guidance. The U.S. luxury EV market looks saturated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Builders FirstSource Stock Soars on Earnings. Forget the Housing Slowdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/builders-firstsource-earnings-stock-price-397be087?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T15:41:00.000Z</date>
      <description>The supplier of building materials forecast higher 2024 sales than Wall Street had expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunrun Stock Drops After Earnings. How the Fed Can Brighten the Solar Sector.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/sunrun-stock-price-earnings-solar-52e97fab?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T15:35:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Sunnova also posted a disappointing quarterly report after the close Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remitly Global Stock Surges After Earnings. It’s ‘in the Early Innings’ of Growth Story, Says Analyst.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/remitly-global-earnings-stock-price-bca54211?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T15:27:00.000Z</date>
      <description>The provider of digital financial services tops quarterly revenue estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Rises as Crypto Traders Look to the S&amp;P 500 and Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/bitcoin-ethereum-price-crypto-markets-today-dc209762?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T15:22:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Bitcoin prices rebound as Nvidia’s standout quarterly results spur gains across stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan’s Nikkei Stock Index Hits Its Highest Level Since the 1980s. Warren Buffett Made the Right Call.</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/japan-stock-market-nikkei-all-time-high-berkshire-hathaway-0ec31cfe?refsec=markets&amp;mod=topics_markets</link>
      <date>2024-02-22T15:13:00.000Z</date>
      <description>Optimism about Japan’s economy, its emergence from decades of deflation, and the signs that the central bank will provide plenty of stimulus, mean stocks could keep going higher.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>